It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and is hurrying toward Navy HQ to save his brother Ace.
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard Pirates have attacked Marineford,
and an all-out war against the Navy has begun.
Oars!
Just a little further to Ace-kun...
Tsuno Tokage: Horned Toad Shadow
Look!  This is the right way to kill someone!
Captain Oars!
Damn the Seven Warlords!
Captain!
Oars!
Ace-kun...
Ace... kun...
Ace...
kun...
Oars!!!
If I use his corpse, I can create the ultimate zombie warrior!
Oars...
You're wide open, Whitebeard!
Vice Admiral Ronse!
H-He beat a giant -
and a Navy Vice Admiral at that - effortlessly!
Oars...
Charge across Oars!
This is priceless!
Doflamingo!  How could you do that to Oars?!
I won't let you get away with this!
What's so funny?!
You wanna know what's so funny?
This feeling of being right at the center of an era, that's what!
This is the turning point!
Quit spouting nonsense!
Just as I'd expect of the Commander!
Doflamingo is running away from him!
Rear Admiral Yukimura!
Impossible!  This is just too much for me!
I'm too scared to do anything!
So many strong people are falling, one after another!
There's nothing I can do here!
Someone like me can't...
Wait, Coby!  If you're running away, then I'm coming with you!
Return to the battlefield!
Let me go!  Please!
It's Admiral Akainu!  What's he doing here?
I'm afraid of dying!  When I think of my family, I can't even move!
Please!  I'm begging you!  Please!
We marines...
fight against pirates and carry the justice of the world on our backs.
Someone who runs away and lets an enemy see his back...
has no right to call himself a marine!
Someone like that is mere...
garbage!
If you truly cared for your family,
you wouldn't have disgraced them like this!
N-No way!  How could he do that to an ally?
Admiral Sakazuki!  We've finished preparing for the operation.
Have you now?  Finally!
Operation?
Ace!
Don't let them close the path Oars has opened!
Advance into the bay!
Right!  Let's break through the shore and clear a path!
Aim straight ahead and fire!
Damn!  It didn't even budge!
Leave it to me!
An icebreaker?
It's the Ice Witch, Whitey Bay!
Nothing to it.
Now, all of you!  Let's go!
Thanks!
Come on men!  Forward, into the bay!
What's wrong, Thirteenth Division Commander, Atomos the Buffalo?
W-What did you do to my body, Doflamingo?!
Commander Atomos!
Stay away!  Don't come near me!
What is it?
Hurry!
Commander!
Stay away!
Commander Atomos!
Why...
My body's not listening to me...
Stop this, Doflamingo!
Pirates are evil?  The Navy is righteous?
Those views change as often as the tides!
Kids who've never known peace have different values from those who've never known war.
Those who stand at the top can decide the definition of "evil".
This place is the turning point.
Justice will triumph, you say?
Of course it will!
Because the winners will become justice!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
The bay's been breached in two spots!
The Whitebeard Pirates and their allies are surging through both openings,
and they're attacking the bay in large numbers, Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
That's not a problem.
What?
Tsuru-san, commence the operation.
At last.
Move it!  Or you'll be more than just wounded!
Move it, old woman!
I've been washed!
I've been hung out to dry!
But it feels so nice!
You're a million years too young to stand a chance against me.
Calling all ships and all men!
You're planning something, aren't you?
Great general, Sengoku the Buddha.
This child's name is Gol D. Ace.
Gramps!
Why have you come here?  Do you wish to protest against my plan?
No, we're up against pirates.  There's no room for sympathy.
Then...
Be silent!
You don't mind, right?
I'm just gonna sit here.
You imbecile!
Ace!
What're you doing, Gramps?!
What do you mean, you're going out to sea?!
I'll never let you!
You're not my father, so quit acting all big and mighty!
Why should I listen to you, old Gramps?
Call me "Granddad"!
Gramps.
You want another taste of my Fist of Love?!
Granddad!
I'm gonna get much stronger and set out to sea together with Ace!
You idiot!  You too?!
Don't hit Luffy, you damn geezer!
"Damn"?!
Ace, how dare you?!
Listen up!  You never know when you'll be called into battle!
So when you eat, you have to eat as much as you can!
This is another important part of being a marine!
Remember it well, you two!
What do you mean, "Marine"?  That's not for you to decide!
What?!
I'm gonna be a pirate!
No, you're gonna be a marine!
A pirate!
A marine!
Delicious!
He ate it all!
That was so good!
So quick!
I'm gonna be a pirate...
If Luffy ever becomes a marine, he'll eat all the provisions on the ship in one day.
He might be even more dangerous than enemy pirates!
I have no sympathy for criminals...
but for my family, I do.
What... should I do?
Damn you Ace!  Why couldn't you just live as I told you?!
Ace...
You two are gonna become strong marines.
You got that?
You're gonna become strong marines.
Gramps...!
If you cause some sort of commotion here, I won't show you any mercy, Garp.
If I was gonna do something, I'd have done it already.
Did you hear their plan just now, Helmeppo-san?
Yeah...
They're gonna ignore Fire Fist Ace's scheduled execution time and just kill him now!
If they do that...
What's that?
Is that...?
Something's falling out of the sky!
Is it a sneak attack from the Whitebeard Pirates?
I knew you'd overdo it!
This is all because of his wink.
Vyou're blaming this on vme, Croco?!
Who cares?!  We're gonna die!
The sea beneath us is frozen solid!
Oh!  I'm made of rubber, so I'll be fine!
Then you'll be the only survivor!
We have to do something!
Vi don't want to die like this!
Someone, stop vus!
I never should've listened to you, Straw Hat!
Dammit!
Ace!
Luffy and the others have suddenly fallen from the sky,
and landed right in the middle of the battlefield.
Now that he can finally see his brother, Ace,
Luffy calls out to him as loudly as he can.
The final battle to save Ace begins now!
Next time, on One Piece:
Straw Hat's Team Arrives
The Battlefield is thrown into Chaos
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!