It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
After losing his brother Ace in the great war against the Navy,
Luffy was overwhelmed by sadness.
But now, we go back in time ten years...
This is the story of the brothers, Luffy and Ace.
Again, we turn time back a little...
To the night when the Celestial Dragon's ship
docked in Goa Kingdom.
In a small village in a certain region of East Blue...
Did you see that guy with the huge face
who was here this afternoon?
Yeah!  I've never seen anything like it!
Look!  His ship is huge too!
Five hundred and eighty...
Five hundred and eighty one...
Five hundred and eighty two...
Five hundred and eighty three...
Five hundred and eighty four...
Vyou're late, Dragon!
How long did vyou plan to keep vus waiting?!
I'm sorry.
Vyou... What's that?
This is awful!
You!  Quickly, bring a doctor!  This is an emergency!
Right away!
Really... Where have vyou been?!
I was watching the ceremony for the World Nobles.
How could vyou go there on vyour own,
without telling vme about it!
If you'd been there, we'd have stood out too much.
This...
We must grow stronger as quickly as possible.
How are our provisions?
A dojo in the village offered us some food.
Time to set sail!
We're going back to Baltigo!
Some months later, after the World Government's inspection of Goa Kingdom...
They've brought more trash!
The people have settled into their old routines...
The trash mountain is back, just like it was before.
Here I come, Ace!
What the hell was that?  You call this a fight?
No matter how much force you put into it,
there's no point if you can't hit me.
I told you, rubber really isn't suited for battle.
Shut up!  Don't say that!
What?!  Are you trying to say that I'm wrong?!
You're just an anchor who's immune to bulletfire!
Don't make fun of the Gomu Gomu Fruit!
Someday, I'll make you cry!
After all, I've thought up a technique more powerful than a pistol!
Luffy, great work!
Your arm stretched a lot further than it did yesterday!
Sabo!  You're far too soft on Luffy!
I really have become strong!
Stronger than I was yesterday!
Hey, Sabo!
Sabo was such a kind older brother...
What's that supposed to mean?!  Would you rather I died instead?!
I never said that!
But that's basically what you meant!
Ow!
Sabo never punched me like that!
What was that?!
What's with you?!  Be a little nicer, will you?!
No way!
Ow...
I've founded my own country.
A country?
What's this?
Me too.
Signs: Ace's Country, Luffy's Country
What is it now?
I'm gonna learn to survive on my own.  You guys can be Dadan's country.
I'm gonna borrow your bath every now and then.
Ace!  Help me out!  It's a bear!
You're gonna survive on your own, right?
Dammit...
Luffy!
Hey!  Dadan's country, is anyone here?!
Luffy is injured!  Please, treat his wounds!
Magra!  Please, help Luffy!
Now, now... Come in, quickly!
Now, now... This is no joke.
If his wounds had been any worse,
he could have died!
The three of you always fought these wild beasts together as a team, right?
It's my fault...
I thought that I learned that fighting on your own
doesn't prove that you're strong...
I'm worthless!
Completely worthless!
Ace...
I'm so sorry, Luffy!
So sorry!
Hey, you guys!
Makino-chan came all the way out here
to bring us some drinks!
How to greet people properly?
Yeah.
What brought about this change of attitude?
I'm Luffy's brother, after all.
Someday, I'd like to meet Captain Red Hair, and
thank him for everything he did for my little brother.
Why're you looking at me like that?!
I'm sorry.  But alright, I'll tell you.
So, first of all...
They ate and ran!
Wait!
Oh, we're being rude here!
Right...
Thanks for the food!
Shut up, you damn kids!  Just pay the bill!
I'm gonna win today!
Alright!
Today, we'll be having bear-stew for dinner!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Take care, Ace!
Sure!  See you later, Luffy!  I'll be going on ahead!
Right!  And when I set out to sea myself in three years, I'll be much stronger!
Do your best, Ace!
Take care of yourself!
Try not to catch a cold!
Just you wait!  I'll make a name for myself real soon!
Ace, the son of the Pirate King who had grown up in secret...
quietly set sail from the coast at the foot of Mt. Corvo.
There he goes.
Really, how is Garp going to take this?
You raise him, Dadan.
You gotta be kidding me!  Whose kid is that?!
Boss...
Ace has left.
That so?  I'm the one who'll get scolded by Garp for this...
That little brat was just hopeless.
Oh, right, I have a message to you from Ace.
What?!  Even now, after he's left, he's still complaining to me?!
He said, "Sorry for all the trouble, and thanks."
That idiot, he can't be serious!
What?  Boss, are you crying?
I'm not crying, you idiot!
Only three more years for me!
Damn... My aim was off.
That was close, Luffy.  Why don't you just aim a little lower?
I'll become stronger!
Much stronger!
Luffy!
Look at the newspapers!
What is it?
Look at this!
Amazing!  Ace made a name for himself!
The picture shows him with his pirate ship and crew!
Amazing!  Ace is amazing!
I'm not gonna lose to him!
Hey, come on!
I'm going now.  Aren't you gonna see me off?
Hey!
Oh, shut up...
The mayor and Makino know us, but we'd scare the other villagers if we came down from the mountain.
But...
Just get going already!
Oh... Well then, guys!
Thanks for everything!
Oh, don't embarrass us... No need for thanks.
Now, now... Take care.
Sure, I will!
Oh, right!
Dadan!  I hate mountain bandits...
Shut up, you little brat!
...but I like you guys!
Don't say dumb stuff like that, and just get lost, damn you!
Sheesh, you guys are just...
What, are you crying?
No, I'm not!
Windmill Village, at the outskirts of the Goa Kingdom on Dawn Island...
Hey, if you're going out to sea, then you should take my old fishing boat, Luffy!
You'll sink right away if you take that thing!
A rowing boat?  Come on, now!
I'm fine with this.  My journey begins right now!
Sabo!
Look at me!  I'm setting out to sea too!
Sabo was first.  Ace was second.
I'm the third to go, but I won't lose!
Wait for me, Ace!  I'll catch up to you soon!
What are you doing, Luffy?  Shouting and muttering to yourself like that...
Is it some sort of good luck charm?
That's not it.  It's a challenge!
Who's Ace?
No idea.
Alright, I'm going now.
There he goes, mayor...
I'm gonna miss him.
He's a disgrace to the village!  Becoming a pirate...
Ah... It's a great day to set sail!
That's...
So there you are, lord of the coastal waters.
You picked the wrong opponent.
Check out my attack, I've been practicing for the past ten years!
Learned your lesson yet, damn fish?
Incredible... He beat the lord of the coastal waters with one punch!
He's grown strong.
First, I've gotta gather a crew.
I'd like to have about ten people...
And then I'll need a pirate flag!
Alright... Here I come!
I'm gonna be...
the Pirate King!
And now we return to the present day...
His brother Ace is dead, and Luffy...
is crying.
Luffy-kun...
Pirate King?  Yeah, right!
I'm...
weak!
Garp returns to Windmill Village where he is met by an enraged Dadan.
At the same time, Luffy is overwhelmed
by sadness and helplessness after losing Ace.
Jinbe watches over Luffy struggling and suffering, and he recalls the words Ace once said to him.
Next time, on One Piece:
I Want to See Them!
Luffy's Tearful Shout
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!