It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
After losing his brother Ace in the great war against the Navy,
Luffy fell into despair.
We now go ten years back in time...
To determine who is worthy of the captain's seat,
Ace, Sabo & Luffy compete to defeat the great tiger.
Then they meet Naguri, a pirate who knew Roger, and he agreed to train Luffy as a pirate.
Why do you always do that?!
Just attack it head-on like an idiot?!
Shut up!  Your plan wasn't any better!
That didn't go well at all...
Tomorrow, maybe we should try stuffing poisonous mushrooms in some bait.
Wait... Despite its massive size, it's still just a cat, so...
Maybe we can use catnip?
Hey!
I wonder what Luffy's up to these days?
It's been a week since he left, right?
We'd better check on him soon.
I mean, it's Luffy...
Maybe the training's too tough for him, and he's crying "I wanna go home"...
Or, the training could have even killed him?!
What is it?
Aren't you worried about Luffy at all?
He's our little brother!
Shut up!  Whether he's crying or dead or whatever, it's none of my business!
Sheesh... You're always so damn stubborn...
You...
W-What was that?
Sorry about that!
Are you alright?  Really, I'm sorry!
Luffy!
Ace!  Sabo!  Long time no see!
Have you been looking after yourselves?
More or less...
Sign: Tiger
What's this?  A target?
Hey, Sabo!
I'll show you the results of my training!
Here I go!
Huh?
That's great!  Just a week ago, you couldn't make it move straight at all.
See?!
Sheesh...
What kind of training did you put him through?
Not much... Everyday, I had him take an axe and cut down trees, noshi...
I suppose it might have improved his physique.
My crew challenged the Pirate King Roger to a fight...
Seriously?!
...and lost.
We all went our separate ways after that.
You hate him too, right?
Hate?
Since you lost to him...
Oh, you mean Roger?
Well true, it was a painful experience...
but it just meant that I wasn't strong enough.
I'm actually grateful to him, noshi.
You're grateful to him for beating you?!
That's right, noshi.
Damn it all!  We lose!
Just take my head!  However...
In exchange for my head, please spare my crewmates' lives!
Captain!
I'm begging you!
He was such a big-hearted man, noshi!
How could anyone ever hate hi-
Don't lie to me!
There are countless people who bear a grudge against him!
I wonder, did any of them ever meet Roger in battle?
In a pirates' world, defeat means you lose your life...
but I'm still alive, as you can see.
Well, if they truly did fight him...
The only reason they can still blame or hate him at all,
is because they survived.
I'm gonna become much, much stronger, and...
Well then, what if Roger had a child?
Then he'd sure have it rough.
Whether he tried to live within the law,
or live his life as a pirate...
he'd always have the Pirate King's name bound to him.
I can't even imagine how cruel that would be.
But if I were that child, I wouldn't
even consider being a pirate.
The name of his father would ultimately destroy him, noshi...
Destroy him?!
You don't know anything...
yet you think you can say something like that?!
Fight me, old geezer!
Ace!
Didn't I tell you...
To a pirate, defeat means losing your life!
I won't lose!
I win.
Damn it!  Do whatever you want, I don't care!
Alright, then come with me, noshi.
This way!
There's a cove out here?
Hey!  Hurry over here!
Hey!  Hey!  Hurry up!
What are you so excited about, Luffy?
Watch, and be impressed!
That's...
a ship?
Isn't it great?  That's a real pirate ship!
A pirate ship?!
So, this is what you're always working on, Naguri?
I wasn't able to make much progress on my own, though...
Do you think you three can help me build it, noshi?
Help you?
Didn't you say I could do
whatever I want with you, noshi?
H-Hey, wait a second!
You said "You three"...
Does that mean I have to help too?
You might as well, since you're here...
What kind of reasoning is that?!
We're busy trying to defeat the great tiger!
I'll train you to fight the tiger too, noshi!
What?!
Oh, well I guess it's fine, then...
Tell me one thing first.
What are you gonna do with this ship?
Of course, I plan on setting out to sea,
in search of the crew I parted ways with.
You're setting out to sea?
What? You're saying that
an old man can't sail the seas?
No, that's not what I meant...
Age is irrelevant when pursuing your dreams, noshi!
I will go out to sea, no matter what others say!
I've made up my mind, noshi!
Do you have a problem with that?
None at all!
He's quite an impressive old guy...
Ace?
A promise is a promise.  I'll help you with the ship.
Also...
Tomorrow, I will win!
What's that supposed to mean?
And so, the days of Naguri's pirate training began.
By working on the ship they trained their bodies, and by sparring with Naguri they developed their skills...
Ace, Sabo and Luffy spent the days growing stronger together.
And then, the seasons changed...
A late spring finally arrived at the Gray Terminal.
I'll win today!
There's no way I'm gonna lose!
I'm the one who's gonna win!
Ouch...
Hey, Luffy!  You did it again!
Sorry!
I swear, you guys...
You don't care about anything but strength...
but are you sure that's enough?
What's that supposed to mean?
We decided that the strongest would be the captain!
Do you have a problem with that?
That's right!  The one who beats the great tiger becomes captain!
The great tiger, huh...
Well, strength is an important quality for a captain to have, but...
There is something much more important, noshi.
Something more important?
Indeed.  And that is...
I forgot, noshi!
What's that supposed to mean?!  You got us excited for nothing!
Now, now...
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Oh, if it isn't Ace-kun, noshi...
What is it?
What's the thing that a captain needs?
What could be more important than strength?!
Tell me!
Very well.
You see...
I'm not entirely sure myself, noshi.
I was a failure as a captain.
However, my crew...
They kept calling me "Captain" until the very end.
That's the only reason why I am still the captain of the Naguri Pirates.
Being respected by one's crew is what makes one a captain!
Or something like that...
Ridiculous.
Alright!  It's done!
You did it, Naguri!
Awesome!  This is so cool!
I owe it all to you!  Thanks!
I'm really grateful to you all, noshi.
Hey, Naguri... Are you going to set sail now?
Yeah, but first...
I have to see your training through to the end!
Today, we'll start the long-awaited great tiger hunt, noshi!
Seriously?!
I'll definitely win, and then I'll
be done with this lousy training!
I'll be the one who wins!
I'm not gonna lose either!
Here he comes!
Alright, now's the time...
I'll go first!
I knew you were gonna do that!
How'd you like that?!
You let your guard down!
Now, I'll take you on!
Just give up and get caught!
Sabo!  Ace!
Damn it...
Not good!  Luffy!
Run away!
Ace!  Sabo!
We can't hold it for long... He's too strong...
Damn it... We're not done yet...
Being respected by one's crew is what makes one a captain!
But there's no way I'll lose!
Hey, you two!  Lend me a hand!
This is getting interesting, noshi...
We're not fast enough... But Luffy, if we use your ability, we might be able to win!
Sabo!  I'm counting on you!
Right!
Hey, Tiger Lord!  Over here!
Kiss my ass!
Luffy!
Right!
Pull back as far as you can!
Sabo!  Over here!
No... It's hopeless!  I'll be eaten!
Don't give up, Sabo!  Lure him as close as you can!
You ready, Luffy?
Yeah!
We did it!
And...
I guess that makes Ace the captain, huh?
I trained so hard, too!
Just give it up, Luffy.
Sheesh... Don't worry about it.
I won't become the captain.
Why not?
It's not like I defeated the Tiger Lord on my own.
Ace...
Well, whatever.
Someday, you two are gonna be
begging me to be your captain, anyway.
You gonna beg for that?
Never!
You guys!
Well, I guess everything worked out, noshi...
So, then...
Old geezer!
The next time we meet, I'll win!
Don't let anyone else beat you until then!
See ya!
Take care, okay?
I'll be waiting for you at sea, noshi.
And so, the trio's days with Naguri came to an end.
Luffy and the others went back to living on their own.
Hey.  You're sure about this, right?
Yes, there's no mistaking it.
I suppose it's about time.
Contact the old man.  Tell him...
we've found Sabo.
In order to save Ace and Luffy, who have been taken hostage,
Sabo must make a grueling decision.
Next time, on One Piece:
Stolen Freedom!
The Nobles' Trap Closes on the Three Brothers
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!