It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy had landed on the island of women, Amazon Lily.
Ready to depart, he went off to save his brother Ace...
...and snuck aboard a Navy ship with the help of the Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock.
He's now heading for the great prison, Impel Down.
Elsewhere, what has become of the Straw Hat crew
who were sent flying from the Sabaody Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma?
Mero Mero Mellow!
Will we even survive this journey?
What a stiff gang...
Luffy, time to eat.
Luffy?
Hey, when're we gonna get to where Ace is?
I am afraid it will still take some time.
I see...
Oh! Food! Food!
Luffy.
W-Would you like some tea?
Sure.
Sure. I'd love some.
Thump-a-thump!
P-Please wait for a moment...
Um, Luffy? Would you please tell me about your crew?
Uh, I did not mean anything in particular by that...
I was most certainly not trying to say that I would like to know a little more about you...
Yeah? Who should I start with...?
Zoro...Sanji...Usopp...Brook...Franky...
Nami...Robin...
Nami?! Robin?!
You have women in your crew, too?!
Yeah. You're spilling the tea by the way.
Sorry, but we can't be together.
Why?! Why, Luffy?!
'Cause I've got these two.
I will not lose!
I will definitely not let them beat me!
What're you talkin' about?
A human...
She's wearing an outfit I've never seen before...
She must have come from the outside world...
She's alive!
Are you alright?
Who knows...
Where am I?
Tequila Wolf. It's a country in East Blue.
You seem cold. Would you like to come to our house?
If it's no trouble, I'd love to.
Come on! Keep moving!
Soran! You went out on your own again?
You can't do that! The government officials didn't see you, did they?
No.
Who is that?
I can tell from her clothes that she's not from around here.
She had collapsed in the snow.
A drifter?
She might be a fugitive.
In any case, she can't be quite right in the head, coming here...
Looks like I'm bothering you after all.
Excuse me.
I'll take care of her.
Don't just decide that on your own!
What if the officials find out that you're hiding some strange woman here?
I'll take responsibility for it myself!
I swear, this girl is so...
Where are you gonna hide her?
In my room!
In the attic, huh?
I suppose she'd be fine up there, for a while.
Are you people serious?
We should just turn her in to the officials right now!
She's here now - what's done is done.
I'd feel bad if we kicked her out now.
It's none of my business what happens to her!
Everyone...
Don't misunderstand us. It's just until her wounds heal.
Though nothing good would come from her recovery...
They are kind people.
Yes.
Thank you.
Lady, you smell nice.
I'm not wearing any sort of perfume.
Is this what the outside world smells like?
The outside world?
I've never left this place...
Lady, are you a traveler?
Did you come from a warmer place?
Yes. I was traveling onboard a ship.
Was it a big ship?
What island did you come from?
Have you ever seen any unusual flowers or birds?
Oh, and...
Soran! Break time is over!
Hurry up and get back down here!
It's time to work.
At this time of night?
We can't stop working.
You can just rest.
Please tell me about the outside world afterwards.
Sure. Have a nice day, Soran.
Sure.
Seems like I won't be able to get back on time...
Did I wake you up?
Soran, you look so...
I'm fine.
Exactly what kind of work do you do here?
We're building a bridge.
A bridge?
This country is built on the bridge.
This is a huge, long bridge connecting islands.
They've been working on it for hundreds of years.
That's what the government said.
For hundreds of years?
Please tell me, where did you come from?
I...
...no longer have a homeland.
But I have been to many seas and islands.
Soran?
What is this?
Drawings of all the islands in the world.
I've never gone to sea, so they're all imaginary, but still...
When I draw these, somehow, it feels like I'm actually on those islands,
and it makes me forget about my hardships!
Really? They're very good.
This is a Sky-Island...
They exist? Islands floating in the sky?
Yes.
Can you tell me more about them?
Sure.
Let's see...
Where do I start?
Amazing!
So there really are lots of interesting things outside of this country!
We get forced to work every day, and it's really exhausting...
...but now that I think about it, building a bridge might not be such a bad thing.
Maybe, when we eventually reach another island,
we can all leave the bridge and travel around freely.
And then, I can travel around the world, and draw pictures of real islands!
What a wonderful dream.
Hey, can you tell me some more stories?
Of course.
Mind if we listen, too?
Go ahead.
The woman is up in the attic.
Thank you for informing us. Charge!
Wait! You'll keep your promise and release me from here, won't you?
Don't move!
W-What?
We're looking for an intruder!
We won't show any mercy if you stand in our way!
What's going on?
Someone went and told the officials!
They're looking for her!
What do we do?
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
What do you want?
We received information that a
mysterious woman is hiding here.
The people who are against the construction of this bridge have been on the move lately, after all...
Just hand her over to us!
We don't know who you're talking about.
It doesn't matter how much you search!
We're all exhausted, so please leave!
You watch your mouth!
Grandma!
If you're not going to speak, then we'll just have to beat the answers out of you!
I'm certain you know how our interrogations work, don't you?
Captain, we found these.
What's this scribbling?
An island?
I drew those! Give them back!
An island, is it?
Ridiculous! What a pointless delusion.
Give them back!
Tell us where the woman is.
Do that, and we'll give you back your drawings.
I don't know.
I'll ask you again. Where is the woman.
I don't know!
If you cooperate with us, you will be released from here someday.
Then you'll be able to see the outside world.
I don't know!
I'll ask you one last time!
Where is the woman?!
I don't know!
You people are in for life, anyway.
You'll never leave this place for as long as you live!
Arrest them all!
We'll torture 'em all till they give her up!
No mercy on the kid, either!
Come on, move it!
Lady...
H-Hey... You guys...
D-Don't come any closer! H-Hands up!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me! Please forgive me!
S-So you've come to your senses...
It's the woman! I've got the woman cornered!
Hurry! Someone, hurry! Call in reinforcements!
What are you doing?
You heard him, right?!
Isn't that the woman you were looking for?
Get out there and capture her!
You sure caused us a lot of trouble.
Captain...
What are you doing?! Hurry up and get down there!
Yessir!
I'll let you go for now.
But I'll remember your defiant attitude!
Do whatever you want!
Are you alright?
Lady...
This is a country of laborers.
Pull! Pull!
The people working here are all criminals from other countries,
or inhabitants from countries that
refused to join the World Government.
Stand up! Stand up!
I guess you could call them slaves.
When will this bridge be completed?
It'll probably take a while...
We've been working on it for seven hundred years, after all.
Seven hundred years? What for?
You have no need to know.
You're one of our workers now,
so you just have to build the bridge!
These islands, blossoming in the sea like flowers, are called the Boyn Islands.
Let's go Usopp Exploration Party!
The captain is me, of course, the King of Snipers, Usopp!
And here is my crew!
Due to unforeseen circumstances, they can't be here.
Still, where am I?
I wonder if Luffy and the others are alright?
They can hardly do anything at all when I'm not there...
I know they must be crying for me right about now!
That must be it! I've got to hurry and rescue them!
Was it just the wind?
The Usopp Exploration Party must always be on the lookout!
I am Usopp...
Where is the exit?
Also...
HEY! IS ANYONE HERE?!
~ Here?! Here?! ~
Could this be a deserted island?
I've got the "If-I-Don't-Find-Anyone-Then-My-Heart-Will-Stop"-disease...
Crashing
Useless.
Hey! Is there really nobody around?! Don't just hide! Come out!
Someone came out!
How are you doing?
You're doing too well, dammit!
You gonna eat this?
No way!
But still, you saved me. Thanks!
I don't know who you are, but...
My name is Heraclesun!
Wow, that's a really cool name.
You thinkun?
I'm Usopp. Nice to meet you.
Is this edible?
I've never seen a fruit like this before.
It's alrightun, Usoppun.
And...My name is...
HERACLESUN!
I got it. You're cool.
It sure smells good...
I'll just give it a lick...
USOPPUN!
W-What was that?!
Was that thing trying to eat me?!
Of coursun. It's a man-eating plantun.
Man-eating?!
WHAT IS WITH THIS PLACE?!
This is the highwayman's forest, Grinston.
HELP!!!
And...
MY NAME IS...
HERA-
Surprisingly, Zoro landed in the same place as Perona.
Zoro tries to return to his crew, but Perona interferes.
Meanwhile, Brook is hailed as Satan, King of Demons!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew's Whereabouts
The Negative Princess and the King of Demons
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!