It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered,
and Luffy has broken into the world's largest prison, Impel Down,
to free his brother Ace, who is being held captive by the Navy.
Together with the red-nosed pirate, Buggy, and former Baroque Works agents, Mister Three...
and Bon Kurei, he advances through the levels of the prison.
After finally reaching Level Four, Inferno Hell,
Luffy is drenched in Warden Magellan's poison and is captured.
Bon Kurei is determined, in one way or another, to rescue Luffy,
who has been thrown into Level Five, Freezing Hell.
What the f-?!
Uh, I mean... What do you mean, you can't make an antidote?
A miracle?
That's it!  Just the person we need is here in Impel Down!
TL Note: Okama = Drag Queen
The Okama Queen, Iva-san!
We've got to go and find him quickly!
W-We're in big trouble now...
Now that it's come to this, we should get inside the cage ourselves!
Right.  I'll try to distract them.
Open it, quickly!
Damn... Take this!
TL Note: Special Muggy-ball
How's that?!
WHAT?!
I'm done!
You opened it?
The key broke...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?!
We're not gonna make it in time!
That was close!
Now, let's get inside the cage.
That won't be necessary.
I've got a great idea.
Take that, you dumb wolves!
You can't hurt us NOW, can you?!
There's no use biting the bars either!
This is my pride and joy, the hard-as-steel "Candle House"!
Even with those huge fangs, you'll never break it!
Well, let's go, partner!
Indeed!
One, two!  One, two!
This is perfect!
They can't reach us now!
This thing's heavier than I thought it'd be.
I made it extra thick, just in case...
Is that so?  Well, that's fine!
It doesn't matter if we're slow as a turtle.
As long as we can make it to the door, we can get outta here!
Indeed.
And the shelter will also protect us from the cold wind.
Right!
One, two!  One, two!
Wait, wait.  Back up a little.
What's up?
Something's not right here...
Where on earth have the wolves run off to?
Good question, where are they?
They've all disappeared...
What's that sound?
Is that...?
THEY'RE PRETTY DAMN CLEVER!
What's with this guy?
He's covered in blood.
Back there, I...
I don't stand a chance at winning!
I'm running away!  Sorry!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan!
I'm so sorry I ran away!
This guy... You're...
His friend!
Straw-chan, I won't let you die!
Now, let's go!
He left the keys...
Breaking out, huh?  I'd never even considered it...
I have to hurry and find Iva-san!
Iva-san?
How should I know where that damn Okama went?
Who are you, anyway?
Emporio Ivankov...
Yeah, he was here a while back.
Isn't he dead now?
What's with that look?
What's the point of searching for someone who's not here?
Nevermind that, how'd you get out of the cage?
Let me out too, okay?
I'm looking for someone named Iva-san.
Hello, you listening?
Hey, can you hear me?!
It's no use.
The guys in that cell have all frozen to death.
Uh...
I heard you.
You want to know about that damn Okama, Ivankov, right?
Do you know something?
Look over there.
You can see the forest, right?
Yeah...
There's a jailer's room over there that no one uses anymore.
I've seen a weird guy coming out of there a few times.
Really?
If you think I'm lying, go see for yourself.
Thanks!
Don't mention it.
Hey, isn't the wolves' den out in that forest?
Oh, really?
The disappearances that sometimes happen within Impel Down.
It's nothing like an escape.
Prisoners who can't even move suddenly vanish, without leaving a single trace.
The Demon's Tug.
Everyone is afraid of these unnatural disappearances,
and because some think they might've been dragged into the underworld,
it has earned the name Demon's Tug.
A gate to the underworld?
The Demon's Tug?  What the hell is that supposed to mean?!
I won't accept such a stupid reason for Iva-san's disappearance!
I've never met him, but I'm sure that man, who has performed countless miracles, has done so here as well!
Iva-san is the God of the Okama world!
I beg of you! Save Straw-chan's life!
If there's no antidote to this poison,
then you're the only one who can save him!
I can only have faith and keep searching!
Oh, crap!
Straw-chan?!
What are you...
doing...
to Bon-chan...?!
Get away...
FROM BON-CHAN!
S-Straw-chan!
What...
was...
that...?
Time left until Ace's execution...
26 hours.
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Damn...
Where did you go?!
It's so hot in here!
It's like we're in Hell!
Wha-?  Sh-?
She's just my type!
Healthy, young and a flawless beauty!
But wait... What?
What happened to that Okama who beat up all the guards?
Huh?  What are you...
That doesn't matter, does it, big guy?
Come over here for a sec...
Huh?
I'm so sweaty, my shirt's stuck to my skin...
Could you help me take this off?
Come on...
Well now, d'you mind opening the door for me?
Yes, of course!
Smash!
There we go!
Okay then, let me give you a hand with that...
You got a change of clothes with you?
Fooled you!
Unforgivable...
What that Okama did was unforgivable!
I'd be happy to blame the Warden for this, but I can't stand being outwitted!
Besides, I wanna be Warden...
I used too much poison...
My stomach is...!
We've finally stopped all the commotion.
We've put all the prisoners back in their cages, and we've retrieved the stolen keys, but...
there are quite a few missing.
This is really troublesome.
How could you possibly...
not find him?!
Hurry and bring him to me, alive!
The Okama-prisoner is, without a doubt...
on this floor!
And then, as more time passes by, Mister Two Bon Kurei finds himself...
Huh?  Where am I...?
Oh, right!
Straw-chan?!
Where is Straw-chan?!
I can hear voices...
This is the place.
So bright...!
Ah, so you're finally awake, bro!
You've been sleeping for quite a while, huh?  Want a drink?
Cheers for the Newkama!
Cheers!
We saw all of it on the monitors.
That uprising of yours was really something to see!
What is this place?
Let me take you to your seat.
What floor did you come from?
We've got plenty of food here!
You must be starving.
What is this place?  Where's Straw-chan?!
Do you think you've escaped to the outside world?
Don't worry.
We're still in Impel Down.
Like hell we are!
Nobody's wearing a prison jumpsuit.
Everyone's eating delicious food and drinking booze...
Is this some sort of paradise?!
That's right!  I...
I was chased by the wolves, and saved by Straw-chan's mysterious power,
and then I lost consciousness.
So, is this a dream?
No, wait!  I must have frozen to death!
Is this the afterlife?
Oh, you're awake?
You sure slept for a long time.
It must have been at least 10 hours.
10 hours?!
What're you talking about?
Who are you?!
My name is Inazuma.
Don't be so rude.
I was the one who carried the two of you here when you were on the verge of freezing to death.
The two of us, you said...
Does that mean Straw-chan is here too?
Where is he?  Is he safe?!
Are you guys prison staff?
Where... Where is this place??
Now, calm down.
He'll tell you everything you need to know.
"He"...?
The lights are down!
The show's starting!
Let us go up to the front.
What's that?
Did vyou sleep well, Candy-boy?
Or rather, Mister Two Bon-boy?
What?  How do you know my name?
Vi'm impressed that vyou made it here.
This is...
Good going!  You're super sexy!
A place that vyou'll reach by taking...
A path that shouldn't exist through the sewers of Impel Down.
A prisoners' paradise!!
There's all sorts of entertainment down here!
Liquor...
Weapons...
Games...
And above all else, FREEDOM!
YEAH!  THAT'S RIGHT!  WE'RE ALL FREE!
That's right.
The guards were making a fuss today.
Saying "The prisoners have been dragged into the underworld", vyou know?
But that's too bad!  Vwe're all down here!
Great going!
Yay!
This ain't the underworld...
It's more like the Okama-world!
The hidden society known to no one!
Vi welcome you...
to Impel Down Level Five Point Five, the secret hideout of the prisoners...
NEWKAMA LAND!
What's with this army of perverts?
Iva-sama!
Iva-sama...  You can't mean...?!
This person is the legendary...
queen of all Drag Queens?!
Emporio Ivankov?!
Bon Kurei begs the "miracle worker", Iva-san, to cure Luffy's poisoning.
But Iva-san's treatment is a cruel procedure that will leave Luffy's body wounded and torn.
A fierce battle to fight the poisoning commences!
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy's Treatment Begins
Iva-san's Miraculous Power!!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!