Kohza
It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy had been blasted off from the Sabaody Archipelago by the Warlord, Bartholomew Kuma.
He was separated from his crew,
and landed alone in the kingdom forbidden to men,
Amazon Lily.
It looked like that Luffy, who was taken prisoner there,
successfully escaped, however...
It's time for the Snake Princess's bath!
Is this...
a bath house?
A man?!
You...
That thing on your back...
I... think I've...
You saw it?!
Sister!
Sister, what on earth is going on?!
Who is that?
A man?!
What is a man doing in this kingdom?
What exactly happened here?
No, well...
He saw my back.
Then the only solution is to kill him, right?
Why? I only saw her back...
But, it's as if...
I've seen that somewhere before...
The thing you have seen on my back...
is something we don't want revealed even if we die!
That?
Why?
Who are you?
Take everything you have seen here to your grave!
TL Note: Madly in Love
Huh? Noro Noro?
That's a Noro Noro Beam!?
Crap, I'm gonna slow down!?
I am slowing down...
Why don't you turn into stone?
Didn't you feel anything wicked in your heart,
even after you saw me naked in the bath?!
That's ridiculous, sister!
The beauty of your naked body...
is at a level that could never fail to capture anybody, regardless of their age and gender!
It's probably his fear of death...
that's suppressing his wicked desires!
He's pathetic, but he's a lucky man.
I don't know what's going on,
but I'd better get out of here at any rate!
I just want to find someone important, that's all!
He jumped out from this height!
You can't run away!
What?
I couldn't make it bounce.
Wasn't it a bullet?
That man is a intruder!
Capture him, Kuja Pirates!
Y-Yes!
A man?
Why is a man....?
At any rate, we have to capture him, right?
That hurt!
It would be best for all of us if you come obediently.
Ran, there is no man who can defy the Kuja Pirates.
Also, he looks very weak.
It's a man!
A living man in our village?
So, the all-female pirate crew are you people?
Do you know someone important?
What are you planing to do if we tell you?
If she's an important person, she'd have a ship, right?
I can ask her if she'd take me to her ship,
and then I can hurry up and sail out to sea!
That's ridiculous!
Do you really think a man who intrudes into Amazon Lily,
a place forbidden to men, can leave alive?
Foolish man.
I can't be captured right now!
Capture him!
What?
Hurry up and go after him!
The Snake Princess ordered us to capture him!
No matter what, we can't let him get away!
A man!
A man has invaded the town!
A man?
The Kuja Pirates are after him right now!
We should give them a hand, as well!
Alright, let's go!
It looks like the Kuja Pirates are in a crisis nyow,
for letting a man gyet off this easily.
I've never hyeard of anything like that before...
I'm worried about the future of our kyingdom.
Capture the man!
It's the Kuja Pirates!
That man returned to the village, as I thought.
I found him!
He's over there!
I thought she'd be in a tall building, but...
I wonder where I can find an important person?
Has that pirate crew already caught up with me?!
We must catch him...
before the Snake Princess find him!
What? Them again?!
He fell!
There he is!
It's the man!
Crap!
Wait!
Wait, you!
I never would have imagined that one of the rookies worth 300 million...
would be in Amazon Lily.
There he is!
I have to run away!
Wait! Show me your face one more time!
I said wait!
Even the old women of this kingdom are strong?
You can't run away anymore!
Shit!
The Kuja Pirates!
The saga of "We Can't Interfere Anymore", right?
As I thought, that man is...
Damn it, get off!
What's with these snakes being as hard as steel?
We were too late...
I hope we're not asked how he got here.
That man is gonna be killed, right?
What is with this kingdom?
There really isn't a single man here.
Snake Princess!
Marigold-sama!
Sandersonia-sama!
Now then, let me ask you, man.
How, and for what purpose, did you come to this island?
I don't know how I came here either!
I was just flying through the sky,
and before I noticed, I was just here!
Liar!
You can't fool us with a ridiculous story like that.
You must have a purpose, right?
If it's a purpose you want, then I want a ship!
I'd be very happy if you gave me an escort, too, but...
Anyway, I must get out of here as soon as possible.
There is somewhere I have to go!
If you are the most important person here, that's what I request!
I want to go out to sea!
He's giving false statements!
Whatever that man said are obviously lies, as the Snake Princess said!
He is definitely hiding something!
Do you think that you can fool us?
Oh, I've just been talking all along!
Is there anything I can do to repay you?
As long as everyone else survived, like I did,
then that's fine!
As long as we are alive...
we'll fight them time and again!
TL Note: "Omae" is a rude way of saying "you".
Addressing the Snake Princess as "you"...
what a disrespectful way to talk!
He is the worst!
Don't think that you will leave here alive.
You won't be able to escape from death!
Wait a second please, Snake Princess!
H-He isn't the kind of person who would lie!
Margaret!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Snake Princess...
Snake Princess,
what he has said is all true...
I don't think that he has bad intentions for this kingdom at all!
Oh, you!
That's right! Please tell her!
Are you one of the guards of this kingdom?
I am called Margaret!
The punishment of the crime of intruding into this kingdom,
which is forbidden to men, is death.
Why are you defending him?
I feel responsible.
The one who brought that man here...
It was me!
Margaret!
Why?
Snake Princess, the saga of "There's a Reason For That!"
That's right!
We just thought the man we found covered in mushrooms in the forest...
was one of the villagers, that's all!
Sweet Pea!
Aphelandra!
We are just as responsible as her for the sin of bringing him here!
The saga of "Exactly".
You two, stop it!
The one who said we should take him to the village was me!
If you say something like that...
You're too honest, Margaret.
What's with you?
You tried to kill me...
So, you were actually kind people, huh?
The only one guilty of bringing the man here is me!
Margaret!
That's enough.
Raise your head, honest Margaret.
I like honest people.
Tell me, do you want me to forgive you?
Y-Yes!
Stand up.
The Snake Princess is gonna forgive those three criminals?
As expected from the Snake Princess!
Not only is she physically beautiful,
she is also merciful!
Snake Princess!
What is this?
They did something stupid.
Hey, what happened to you?!
What happened?!
They turned into stone! Why?!
Hey...
Hey!
Hey, what did you do to them!?
They saved my life!
Yes, they have been punished for helping you.
Because of me!?
Wait!
Turn them back to normal!
Who do you think you're ordering around?
Hurry up and turn them back to normal!
Bring Bacura to the arena!
Bacura!?
That man is finished off already, right?
I told you to turn them back to normal!
This place is the kingdom of the warriors, Amazon Lily,
where if you are powerful, you are beautiful.
You should die fighting.
We are gonna watch it.
That black panther's name is Bacura.
It is a carnivorous animal that was used as an executioner by the empress of this kingdom for many generations.
After the execution, not even a single bone will remain.
Bacura seems to be extremely hungry, doesn't it?
Yes, it is, sister.
Because it hasn't been fed for a while.
Be grateful, man!
Even if it's a small and thin monkey like you,
Bacura will eat it with pleasure!
Aside from that...
What's gonna happen to these people?!
Are they gonna turn back to normal?!
What a disrespectful way of speaking to the Snake Princess!
Go finish him, Bacura!
Bacura!
Go!
He is strong!
Bacura was defeated by a single hit?!
He didn't use "Willpower"!
So he did that just using brute force?
There is something wrong with all of you...
Even after your comrades...
have been turned to stone by that woman,
why are still laughing childishly?!
The savage is shouting at us!
Unbelievable!
What a fierce animal!
We feel sorry for those three,
but what Snake Princess did wasn't wrong!
They have broken the laws of this kingdom!
The ones at fault are them!
I will be...
forgiven no matter what I do.
If you ask why...
Indeed,
It's because I'm beautiful!
Snake Princess!
You think so, too, right?
You're pissin' me off.
Sister, get a hold of yourself!
This is just ridiculous!
There can't possibly exist a man...
that can't be captured by my charm!
I can't bear that man's existence!
How could you speak to the Snake Princess that way?!
Hurry up and execute that man!
Execute him!
Go, Marigold and Sandersonia!
Take that man's head!
Yes, leave it to us, sister.
Execute him!
Those people use devil-fruit powers, too?
Sandersonia and Marigold, who were ordered to execute Luffy,
turn into their snake forms and start to attack in turns.
Luffy dodges all of the attacks, and counters back.
However, in the end he is cornered!
Next time on One Piece:
Luffy's Hard Battle!
The Power of the Snake Sisters' "Willpower"!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!