It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy was trying to escape from Impel Down in order to catch up to Ace...
but Warden Magellan stood in his way.
To the sea?  If you think you can, then just try and get away!
The moment you touch the water, you'll be in the Sea Kings' nest!
You won't get away!
What?
So you made it in time...
I'm sorry for calling you out to such a dangerous sea!
It's a school of whale-sharks!
Jinbei called them here!
Awesome!
Carry them over here!
He's amazing!
Awesome!
We did it!  We've finally reached the warship!
We managed to escape!
It's like I'm dreaming!  I never thought I'd make it out of Impel Down!
We don't have time to celebrate yet!
We've got to hurry and get out of here!
We did it!
Thanks, whale-sharks!
You saved us!
Be careful on your way back!
Vwe have to cure Inazuma's poisoning.
Bring all the medicine vyou can find in the medical office!
I'm never going back to that Hell!
Me neither!  I'm turning over a new leaf!  I'm gonna go home and be with my family!
WE ARE FREE!
And who do you have to thank for that?
Go on, say it!
CAPTAIN BUGGY!
I never thought they'd make it that far...
Marines, send one of your ships back here.
I'll come with you, and take them down myself.
Understood.
It looks like they haven't noticed that they're trapped yet.
The only thing waiting for you where you're going, is despair.
No matter how hard you try, there's no escape!
Rear Admiral!  We've fixed the cannons that Jinbei disabled.
Very well.
All ships, open fire!
Adjust for range!
They've started shooting!
This is really bad!
How many ships are there, anyway?!
The entire fleet is chasing us!
We're hit!
Everyone ranked Vice Admiral or above has already been called to Marineford...
but a warship is a warship.  They're still tough, no matter who's onboard!
Don't you realize that it's useless?!
The Gates of Justice won't open...
FOR PIRATE SCUM LIKE YOU!
That's right!  I forgot about this!
This is bad!  These gates will never open for us!
Oh no!  We've made it this far, and now we've hit a dead end!
Don't imitate me!
What're we gonna do, you damn shark?!
We'll break through!
That's just impossible!
This is the worst possible situation!
How can you be so calm?!
SAY SOMETHING!
First of all, we've gotta protect the ship!  Don't let them sink it!
Are you just gonna sit back and take their attacks?
This is a warship too, remember?
Aren't you gonna shoot back, you worthless fools?!
That was gonna be my suggestion!
Let's shoot back at them, men!
UNDERSTOOD, CAPTAIN BUGGY!
How's that?!
It's no use!  We can't escape from this place!
Damn it!  At this rate, we'll just end up as the Navy's prey!
Damn these prisoners...
They must have realized that they're trapped, so why are they still heading towards the Gates of Justice?
The Gates can only be opened by operators inside Impel Down.
There's no other way to open them!
Fire!  Send them to the bottom of the sea!
The Gates of Justice are opening!
How can this be?!  What's going on?!
Why are the Gates opening?!
IT'S OPEN!
H-How can this be?
Is it a trap?!
Alright!  I don't know why, but the Gates are opening!
What?!
Warden Magellan!  Hurry aboard!
No, wait!
Impossible!  Why are the Gates opening?!
Are you sure opening the Gates was a good idea...
Warden Magellan?
Yes, this will do.  Have my orders ever been wrong?
No, it's not that I doubt you...
As soon as their ship has passed through, you are to close the Gate immediately.
Do you understand?
Very well, Sir.
Don't let them escape!
Letting them get away is unforgivable!  Fire!
Are these Magellan's orders?  What is he thinking?!
I don't understand what he intends to achieve by doing this.
What is Warden Magellan thinking?!
Uh, well, I don't think this was done by the Warden.
He was just standing on the bridge by the main entrance.
Why-?  What is happening?!
Control Room!  What are you doing?!
Who told you to open the Gates of Justice?!
W-Warden?!
Oh, my.
Is that really true?
Bon-chan...?
You!
That's right!
It's me!
I tricked you again!
It was a fake?!
Warden!  We've received word from the fleet!
The stolen warship is just about to pass through the Gate!
Even if they manage to make it through the Gates of Justice...
they can't possibly escape with that many warships pursuing them!
In that case, close the Gate immediately!
Press the button!
W-What?!
Uh, yes...
Uhm...
Wait!  Don't push it!
Oh!  Yes, Sir!
No, push it!
Don't push it!
Push it!
Just push it already!
Yes, Sir!
TL Note: Memoir of that Desert Kingdom
I win!
W-Why, you little!
I won't let you chase after Straw-chan and the others!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Look!  The Gates are closing!
They're closing!
If we can get through, the Navy will be trapped on the other side!
He was just with us at the exit!
Are you saying that Bon-chan stayed behind in Impel Down on his own?!
Even though we'd made it so far!
Even though we were almost free!
The only reason we managed to meet Iva-chan and the others,
and escape from there, was because Bon-chan was with us!
And you're telling me we should just go on without him?!
There's no time to waste.
Are we just gonna abandon him?!
We've already abandoned countless allies who fell along the way!
Do you intend to return there and fight Magellan again?!
Then there will be even more sacrifices!
We'd waste even more time, too!
If someone hadn't stayed behind, the Gates would never have opened for us!
I'm the one who can pull it off best.
I'll open the Gates of Justice!
And what do you intend to do afterwards?
If I told you that, it wouldn't be as cool, would it?
Don't tell Straw-chan anything before we part ways!
Words are not needed for an Okama's parting.
It's still connected.
The Baby Snail Phone has a very short range.
As soon as the Gates close, we'll lose contact with him.
It's no use!  The Gate's opening mechanism is broken!
It'll take a while for us to repair it, Warden!
How dare you transform into the Warden?!
Good thing I memorized your face back then!
Open your eyes, Hannyabal!
What happened here?!
W-Warden!  Let go of me!
Touch.
How dare you?!
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan?!
Hey!  Can you hear me?  Bon-chan?!
Why are you doing this again...
just like you did last time?!
Bon Kurei-sama...
Running away now would be a disgrace to all Okama!
If we were to abandon our friends, who risked their lives to meet up with their own friends...
would you be able to enjoy your breakfast tomorrow?!
Gasp!
Listen up, my men!
And you too, Straw-chan Team!
Listen real close to what I'm about to tell you!
Could this "Straw Hat Luffy" you're looking for be...
me, by any chance?
Just kidding!
Madame Hina!  The sheep-ship is sailing east!
We got you!
We're experts at disguising ourselves!
And we are Straw-chan's friends!
Come and get us!
Why are you doing this again...
just like you did last time?!
Jinbei!  Didn't you promise not to tell him before we'd lost contact?!
Weren't we gonna escape together?!
You just keep saving me over and over again!
If you're there, then answer me, Bon-chan!
Is that how it is...?
That Okama-guy...
he stayed behind alone for our sake...?
Bon-chan!
Answer us, Brother Bon!
Why won't you answer?!
Bon-chan!
Mister Two!
Mister Two, you're...
I'm so sorry for everything!
Bon-boy!
Fire!
Don't let them get away!
Blow them to pieces!
Bon-chan!
BON-CHAN!
Bon-chan... The Gates are closing.
We're... going.
Thank you!
Brother Bon!  Thank you!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan...
You have to save your brother, no matter what!
I'm sure... you can...
save your brother!
Bon-chan!
The Gates are closing!
Sink them!
Long time no see!
I'm perfectly okay!
Quit joking around!
Straw-chan!  I've come to save you!
In the name of our friendship!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
Words are not needed for an Okama's parting.
BON-CHAN!
How can this be?
They got away!
If he hadn't been here, we'd be at the bottom of the ocean by now!
Even in Hell, there is a single blooming flower of friendship.
It rocks back and forth over the waves,
leaving one single petal behind as a memento.
Someday, it will certainly bloom.
Okama Way!
Bon-chan!
Brother Bon!
Bon-boy!
Mister Two!
Do you have any last words?!
Satisfaction!
Let us meet again on the field of Okama.
On this day, the number of prisoners who escaped from the world's most feared prison, Impel Down...
was a total of 241.
It was the greatest disgrace Impel Down had suffered in its entire history...
but this incident is still not over.
Time remaining until Portgas D. Ace's scheduled execution...
4 hours.
After parting with Bon Kurei, Luffy and the others set sail.
However, as soon as Buggy and the others learn that the ship is headed for Navy HQ...
they start planning a mutiny, attempting to steal the ship for themselves.
Right then, they receive another, even more shocking piece of information from Navy HQ.
Next time, on One Piece:
Destination Navy HQ
The Voyage to Rescue Ace!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!