It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has come to Marineford...
to save his brother Ace, who is about to be executed.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates have been advancing toward the execution platform,
and at last, they've made it past the defensive walls.
As a fierce battle between the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates rages in Oris Plaza,
Luffy runs toward Ace.
Damn it to Hell...
So even you can't fight old age,
Whitebeard?
The one thing we'd feared the most...
The battle is over once you let your guard down, even for a second!
Marco!
You just got distracted, didn't you?
Now, I guess it's time for me to send you off to the next world!
Old Man!
As long as I've done all I can,
then I don't mind dying!
Please let me fight, Iva-chan!
If... I don't fight here...
If... I can't save Ace...
I'll...
end up wanting to die!
Please... Give me the power to fight!
Fine!
Do whatever the hell...
vyou want!
Luffy...
Ace!
They're late!  What are they doing?!
Pardon the delay!
Here are the two replacement executioners!
They're finally here...
Hurry up and get ready!
Yes, Sir!
Straw-Hat-boy, Vi should warn you...
The next time vyou fall, no matter how persistent vyou are,
Vi won't be able to bring vyou back!
The Tension Hormones can only deceive vyour body!
Vyour injuries haven't been healed!
I...
I will not fall again!
Another empty boast...
Those guys!
Wait!
They're trying to execute Ace again!
Of course... There's nothing Vi could say to stop Straw-Hat-boy in this situation...
The only thing Vi can do now is make sure he doesn't fall!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat is here!
Take down Straw Hat!
Leave this to me!
I'll finish him off!
It's not over yet!
We can't let him pass!
If you want to keep moving...
You'll have to fight us all!
We'll show you the Navy spirit!
Out of the way!
Vi will back vyou up!
Thanks, Iva-chan!
Luffy-san...
You...
Coby!
Back then...
I've decided to become the Pirate King.
And if I die fighting for that dream, then I don't mind.
Can I do it too?
If I'm determined to die trying...
Do what?
Do you think I could join the Navy?
The Navy?
That's right!  Capturing evil people is my dream!
It's been my dream ever since I was a child!
If I hadn't met Luffy-san back then, I wouldn't be who I am today.
Alright... In order to be a real marine...
I have to fight, or I won't progress...
This is a battlefield!
I must be prepared...
to kill him!
Someday, I will...
become one...
of the Navy's Admirals!
Uh, no...
I-I-I'm sorry!  I-I got carried away!
How embarrassing... If there's a hole around here, I'd like to crawl into it!
I-I got a little too excited about meeting you again...
Coby.
You're gonna fight me, aren't you?
So of course you gotta advance that far!
W-We're talking about becoming an Admiral here!
The next time we meet, we'll be much stronger!
Much more incredible!
Why?
Just now, it felt like just saying that would make me collapse...
It's an impossible dream...
So why does he believe in me?
He really is strong...
It's no good... I have to become much, much stronger...
Hey!  Coby!
Damn it!
What now?!
Vyou guys are...
the Kuma impostors!
Monkey D. Luffy...
Damn it... These guys are trouble!
That's dangerous!
Boa Hancock... One of the Seven Warlords.
Cease fire.  She is an ally.
Oh, right... You guys are allies!
Thank you, Hancock!
That's the Empress, isn't it?
How do vyou know her?
Luffy...
You said my name again...
Thank you, Hancock.
Just hearing you say my name is more than I can take!
Hancock.
Yes.
Move.  Boa Hancock.
When did I give you permission to say my name?!
Magma-brat...
Old... Man...
I... I'm coming... now...
Your guard is down.
You've already been hit three times, so have yourself a nice, long rest.
Old Man!
Oh, I suppose it isn't that easy.
You can regenerate, can't you, Marco the Phoenix?
Hey, it's your turn.
Sea Stone?!
Commander Marco!
Oh, that looks painful.
Commander Jozu has been defeated too!
The Commanders are falling, one after another!
The Whitebeard Pirates have fallen.
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Old Man!
You Fishman monster!
Let me go!
Don't just stand there!
Attack together, and take Whitebeard's head!
Old Man!
Stay back!
Do these guys really think...
they can kill me so easily?!
I don't need any help.
I...
I am Whitebeard!
H-He's a monster!
Don't hesitate!  He's been fatally wounded!
Everyone, follow me!
Yes, Sir!
Fatally wounded, am I?
Don't make me laugh!
Do you really think I'll die so easily?
Do you... really...
Don't you understand...
what it would mean if I died?
I know...
if that happened...
my eyes wouldn't see the bright future ahead of my sons.
I can't let myself die, can I?!
Right, Ace?
Old Man...
You just refuse to die!
What was that?
W-What's with these guys?!
Covering Whitebeard's back like that...
Do they intend to die together with Whitebeard?!
You people will never understand!
We will protect the Old Man's pride!
You're getting too worked up, you fools!
Old Man...
Captain Squardo, we must go to the Old Man's side too!
C-Captain?  Where are you going?
Don't follow me.
I must settle this in my own way.
If you want to see the future, I'll show it to you right now...
Whitebeard!
Do it!
Ace!
That won't work!
Do you really think that would stop...
Behold, Whitebeard!
Stop it!
Here I come!
What did vyou just do?!
The Conquering King's Haki?!
Hey, hey!  Seriously?!
How surprising...
That kid...
The Navy continues their attack, even more ferocious than before.
In response, Iva-san uses his final trump card.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Execution Platform Within Reach!
The Path to Ace is Opened!!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!