It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy lost his brother Ace in the great war against the Navy,
then he escaped to the Island of Women.
There he was overwhelmed by an unbearable sadness.
But now, we go back in time ten years, to East Blue.
This story takes place when the brothers Luffy and Ace were still children.
Luffy was left in the care of the Dadan Family, a group of bandits on Mt. Corvo.
There he met Ace and Sabo, two troublemakers.
They shared a toast of brotherhood together.
Our bonds will keep us connected as brothers!
With this, starting today, we're...
brothers!
Yeah!
I'm gonna become a pirate first, so that'll be impossible!
That's not fair!  I'm going to become a pirate before either of you!
You two are still going on about that?
I'm telling you, you're gonna become marines!  Why is that so hard to understand?!
"We're moving out..."
This is great!
Yeah, it's the best!
Our very own secret base!
Found them!
The season changes...
Winter.
Sabo!  He went that way!
Don't let him escape!
I'm on it!  We won't let you escape!
Alright!  We've got him surrounded!
Luffy!  He's almost there!
Here he comes... Here I go!
You're not getting away!
I did it... I got him!
You did great, Luffy!
That's our second catch of the day!
Now we'll get to eat a lot of danpa soup!
Yeah!
I did it!  Alright!
It's my first ever catch!  Yay!
Hey, look up there!
Luffy!  Look behind you!
Behind me?
A tiger!
He must have followed the scent of our prey.
Luffy!  Get out of there!
He's after the danpa!
I killed this one myself!
There's no way I'd...
l-let you have it!
He's too strong for you!  Run away, quick!
No way!  Get lost, you idiot!
If you don't leave, I'll beat you up!
That moron!
Luffy!
Why, you...
Damn you...
Gomu Gomu no...
Wait!  Wait!  Wait!
Let's run away while he's distracted by the prey!
Right!
I'll be back for you later!
It's a shame that you lost your first ever catch like that...
Give it a rest.  What else can we do when we're up against the Tiger Lord?
But I caught that one!  Why'd he have to take what wasn't his?!
S-Stupid!  Don't shake the bridge!
Hey, don't!
Cut it out!
Sabo!  Hurry and pull us back up!
Alright...
Sorry.
We're finally back... We've had really bad luck today.  Let's just go to bed.
Pun on Tsuita: Arriving and Tsuite nee: Bad Luck
We're back, but we're unlucky, huh?
Ah, I sure am hungry!
And whose fault is that?!
Ow!
But still, the first prey he'd ever caught got stolen...
it's no wonder he got mad.
Trying to fight the Tiger Lord is just far too reckless.
You're one to talk!
Shut up.
Brothers sure are a nice thing to have.
If the two of you were part of my crew...
Captain, there's no need for you to get involved here.
Let us handle this!
No.  As the captain, I'll go too!
What're you laughing about?
Laughing won't fill your stomach, you know...
I've decided!
Ace, Sabo!  You should join my crew after all!
Right?  You'll join, won't you?
What's gotten into you, all of a sudden?
I thought we'd agreed to decide that when we're older?
Still, I think, it'd be much more fun if the three of us were together!
You'll need my help.  Right?
I'd understand if you said that you needed our help, but...
Yeah...
You're wrong!
I'll be saving you!
If you two decided to join my crew, I'd let you join any time.
No, it'll be my crew!
Then this conversation is over.
You won't join me, no matter what?
I won't.
What about you, Sabo?
I don't want to be anyone's underling.  Give it up.
What the hell?  It would be fun, too...
Oh, I know!
How about, the one who defeats that huge tiger gets to be captain?
Huge tiger?  Are you serious?
The chances of you becoming the captain are practically zero, you know?
That's not true!
None of us can beat that thing now, right?
Interesting!
Alright!  That settles it!
It's a deal!
Is everyone ready?
Yeah.
We worked hard fishing these up... What a waste.
We've got no choice.  This is bait to draw him out.
Here he comes!
Greedy jerk!  We won't let you take them today!
He's here!
Huh?  Is that the Tiger Lord?
What the hell?  That's just some bear.
How boring.  Go away!
No.  This guy is as strong as the Tiger Lord.
If we can't beat him, we won't stand a chance against the Tiger Lord!
I get it.  So he'll make for some excellent practice, right?
I'll go first!
That's cheap!
Not fair!
It's no use!  He won't calm down!
We're done for!
W-Who's that?
That old guy's in trouble!
That's Naguri from the Gray Terminal!
Run away!  He'll send you flying!
What're you doing, old man?!
Noshi!
This isn't your den, is it?
Go back to the forest, noshi!
Amazing!
It's just like back then!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Naguri, you were a pirate?!  Not only that, but a captain?!
I was indeed.
I knew it!  Only a pirate captain could pull something like that off!
Something like that?
Chasing that huge bear off just by glaring at him... You're just like Shanks!
You're incredible, old guy!
You don't say...
I can't believe that Naguri used to be a pirate.
I mean...
He goes around collecting junk...
and spending whole days hammering at it...
trying to create some nonsensical device.
The Gray Terminal residents and Bluejam's crew are always taunting him.  That's all I've ever seen...
He was quite a pitiful oldtimer...
You're such a kid, Sabo!
That's what a true pirate is like!
You're just a kid, too!  What do you know about pirates?!
I do know!  Shanks never picks meaningless battles!
Shanks again, huh?
Hey.  This one's done.
Hot!
He got the bigger part!
It's 'cause you were spacing out.
Hmph!
Naguri, you have some too.  It's your reward for saving us.
Oh, thanks a lot...
So, what is a pirate captain doing in a place like this?
You really want to know, noshi?
If you don't want to tell us, then you don't have to.
No, it's fine, noshi.
Have you heard of Gold Roger?
Roger?
I know of him!  The Pirate King, right?
My crew challenged the Pirate King Roger to a fight...
Seriously?!
...and lost.
We all went our separate ways after that.
I kept drifting around as if I was rolling down a slope...
and ended up like this.
It's a simple story, but that's what happened, noshi.
But you fought against the Pirate King, right?  That's amazing!
Oh, no, no... We were no match for him.
He completely beat us into the ground.
Really?  So the Pirate King was so strong, even you couldn't beat him...
Yeah... It wasn't just Roger.  His crewmates were all unbelievably strong, noshi.
Their constant, flawless teamwork was the most impressive thing about them...
We might have been enemies, but it was an honor to meet them.
I see... I've got a long way to go before I can become a true pirate.
You're interested in pirates, noshi?
I'm gonna be one!
A pirate?
Yeah!  A pirate!
Oh, right!  Pirate-oldtimer, can you train me?
I want to become strong!
I've gotta become Ace and Sabo's captain!
Their captain?
It's fine, right?  Be my Pirate-master!
Alright, noshi.
You're okay with it?
Yay!  Then I'll be counting on you from tomorrow on!
Huh?  Where'd Ace go?
Well, about that...
The Pirate King is Ace's dad?!
Yeah.  But this is a secret, okay?
Never say a word about this in front of Ace.
If you do, he'll kill you.
Why?
I don't know the details... But anyway, he hates Roger.
But he's his dad, right?
So what if he's his dad?
I feel bad for you two but, even with parents, I'm still alone!
Right... Your parents were...
Not all kids get along with their parents.
Still, he was the Pirate King and all...
I understand that you want to ask him about Roger...
but you mustn't say a word!  Alright?
Right, I understand!
Oh, and you too, Naguri.
Alright, I understand, noshi.
Still, I never would've guessed he was Roger's son...
There he is... Listen, you've gotta act ignorant, normal and casual.
Right.
Don't say a single word about–
I won't!  Don't worry!
Oh, Ace!  So you went home before us?
Oh, Ace!  So Roger was your dad?
Did he really say that?!
Damn it, Luffy!  I kept telling you not to bring that up!
Luffy.
Yeah?
Who'd you hear that from?
From Sabo!
Hey, Ace!  What kind of guy was Roger?
Stop it!
Don't ask him that, you idiot!
Let go of me, Sabo!  I want to know!
Don't blow our cover so casually!
Ow!
Ouch!
I don't want to hear that name ever again!
What was that for?  Don't be so stingy, just tell me!
You didn't have to punch us out of the blue without any explanation!
Shut up!
You could at least tell us something!
You meanie!
That's right!  Brothers don't keep secrets from each other, right?!
Shut up!  What do you mean, brothers?!
Roger!  Roger!  Roger!
Ace's dad, the Pirate King!
Shut up!  Don't provoke him!
This is all because you couldn't keep your mouth shut!
What?!  What did you say?!
What are you doing?!
As of today, you two are no longer my brothers!
That's just what I was gonna say!
Alright, I'm counting on you.
Sure.  I'll leave no stone unturned.
It's just as you heard.
We'll start looking immediately.
Sure.  But if you do find him, don't grab him just yet.
Don't you get it?  We have to make sure that man winds up indebted to us.
If we keep him waiting, he'll be all the more grateful when we bring the kid back.
I get it.
Just watch quietly until the time is right.
"An important guest is arriving this spring"?
Dogra, Magra!  Where is this Goa-place?
Well, Mt. Corvo, the Gray Terminal and Windmill Village all happen to be part of Goa Kingdom...
You're right...
Now, now, boss...
You hardly ever read the newspapers... Are pigs gonna fly today, too?
Ow!
A guest will be coming to this kingdom?
They seem to be making quite a fuss over this...
What's the commotion about?  Are they really so important...
These Celestial Dragons or whatever they're called?
After being trained by Naguri...
Luffy and the others finally challenge the great tiger to battle!
Next time, on One Piece:
Showdown With the Great Tiger!
Who Will Be the Captain?!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!