We are in the Great Pirate Era.
Looking for the great treasure One Piece...
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger,
a struggle between countless pirates began.
The young boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit...
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many who went to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have experienced countless adventures,
and not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
The crew, aiming for the New World...
will advance on the Grand Line once again today!
In order to reach Fishman Island on the bottom of the sea...
the Straw Hat crew went to the Sabaody Archipelago to find a ship-coater.
There, they met the former vice-captain of the Roger Pirates...
the skilled coater, Rayleigh.
While Rayleigh coated the ship, the crew went off to hide...
but they suddenly ran into an artificial human who looked just like Bartholomew Kuma.
Let's rest for a bit...
I never thought we'd be forced to go all-out in a battle so soon...
However, the captain of the Navy Science Patrol...
Sentoumaru, then appeared,
bringing with him another Pacifista.
Let's run away from here!
We can't stay together... We'll split up and escape!
They're splitting up and running!
Chase them, PX-1!
Zoro!
W-What?! Who are you?!
You... Get away!
Get away from Zoro, you freak!
Z-Zoro-san!
Zoro-san was hit by a beam!
Kizaru?!
Furthermore, the navy admiral Kizaru appeared.
This was a hopeless crisis for the crew.
Here he comes!
He got me.
Hey, damn Warlord!
Come at me!
This time, I'll crush you for sure!
Kid!
There's no way he'd be able to get up after being hit by that attack!
We trashed one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Bartholomew Kuma wasn't any stronger than this?
What the hell?
This guy... He's an artificial human?!
Why'd you interfere?!
You overestimated your own ability, Eustass.
What?!
Did you really think this guy was a Warlord?
What's that supposed to mean?
We've got some more company. We'll talk afterwards.
Charge!
A white bear?!
Hey, you!
Hey, Trafalgar! About what we were talking about earlier...
What'd you mean he wasn't a Warlord?
What now?!
Zoro!
Hey, he can fire beams too!
This is bad! We've gotta do something!
If he's hit at such a close range, he'll die!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
Usopp!
You... Stop it!
Why, you..!
Damn it! Why?!
I can't hit him!
I can't stab him either! What do we do?!
Stop there!
Damn!
You...
Move your leg!
Please move!
That's no use.
I ate the Pika-Pika fruit, I'm a light man.
I'm a Logia.
Light man?!
You're kidding, right?! He's gonna die!
Zoro! Run!
Zoro!
My body... won't...
It's no use! That guy is at his limit already!
Alright! Great, Robin!
He just... got over there in an instant!
How?!
I won't let you get away.
It's useless.
You'll die now.
So, now you decide to appear...
..."Dark King", Rayleigh?
I won't let you take out these youngsters.
Their era is only beginning!
Pops!
He saved him!
Thank God...
He just said "Dark King"...
So that's him...
I'd heard some rumors that you were on this island...
So, that was true?
Seeing how you helped out these brats,
that must mean you're still a pirate, at your age...
Rayleigh-san?
If you people would withdraw my bounty...
I'd be able to retire in peace, too.
The pirates' sins won't disappear, right?
Especially not those of the Roger Pirates.
But if we were to try and catch you...
it would require a bit more dedication than we have right now.
What a relief, Zoro! This old man really is amazing!
The body I could not pierce no matter how many times I stabbed him...
He just stopped him! How?!
You can't let them leave, can you, Kizaru-kun?
Give me a break, here!
If we can't catch these kids...
then we at Navy HQ wouldn't be able to face the Celestial Dragons in Mariejoa.
Would you please get out of my way?
Usopp! Brook!
Take Zoro and run!
Right!
Let's go, Brook!
Everyone, only think of how to escape!
Right now...
we can't...
beat these guys!
Oh, great. That's really annoying.
Franky!
I'm gonna use all my cola energy...
This'll be my last attack!
That damned idiot must have felt that!
Run!
Pops, thank you!
No problem! I'll pray for your safety!
It's bright!
Light! He's doing something!
I won't let you pass!
It's been a long time since I used my sword.
I'm in trouble here...
I was expecting things to be easy when I came to this island...
Worries are also a part of life, Kizaru-kun.
The light ahead of us disappeared.
Seems like the old man saved us again.
T-T-That was scary!
Seems like he's the real Dark King.
This is the first time I've seen anyone stop the old guy.
But we're just one step away from catching Roronoa with his bounty of over 100 million...
PX-1! Roronoa is half-dead!
Go take him out!
He's...
Franky!
Take care of Nami-san! Please go on without me!
Be careful! We'll be alright!
Sanji-kun?!
He's going after Usopp and the others!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Put me down...
I'll let you escape...
Don't be ridiculous! You're even more useless than I am right now!
We're running together! That's what Luffy wanted us to do!
Could it be...?!
He's here!
Usopp-san!
Usopp-san, go on ahead!
Stop it, Brook!
You know how strong he is, don't you?!
Hurry!
All for one, one for all!
There are times when a man has no choice but to act!
A bone-crushing defeat...
Brook!
Don't come here!
Stop right there, you damn bastard!
Sanji!
My leg...!
Run, Sanji!
He's aiming for you!
Idiot! Hurry up and go!
As you can see, my subordinates are more than strong enough.
Zoro, I'm sorry! I dropped you!
Are you alright?
Wait, you damn bastard!
Damn it!
Stop, already!
Zoro...
They're in trouble over there!
I won't even need my broadaxe, will I?
I thought I told you, you don't have time to worry about your friends!
Luffy!
How can that guy's attacks hurt a rubber man like Luffy?!
Damn!
Chopper! Don't stop!
Sanji!
Damn it! They'll all be killed!
Don't do it, Chopper!
Stop it, you people!
Chopper!
That's the thing from back then!
What's this?
I had heard of this...
That's an interesting power, but...
It seems like you've lost your common sense, huh?
Luffy, watch out!
That Chopper... He did that again?!
I don't know why, but he seems to be distracted by him...
Now's our chance!
Sanji, Brook! Get up!
Let's hurry up and get away from here while we have the chance!
He's gonna fire another beam!
Hey, hurry and wake up, Brook!
Sanji!
Wait, PX-1.
ANOTHER ONE SHOWED UP!
What's going on?!
No way!
How many of these guys are there, anyway?!
This guy...
...He's the real one!
What happened here?!
N...
Nothing... Happened...!!
So, you survived, Roronoa?
Thanks to your mercy...
H... Hey, Zoro...
This is no time to be talking...
Hurry!
If you were to go on a vacation, where would you like to go?
Hey, Zoro!
If you don't hurry up and run...
Huh?
Zoro!
Zoro... san?
Zoro? Zoro!
ZORO!!!
What?
What just happened?
Zoro...
Zoro... vanished!
Everyone was killed...
What's wrong with me?!
I couldn't save a single one of my friends!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Vanished Crewmates
The Last Day of the Straw Hat Crew