It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy was separated from his crew...
then he broke into Navy HQ to free his brother, Ace.
But, right before Luffy's eyes, he died.
Having escaped from Navy HQ,
the heart-broken Luffy was brought to
the island of women where he could hide...
I'm so weak!  I can't protect anything!
Can you not see anything?!
Don't just count everything you've lost!
What's gone, is gone!
But ask yourself this, what remains?!
My crew...
I still have my crew!
I want to see them soon...
I want to see them again!
This is Kuraigana Island on the Grand Line.
The ruins of the Shikkearu Kingdom
W-What are those?
B-Baboons?!
What do you think they're saying?
No idea.
But from what I see, I doubt
these guys can be reasoned with.
There's more of them?!
These guys...
They're as skilled with weapons as humans!
What?!
My wound from before... Now, of all times?!
H-Hey!  Are you still alive?
Shut up.  You're distracting me, just stay quiet.
So not cute!  I was worried about you, and this is how you respond?!
Come to think of it, why should I care at all?!
This is not good...
This aura...
He's...
It's you!
Hawk-Eye... Mihawk!
Moving now to Torino Kingdom in South Blue...
Here a war between humans and birds rages on.
Please don't cook me!
We catch raccoon dog again!
Raccoon dog!  Raccoon dog!
I keep telling you, I'm not a raccoon dog!
Daddy.  He says he not raccoon dog.
What you talking about?  Raccoon dogs can't talk.
Yes I can talk!  Listen to your son,
he's telling you the truth!
I'm a reindeer!  And I can speak
the human language!  Also, I'm a doctor!
What you talking about?  Raccoon dogs can't talk.
But Daddy, he is talking...
Oh my!
If you understand, just let me down already.
Show me wound.
Incredible!
This is burn medicine.
We can make many different medicines from plants.  It make life easier.
You have more of them?  Show me!
None right now.
The plants we need to make medicine
grow on giant tree.
But evil birds make nests there one year ago,
it impossible to go up there now.
We out of most types of medicine, so more and more now sick.
Is my friend.
This is...
It hurt...
They'll be in danger if I leave them like this...
Can't wait no more.
Must go end things with birds!
Kill or be killed!
War!  Be prepared!
Daddy!
Son!  Protect Mommy!
J-Just wait a second!  Don't be so hasty!
I'm a doctor myself.  I can't neglect these patients.
I'll go talk to the birds, and convince them
to stop being mean to you!
Really, mister raccoon dog?
Don't worry.  I can communicate with animals.
Oh, and...
Stop making me repeat myself!  I'm not a raccoon dog!
I was able to become friends with that chick... I'm sure the grown birds will understand!
Mister raccoon dog... I no doubt you,
but I doubt mean birds will listen.
If they don't...
We must kill them!
Hiya!
I came to speak with you!
The humans living in the forest are in trouble!
Huh?  "We won't let the humans have our treasure"?
What are you talking about?
Mister raccoon dog!
J-Just wait a minute!
Ow... Damn it...
What treasure are you talking about?
Why do you hate the humans so much?!
You guys...
Talk is over, mister raccoon dog!
We have no choice!
Mister raccoon dog!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Geez!  Neither the humans nor the birds will listen to what I say on this island!
Dammit!
You're the chick from the other day, right?
I see you've recovered!
All of you!  Please listen!
Really?
It looks... like they came to understanding.
Please listen to me.  The birds
have been acting like this for a reason.
These guys love shiny things, so they gather them from all over the world...
But some humans wanted to steal their treasure and drove them off their island!
That's why they thought that the humans on
this island would try to steal from them as well.
These are medical plants!
Is that enough?
If there's any medicine left, please give me some too...
Mister raccoon dog!
There's no pain!
Here.  Shiny stuff.
You've become great friends, huh?
Oh, the News Coo!
Thanks for the newspaper!
Let me see...
This is a small Sky Island, Weatheria.
You're not working very hard, are you?  Are you even motivated, girl?
Of course I'm not!  I wanted to learn weather science, not field work!
Get it?!
This is weather science as well!
This is the weather-field,
where we grow Weather Balls.
Science also requires diligent manual labor, you know.
Really, nobody told me about this before...
Ah, there's the News Coo.
Bringing today's newspaper?
Thanks.
The weather forecast for tomorrow...
Wait, let me see that!
In the Grand Line, the Boyn Islands.
Right now, Usopp...
put on a lot of weight due to excessive eating.
How do you like my body?
Don't eat anymore'n, Usopp'n!
These aren't muscles'n...
It's visceral fat'n!
This is a bad lifestyle you're living'n!
I'm becoming stronger!
He's ignoring me'n...
Here's the newspaper'n.
Roasted bird!
You can't eat that'n!
Momoiro Island, Kamabakka Drag Queendom
Oh no, stop it!
What a beautiful sunset.
Oh, bird-san.
Thanks, sweetheart.
What's todays love horoscope...
What's wrong?
What the hell is this?!
East Blue, Tequila Wolf.
Nico Robin, put this on.
Thank you.  But how do you know my name?
Every soldier in the Revolutionary Army knows you.
I ask that you trust us and come with us.
I'm sorry.
I made an important promise
to my friends that I must keep.
I see.  That's too bad.
Your friends... are you talking about the Straw Hat crew?
We have some information about them, too.
If you'd like, should I tell you?
Yes.  I'm interested to hear it.
On a winter island; The Future Kingdom of Bulgemore.
Cola up!
Ah, I missed this feeling.
It's fizzing all through my body.
I didn't think there'd be
Mecha Animals inside the lab, though...
That Mecha Polar-bear...
hit me, and...
I crashed into the refrigerator,
which was fully loaded with cola!
I was able to turn the situation around...
and it all turned out alright!
Hmm?  What's that?
Namakura Island, Harahetternia
What a terrifying, malicious voice!
Satan-sama must be performing some sort of forbidden ritual,
in order to curse the Longhand Tribe with death!
I lost my focus.
No!
It's getting more and more ominous.
Leaning at 45 degrees!
Oh, no!  This is 60 degrees!
I am in quite a slump...
Could this be punishment for seeing too many panties?
What is this?
Relax, Roronoa Zoro.
Your injuries have pushed you far beyond your limits.
But even if they hadn't,
do you really think that someone who can't
defeat the baboons is in any position to challenge me?
Why... are you here?!
That castle was my home, once upon a time.
But what are you doing here?
One of your fellow Warlords...
Kuma sent me flying here.
I see.  So that's why Straw Hat
arrived at Marineford with that other group.
You met Luffy?!  How is he?  Is he alright?!
He is most likely alive.
However, his heart has been dealt a grave injury.
What happened?
He...
has lost his brother.
No way!
That can't be!
Oh my!
You're kidding... right?
I don't believe this!
What... did you say?
Fire-Fist Ace...
died right before Straw Hat's eyes.
Luffy...
Luffy!
Just as Luffy is headed for the Sabaody Archipelago,
Rayleigh arrives.
Next time, on One Piece:
Reunion with the Dark King Rayleigh
Decision Time for Luffy
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!