Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
Luffy and the others have landed on a burning island, Punk Hazard,
in order to answer a distress call, when...
Poooh- I must say, this is pleasantly cool!
This is incredible!
There's a human sticking out of the dragon's back!
Meanwhile, Nami and the others...
Tie them all up!
Yes, Sir!
Pirates are ideal for our purposes.
Even if they go missing, nobody will care.
Let's take them straight to the Master.
The Crew is Astonished!
The Shocking Samurai Who is Only a Head!
Punk Hazard Island
The Burning Lands
So... What should we do about him?
Let's pull him out!
I say, who are you?!  Unhand me, now -pooh!
Hey!  I'm gonna get you out of there!
Hold still!
Heave, ho!
Boy, he sure got himself wedged into the dragon's back.
How could that even happen?
His upper half is inside the dragon, yet he speaks normally.
Wouldn't it be hard to breathe?
Just who is he, anyway?
Th-Th-There's nothing there!
What's not there?
I tore him in half!  Sorry!
Idiot, you think apologizing will fix this?!
You've killed him!
Pooh- Am I free now?
The legs are speaking!  What's going on?!
Zombie!  Monster!
Hang on.
What could this mean?
There's no sign of his body being torn off.
What's up with that?
So... does that mean he was just a pair of legs all along?
What a weirdo!
He's pretty tall.
Who goes there?  What are you doing?
I sense your presence,
but I have neither eyes nor ears.
You sure are unique!
Poooh- Though I know not who you are,
you will let me pass!
What?
I will not die here!
He's running away!
You shall not get away with this!  Foolish Warlord!
Hey, wait!  Join my-
Cut it out, Luffy!
I'm gonna go catch him!
In the meantime, you cook up a dragon barbecue!
Wait, legs!
Luffy is as impulsive as ever.
Why does he like that monster so much?
I'm worried that he mentioned a Warlord.
Could that mean...
that one of the Seven Warlords is on this island too?
This is bad!  This is too dangerous!
I don't want to face a Warlord!
It's still not too late!
Can't we turn back?
Hey!  Wait up, legs!
What's he doing?
Hey!
You'll crash!
What is he?!
Hot hot hot hot!
What are you doing -poooh?!
What are you, exactly?
You most certainly attacked me,
but why?!
I feel no killing intent from you whatsoever!
You're good!
Poooh- I know not who you are,
so what business have you with me -pooh?!
If you intend to hinder me,
then I shall show you no mercy!
Hinder you?  What're you talking about?!
Anyway, join my crew!
Poooh- What are you doing -pooh?!
Gotcha!
Argh!  Unhand me -pooh!
Now, join...
my crew!
Sorry!
That scared me!
Hey, legs, are you okay?
Oooh!  I'm...
And... that's how it happened?
Yeah, that's right!
This dragon meat is delicious!
What are these things called, Usopp?
Huh?
I guess...
a centaur, right?
I'm a centaur!
This is awesome!
First he was stuck to the dragon, and now to Luffy?
What's up with this guy?!
You give up?
Damn!
I have been attached to something again -pooh!
Grrr... I could just... Let me go -pooh!
That isn't very polite, Luffy.
Really?
What?
See?  Of course he won't just become part of you!
Nobody would be that obedient!
His upper half must be in trouble somewhere!
Give those legs back to their owner!
Don't you have any imagination, Usopp?
This is just the way he is.  See?
I see, so he's supposed to be a Legman?
Yeah right!  Like hell I can just accept that!
What's your name?
And about this dragon meat...
You're gonna eat most of it anyway,
so you carry it!
Hey, you guys!  Come over here!
Oh, Zoro!  Did you find them?
The samurai and the guy who got killed?
Look.
Huh?  What is it?
A-A snow covered mountain?!
No... a whole mountain of ice?!
The other half of the island, across the lake,
has snow covered mountains!
Yet this side is scorching hot
and covered with active volcanoes!
What's up with this island?!
This solves one mystery.
Mystery?
Oh, right!
The voice on the Snail Phone said it was cold!
Please, help me!
What's wrong?!
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
My companions keep getting cut down.
The samurai's gonna kill us all!
So the killer samurai and his victims are over there.
This island is so interesting!
It's snowing on that mountain, right?!
And it's so hot here... I wanna eat a snow cone!
Idiot, you're actually going there?!
It'll be way too cold!
Besides, it's too far away!
Let's head back to the ship now.
How troubling.  It looks rather cold.
If there are beasts there, we can take their fur coats.
We'll manage somehow.
No we won't!  Why are you guys set on going?!
Snow cones!
H-Hey, wait, Luffy!
A-A-And you guys too?!
I'm definitely not going!
As long as I'm here, at least I won't die...
but if I go to the other side, I'll definitely freeze to death!
I definitely won't...
Monster!
Ow... What are you-
I saw it!  I saw it!  I saw it!
A bird!  No, a person!  Huh?!
It was a person yet a bird!
A bird?  A person?  Which was it?!
Huh?  What're you talking about?
Huh?!  Was it a bird or a person?!  Zoro?
There's nobody there.
Huh?  Whaaaat?
Sheesh... Hey, let's go!
No, it's true!
It really was there just a second ago!
I swear it's true!
Reporting in, Master.
We have captured the intruders.
They are most likely pirates.
Oh, perfect.
You see, I was running low on test subjects.
Oh, my...
They're all quite unique and fascinating.
You've found me
some fine subjects for my experiments.
Indeed.  We thought
this iron man in particular might interest you.
Oh, now this is unusual!
Seems quite worth examining.  I look forward to it.
Is this all of them?
There was one other person
who we believe was part of their crew.
He must have been killed
during a quarrel with the others.
There were just bones left.
I suppose that isn't unusual for pirates.
I see.  Very well.
In any case,
we need to prevent this group from escaping.
Lock them up.
Check their cargo.
Search for food and other useful items.
Yes, Sir!
Hmm?  What have I been...
Where are Nami-san and the others?
Who are those gentlemen?
It was so unbearably hot earlier...
yet it's gotten so cold while I slept.
Who's there?!
Are you one of the pirates?!
It's so cold, I feel it right down to my bones!
Ah, I'm nothing but bones, so I suppose that's a given.
The corpse is speaking!
Um, whoever you are,
do you know what happened to Nami-san and the rest?
F-Fire!  Shoot him!
What?!  P-Please wait a second, gentlemen!
You can't just...
Sanji, what're you so worked up about?
Oh, you're awake?
Take a look around, and you'll understand.
This is terrible, Franky!  We've been locked up!
Hey!  What is this place?!
Where are we?!
I was on deck eating that giant shellfish dessert,
and then... I can't remember!
This is just a guess,
but it seems likely that someone used sleeping gas...
and captured us while we were unconscious!
What?!
The ship was gassed, there's no doubt about that.
I'm so sorry.  If only I'd noticed it sooner...
This is not good.
Are we gonna be sold off?
Are they human traffickers?
But if they got everyone who was on the ship,
where is Brook?
I don't know.  We are the only ones here.
They're human traffickers,
so they wouldn't bother with a skeleton, right?
You can't really be called a human either, you know.
Neither can you!
Whatever!
You there.
Did someone just... say something?
No, it wasn't any of us.
You there, do you enjoy a challenge?
In particular, a puzzle!
Did this thing just speak?
What is this?
This thing?  How insolent!
What's this?
Huh?  An insect?
Is it some new kind of Snail Phone?
There are eight of them!  I didn't notice!
I am no pathetic insect!
You do not seem like bad folk...
These are all bits of my face.
Forgive me,
but could you put them back together for me?
Face?  Now that you mention it...
This is a mouth, and this is an eye.
Like this?
How's that?!
It's true!  It became a face!
No, there are quite a few parts left over!
Isn't it like this?
Well?
Completely wrong!
No no no... This should work.
We're making progress!
Wrong!  Wrong!
I wanna try!
You...
Don't play around with other people's faces!
It's done!
It's become a proper face!
I feel some slight discomfort in my jaw and forehead...
but, very well.
I thank you!
A detached head is talking!
Now you notice?!
How can you be alive?!  Are you an evil spirit?!
I do not understand either.
I was not reduced to a head by choice.
That fellow used some queer technique.
I thought I would die upon being cut to pieces,
yet I found myself in this state.
To be cut up by the enemy and yet remain alive...
is a disgrace to a warrior!
It looks like we won't be able to reach the other side...
unless we cross that lake.
The question is, how do we cross it?
First of all,
are we going to survive long enough to reach the lake?
It'th sho hot...
Snow cones!
How can Luffy be so cheerful?
Snow cones!  Snow cones!  Snow cones!
Who's there?!
I've found you, intruders!
You...
Those...
legs are...
so awesome!
You'll have to excuse me!
I was searching for intruders.
You may be a stranger,
but that doesn't make you an intruder!
Oh, really?  You took me by surprise!
Anyway, your legs sure are cool!
Well, yeah!
Your hind legs are a bit weird though.
Really?
Hey!  Where are we -poooh?!
H-Hey, stay still!
What?!  Your hind legs can talk?!
Yeah!
Really?
Amazing!  Even among my companions, nobody has legs like that!
This is the first time I've seen this!
Really?
Hey, Luffy's befriending another weirdo.
A leopard-centaur?
One.  Two.
Three.
And four.
Hello?  Did you find them?
Yeah, I did.  I'm about to take them out.
Four intruders.
I see.
How exciting.
Be careful, now.
Roger that.
A new crisis looms over Luffy and the others while they wander the burning lands.
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others learn about the bodiless samurai and escape from their cell.
While being pursued, they stumble into a room...
where they learn
a terrifying secret hidden on the island!
Next time, on One Piece:
Shock!
The Island's Secret is Finally Revealed
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Shock!
The Island's Secret is Finally Revealed