It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered...
Luffy, trying to save his brother Ace from execution,
has teamed up with Ivankov, Jinbei, Buggy, Crocodile and the others, and is now headed for Navy HQ.
Meanwhile, the other members of the Straw Hat Crew...
So their "battle-outfit"...
was this thing?!
Cute!
SHUT THE HELL UP!
This is strange...  Why do I keep missing?
This means that your heart is astray.
There's no way!
Really?
Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan...
Are you doing well?
I can't wait to see you again.
When I do, I'm sure we'll become great friends.
There it is!  Over there!
Oh, no!
There's nowhere to run!
Did you come here to save us?
So he was that bird's baby...
I hate this place!
So, how do the Sea Stone handcuffs feel?
Yes, there are people like you...
People that have no idea what a lady wants for a present, I mean...
Answer me!  Where are the Straw Hats?!
If you're trying to seduce me, you should try to set the mood.
Why, you...!
Nico Robin...  She's gonna be hard to deal with...
They say that she sunk six warships when she was only eight years old...
but I don't think she'd have been caught so easily if that was true.
If she even just tries to escape, though, this whole country will be turned upside down.
I have to make sure that people don't find out who she is.
Excuse me.
What?
Well, it's about the delays in the construction schedule...
Just extend the slaves' working hours.
Feeding them once a day is enough.
But, Sir, there are rumors that rebels against the construction of the bridge are on the move.
We can't be too rough.
There aren't many of those rebels.  They can't do anything.
The one we should really be afraid of is Nico Ro-
Well, in any case, we'll just have to work the slaves harder.
Hey, don't stop working!  Pull harder!
Hurry it up!  I'm hungry!
Old man!  Are you alright?
What're you slackin' off for?  That guy's almost dead, just ignore him!
What're you looking at me like that for?
What's with you guys?
H-Hey...
You lot!  Get back to your work!
If you don't wanna work, then we're happy to send you to the Special Imprisonment Tower.
The Special Imprisonment Tower...
Lady...
It's the seawater you love so much.  Have a good taste!
It's lukewarm.
If we hand you over to the Navy's convoy, we'll be hailed as heroes!
Even if you're dead when we do...
Such an unrefined laugh.
Why, you...!
Sheesh, potato skin soup again?
We won't last long with food like this.
You're cooperative.  Want some chocolate with your soup?
Thank you, master.
You traitor.
It's so I can survive.  I'm not giving it to you!
Old lady!
I'm not giving it to you!
Just leave her alone.
That lady you saved was sent to the Special Imprisonment Tower...
because that woman sold her out!
She allowed herself to be caught, in order to protect us...
That lady is strong!
I'm sure she'll forgive her.
What're you here for?  You're not getting any!
I wanted to get out of here.  Please don't think badly of me.
Sure.
You eat it.
Thank you, old lady.
You're so nice.
Sorry...
I had no choice...
There's nothing we can do...
We can only keep on suffering here, until we die.
I still haven't thanked her...
I want to give the chocolate to her.
Come on!  What're you doing?!  Get back to work!
Here's your food.
Once you've finished eating, we'll question you again.
I look forward to it.
Seems they beat you pretty badly, young lady.
Who are you?
I'm just an old man.
I was brought in here today,
but because they have no use for old people, they just locked me away in here.
What a shame.
I...
I can't waste any more time.
I have to get out of here...
even if I have to cut off my own arms.
Young lady, you mustn't be so hasty.
Listen close.  I'm sure you can hear it.
What is it?
What?!
The rebels are causing trouble in the residential area!
Warden's orders.  Everyone, move in and restrain them!
Yes, Sir!
Lady!
Lady...
Where are you?
Lady!
Soran!
Lady!  I wanted to thank you...
What are you doing?!
The rebels?
Yes.  As per your orders, all troops have been sent to subdue them.
It's our top priority.
I never gave that order!
You didn't dispatch the guards at the Special Imprisonment Tower too, did you?
Lady!
Soran!  But how...?
I'm an agent for the Revolutionary Army.
Are you alright?  The diversion went well.
Good job.
If you lead us, we can win this battle.
You can leave it to me.
Oh, that's right.
While you're at it, release the young lady over there, too.
You're lucky, woman.
I'm in your debt.
Fools!  Who cares about some puny rebels?!
Don't let Nico Robin get away!
Not this one either...
Young lady.  Things are going to get a little chaotic now.
Please find a safe place to hide yourself.
I'd rather you don't slow us down.
What?
Oh, damn!
It's Nico Robin!
Shoot her!
Did he just say Nico Robin?!
I have a debt to the people here.
I have to pay them back.
The woman from the Imprisonment Tower is headed this way!
P-Please, save us!  Warden!
Robin...  Robin is coming here!
It's over.  It's all over!
Nico Robin!
What a nice name!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Luffy-kun.  You'd better try to get some rest.
Sure, thanks.
But I'm fine.
The wind is slowing down...
We're still advancing on the sea current...
but it could take longer to get there now.
Luffy-kun!
No.  It'd be better if I didn't disturb him.
A battle beyond imagination is waiting for us once we reach Navy HQ...
Ace...
It's a man-eating sunflower!
My name is Heracles'n!
Heracles'n!
Help me!
Hera-
Whatever!  Just save me already!  I'm tired of you showing off!
What?!  He's depressed?!
He went to sleep?!
Please help me, Heracles!
You're the champion of the forest, right?!
Champion...  of the forest?
The strong, cool champion of the forest!
I am the champion of the forest!
HERACLES'N!
Wow!  That's cool!
USOPP'N!  I'M COMING'N!
Heracles!
Watch out!
Heracles!  Heracles!  Heracles!
What are you....
...DOING?!
I'm saved...
But why do they always come after me?
In order to survive on this island, you need both attentiveness and strength'n.
Right now, you are the weakest creature on this island, Usopp'n!
Weaker than a baby ant or an earthworm'n!
You idiot!  I'm stronger than a baby ant or an earthworm at least...
Huge!
Want to eat'n?
You're gonna eat them'n?!
You have to increase your stamina, or you'll keep getting beat'n!
I know that, but I can't find anything that looks edible here!
I'm famished...
Guess there's no choice'n...
Hey, are you sure we'll find something to eat if we pass through here?
Yes'n.  But it might be TOO tasty, so we have to be careful'n.
AWESOME!
What's with this place?!
Smells good...
Yeah, I can definitely eat this!
Ramen waterfalls...
Spaghetti grass...
Ham fruits...
and chocolate rocks for dessert.
Everything you see here is edible'n!
You sure it's edible?!
It's edible'n.
If you eat with gusto and condition your body,
the man-eating plants won't dare to attack you'n!
Really?  That's great!
But this is delicious...  I'm gonna just keep eating as much as I can...
You can't just eat'n!
There's no point unless you train!
I get it!
If I just keep eating and eating...
I'll be able to become a cool champion of the forest like you, right?
Usopp'n becoming a champion of the forest?
WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS OF THE FOREST...
HERACLES'N!
AND...
USOPP'N!
Usopp'n?
Huh?  Usopp'n?
Where did you go'n?
This is delicious!
I'll keep eating 'till I burst!
Not good!
Yum!  This is just so good!
It's so good, I can't stop eating!
Usopp'n!  Where are you'n?
If you eat too much of the food here, you'll be in big trouble'n!
But I just keep eating!  I can't stop it!
I finally found you'n.
What do you think, Heracles'n?
Now I'm a champion of the forest, too!
Usopp'n!
That body of yours is a disaster!
You have to hurry and exercise to burn off some calories, or it'll be too late'n!
What's this?  An earthquake?
It has begun.
A huge mouth?!
I'm falling!  Crap!  I'm falling!  Crap!  I'm falling!!
Usopp'n!
Heracles'n!
You're heavy!
Wha?!
Hey!
Help!
Farewell, Usopp'n.
You're saying goodbye?!
Oh, ramen.
Usopp'n!
I can't eat any more.
Usopp'n...
On this island, fat creatures get eaten right away'n.
I'm gonna get eaten?!
We are on the inescapable Boyn Islands!
They're inescapable?!
AND I AM THE CHAMPION OF THE FOREST!
HERA-
Zoro wanders the island with Perona, trying to get back to his crew.
As usual, Zoro gets lost, and a mysterious shadow sneaks up on him.
And in the meantime, Brook attempts to fulfill a pledge for panties.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew's Whereabouts
A Giant Tombstone and a Debt for Panties
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!