Translations, Vegard Aune
Timing, G_I_A
Typesetting, DeSi
Editing, mithrandiryod
Encoding, SockPain
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
QCing, Asuka
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
While they were heading for their next destination, Fishman Island...
Luffy and the others went to help Caimie's friend, Hacchin.
Before they knew it...
A fierce battle broke out between Luffy's group and the Flying Fish Riders.
In the meantime...
The true identity of Duval, the man who held a grudge against Sanji, was revealed.
QUIT SCREWING WITH ME!
Explosion!
The Sunny's Super Secret Weapon Gaon Hou
That face...
Can something like this really happen?
Amazing...
I never thought there would be someone in this world who looked exactly like that drawing on Sanji's wanted-poster...
Black Leg Sanji...
Dis is all yer fault!
Hey, Sanji, where are you going?!
Do ya realise...
How frightenin' it was, suddenly bein' targeted by bounty hunters?!
Why?
Why'd I suddenly have to be chased by the Navy HQ?!
Why'd all those big name bounty hunters suddenly start huntin' me?!
Why?!
Sanji?
S'all because ya decided to become a pirate, and became famous...
dat I had to go into hidin'...
Fearing the bounty hunters ev'ry single day!
What'd I do?!
Give me my life back!
BLACK LEG SANJI!
LIKE I CARE!
Head!!!
Whaddaya mean, "Like I care"?!
If ya ain't gonna take responsibility for dis, then who will?!
Shaddup!
I'm more pissed about that wanted-poster than anyone!
I understand how that guy feels...
But...
Sanji was really depressed because of that poster, too...
Who's that...?
How long are you gonna keep sulking?
Shaddup!
Why is mine the only one that's drawn?!
-How does this look like me?!
That looks exactly like you.
I can't understand what you're saying.
I'll be laughed at...
...by all the ladies in the world.
So, things like this really can happen, huh?
What a surprise...
This world is really big.
Was Sanji born under some kind of miracle-star or something?
He might meet quite an interesting end someday...
I can't help but feel sorry for that Duval guy...
Those two look exactly like each other!
Like two peas in a pod.
Brook!
I'm so gonna kick the crap out of you afterwards!
Well then, Sanji...
We'll just be going on ahead.
Are you saying this is my fault?!
If you don't want to look like that wanted picture...
Then how about trying to change your hairstyle or your beard?!
There are plenty of things you could just change, right?!
So, I could have done that?
Are you all morons?!
I ain't no moron!
You know, Black Leg, we...
We...
Were running a small, unknown mafia in some distant corner of this sea...
What're you doing to our leader, damn you?!
Are you her father?
I-I-I apologize...
Please forgive her!
Dear!
Daddy!
How are you planning on making up for this?
Huh?!
Daddy!
Dear!
We spent every single day by threatening the villagers for money...
That was the kind of happy life we had.
But that tranquil way of life suddenly recieved a huge shock.
What'd he do?!
This is an incredible price!
Seems like the Navy considers him really dangerous, huh?
He's coming out!
It's dangerous to be seen with him!
We'll be arrested, too!
Run away!
What?
Why'd everyone run away?
At that time...
I was convinced that the entire village had learned to fear me.
But then, what happened?
I never thought you'd run all the way out here...
We're going to restrain you now!
What're the Navy doing here?
Just give yourself up peacefully...
Black Leg Sanji!
No way!
I'm a wanted man?!
Worth 77 million beli...
Sanji?!
Get him!
I ain't him!
I ain't Sanji, I'll tell ya!
I'm gonna be killed!
Black Leg...
Do you understand?
I, who had never caused any kind of uproar...
Suddenly found myself with a bounty of 77 million...
and was chased around by those powerful marines...
I got this nasty scar on my back,
and was forced to wear this iron mask to hide my face from the world!
It's yer fault dat my life was ruined!
I'm prepared to chase ya to da ends of Hell!
If dat's a problem for ya...
Then how about you just kill me right now?!
I'm bein' killed!
Those stupid accusations of yours...
Why'd you even have to put Nami-san and Robin-chan in danger?!
S'dat ship and dat crew dat made ya a famous pirate!
Of course I'd want revenge on'em!
Ya guys should all die!!!
Poison harpoons?!
Get in formation!
Huh?
Pervert?
This is the end for you...
Black Leg!
Get him!
Cut it out already, you guys!
Ya came at'em, huh, Black Leg?
Oh, crap!
Sanji-kun!
They're trying to pull him down into the ocean!
Sanji!
Hurry up and get out of there!
Damn, this net is made of steel!
Now, suffer and drown!
Sanji!
Dammit...
I'll save you right now!
Don't go there yourself, idiot!
I'll go get him!
Wait!
You humans are too slow, you can't catch him!
Leave this to me!
Fool!
You fishmen don't stand a chance at catching up!
The Flying Fish are the fastest animals in the sea!
And the Riders riding them have air canisters...
So they can stay under water for as long as they like!
That guy doesn't stand a chance!
The next time that guy, Black Leg surfaces...
He'll already have drowned and died!
WHAT'S THAT!?
Feel the Head's anger, Black Leg!
Can't breathe...
It's OK!
Caimie!
Hey, cowboy!
It seems that you forgot someone here!
Huh?
The Flying Fish are most certainly faster than fishmen.
They're in the top-class among sea-creatures.
They really are something!
However...
The creatures at the very top of that top-class are the mermen!
In this great sea...
There are no creatures that can outrun a mermaid under water!
It's alright...
I'll save you right now, Sanji-chin!
Is she really that incredible?
Actually...
If she hadn't been spacing out all the time, nobody would ever catch her!
I see...
Caimie!
Take care of Sanji!
What's that?!
A huge anchor?
It's way too huge!
Aim for the Straw Hat crew's ship.
Hit it head-on and sink it!
Some of'em are Devil Fruit users!
If we get'em into the water, they're ours!
This is bad!
Just one hit from that, and we'll sink!
Dodge it!
Use the Burst or the Paddle!
Can we make it?
No, it's too late!
Hurry and come with me, Usopp!
Huh?
Y-Yeah!
You get on the bow!
Huh?
Uh, right!
We're gonna use our secret weapon!
Secret weapon?
The Sunny's in trouble!
That thing is dangerous!
Drop it!
No way...!
At this rate, it will hit us head-on.
SINK!
It's falling right at us!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com!
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net!
Drop it!
The Sunny's in trouble!
That thing is dangerous!
Believe in this ship!
The mane started spinning!
SINK!
It's falling right at us!
Emergency Evasion...
Secret Weapon!
They dodged it!
No way!
I've never heard of any ship that can go backwards!
Usopp!
Get inside the prow!
The prow?
Woah!
You can enter it!
Franky made something like this, too?
Don't think dodging it was all we could do!
This ship has got way more power than that!
Awesome!
Cola Energy now charging!
What is it now?!
Charging complete!
Hey!
What should I do now?
Get as many as you can inside the circle!
Circle?
Like this?
They're in!
Lock on with the button on the handle, then pull the lever!
This and...
This!
What's that?
Note: Gaon is lion's roar. Hou is cannon.
Fire!
Amazing!
You're too impressed!
Did you see that?!
The Sunny's full power?
That move took out almost all the Flying Fish...
That's just how good Usopp is!
Even if it was his first try, it was magnificent!
What an amazing destructive power!
Sunny!
Lion-chan is incredible!
It seemed as if my eyes were going to pop out!
Though I have no eyes to pop out...
It uses three barrels of cola to prevent the ship from being blown away...
And at the same time, it releases two barrels worth of Coup de Burst from the cannon.
It uses a ton of cola, so don't you overuse it!
She's tied us up with the net!
Damn!
That speedy mermaid!
We're almost there, Sanji-chin...
Hang in there!
Caimie!
Thank god!
Is Sanji all right?
Everyone, it's terrible!
Sanji-chin is losing a lot of blood!
Huh?
Did he get done in?!
Just when I thought I'd saved him, a lot of blood suddenly started flowing out of his nose!
Nosebleed?
It's fine...
If he dies like that, then let him die.
That's true...
At least he seems happy.
Hang in there, Sanji-chin!
Is this...
Heaven?
Damn...
He survived, huh?!
Well, it looks like your subordinates are useless now, doesn't it?
Why, you...!
Then, I guess you should learn how terrifying Motobaro is!
Up until today, I've lost count of how many fools have been impaled by his giant horns!
They say his horns have even managed to destroy village dams...
Put him in a cage, and he'll break straight out!
The only reason I've been able to escape from the Navy all this time...
Is because of this guy's horns!
They call them the "Heart-smashing horns"!
Ok!
I'll stop you!
Go, Motobaro!
Watch out, Luffy!
The horns were completely useless!
There's no point in us fighting!
Hey, what's wrong, Motobaro?
The cow's acting strangely, isn't he?
What?
He lost consciousness?
What just happened?
Luffy!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything!
Motobaro!
Damn, how can this be?!
It doesn't seem like he attacked it...
It seems like Luffy won the cow over by talking to it...
What?
You mean, he psyched it out?
But that huge thing just fainted!
Is that even possible?
Why, you...
Damn Straw Hat kid...!
Hey, wait a minute, Luffy!
Huh?
Sanji!
Glad you're alright!
I'll end this stupid incident...
filled with pointless accusations myself!
Finish it?
Black Leg?
As long as you keep on living as a pirate...
I'll never find peace!
I'm the one who's sick of the accusations!
Shut up!
I don't want to see that stupid poster-face any more than you do.
It shouldn't even exist in real life!
Well, then...
You should just die!
Please, stop it...
Taste the classiness of my finishing attack, and end your misery.
You shitty bastard.
Attention, please!
You guys have no idea how to get to Fishman Island, so I'll tell you!
First off, you have to get to a certain island to get your ship coated.
That island is...
I see it!
That's the island!
Awesome!
Soap-bubbles!
Caimie...
I wasn't done talking...
Next time, on One Piece,
Landing to Get to Fishman Island.
The Sabaody Archipelago.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Landing to Get to Fishman Island
The Sabaody Archipelago