It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Ten years ago, in East Blue...
Three brothers lived together and dreamed of becoming pirates.
Seven years after Sabo's passing, Ace set sail...
See you later, Luffy!  I'll be going on ahead!
And three years after that, Luffy set sail from his hometown, Windmill Village.
Sabo was first.  Ace was second.
I'm the third to go, but I won't lose!
Wait for me, Ace!  I'll catch up to you soon!
And we now return to the present.
Right now, Luffy is...
Pirate King?  Yeah, right!
I'm...
weak!
Full speed toward the Grand Line!
Our era begins now!
That island will be our first victim!
Give me a cannonball.
Genkotsu Ryuuseigun: Fist Meteor Shower
There!  There!  There!  And there!
Haven't you had enough?
It's Garp-san!
Garp-san has returned in a battleship!
Is he on official business?
Garp-san!  I read the article about the war!
I heard it was an overwhelming victory for the Navy?
Yeah, and I'm glad to see you're all safe.
How is Luffy doing?
What will happen to the world now that Whitebeard is dead?
Hey, Garp-san!
These past few days, we've seen
a lot of pirate ships on the open sea.
They could attack us anytime,
it's keeping us awake at night!
Don't worry.  I just sank
three of them on the way here.
Really?  What a relief!
They were just a bunch of amateur pirates
who hadn't even learned how to spell "Battle".
But still, Whitebeard was a deterrent.
Now that the world has lost him, the seas are going to be uneasy for a while.
Don't let your guard down just because you live in a remote part of East Blue.
Men.
Yes, Sir!
"Security - Navy HQ Vice-Admiral Garp", huh?
That's so reassuring!
There's nothing to be afraid of now!
Garp-san, we have another problem...
Bandits came down out of the mountains, and took over Makino's bar!
Bandits?
Stop!  Don't!
Hey, Garp!
Oh, that's her!
You've got some nerve showing your face here again!
Garp-san!
Boss!
Vice-Admiral Garp!
Don't interfere!  I know this woman.
You...
You were right there on the battlefield...
They were right there in front of you...
So, what the hell were you doing?!
What the hell were you doing?!
Why?!  Why?!  Why?!
Why?!  Why, dammit?!
Why did you just let Ace die like that?!
Is duty more important than your family?!
Huh, Garp?!  What kind of hero of the Navy are you?!
Just die, you damn old man!
Now, now, boss!  Please stop!
Boss...
Garp, say something!  Why didn't you help him?!
Why didn't you prevent it?!
Stand up.  Get on your feet!
You inhuman filth!
Stop it, Dadan-san!
Makino...
They were within an arm's reach,
yet he was unable to help them...
Garp-san is suffering the most because of this!
Y-You're wrong...
You're wrong...
You're wrong!
The one who's in the most pain... is Luffy!
Alright, let's get started on today's lesson...
How to greet people properly!
Pleased to be working with ya.
That was great, Ace!
Wrong.
In times like this, you should say
"I'm pleased to be working with you."
What, he got it wrong?
The way he said it sounded cool, though.
Someday, Ace-kun wants to meet
the red-haired captain you're indebted to.
We started these lessons because he wants to greet him properly.
You mean Shanks?
Yeah! By the time I meet Red-Hair I'll be a pirate myself.
As a fellow pirate, and as your brother,
it's an obvious duty to show him respect.
Now, try to imagine that he's right here in front of you.
I'm Ace!  Who the hell are you?
Bzzzz.  That's no good.  "Who the hell" is too rude.
It's "Who're you?!", right?
Who might you be?
Bzzzz.
It's "Who are you, you bastard?!", right?
Who are you supposed to be?
Bzzzz.
Who is this?
It's "Who is that?", right?
Bzzzz!
All wrong.  Are you even trying?
This is all because you keep talking nonsense!
Quit distracting me!
Hey, Ace!  Yesterday, I found the nest of a giant snake, filled with huge eggs!
Let's go get them now!
Huh?  Huge eggs?
No, I can't!
I'm studying how to greet people!
I'll be in trouble if that huge snake catches me by myself!
But I'll be fine if you're with me.  So come on!
Shut up!
Do you have any idea how highly he thought of his brother?!
Makino!
Garp...
How's Luffy?  The newspapers say they don't know where he is...
Mayor...
He escaped in a submarine.
The Navy pursued him with everything they had...
and they searched the area thoroughly.
But they couldn't find the ship.
For now, at least he's alive!
Thank goodness!
Still, how does Vice-Admiral Garp from Navy HQ
and this bandit know each other?
Who knows?
Luffy is such a fool!
But whatever kind of pirate he becomes, it doesn't matter.  I'm on his side.
When I think about how he must be feeling...
It's like my heart is getting torn in half.
Luffy!
Don't give in to the pain!
Now, we turn far away...
to the second half of the Grand Line, The New World.
Red Hair...
How can I thank you for this?
Don't be ridiculous.
He might have been my enemy, but Whitebeard was a pirate worthy of respect.
Even Sengoku thought so.
Whitebeard.  Ace.
Please leave their burial to us.
Very well.
I will take the blame.
Well, it's time for us to go.
Sure... Thanks.
Luffy... This must be difficult for you.
I was surprised when I heard about Ace's last actions.
Take back what you just said!
Don't make fun of the man who saved my life!
The name of this era is "Whitebeard"!
He behaved just like Captain Roger.
There were times when I wanted the captain to run away...
I even wanted him to cry.
Listen to me, Luffy.
Knowing both victory and defeat, running away and shedding tears...
That is how men grow up.
It's okay for you to cry.
Overcome this!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Damn it all!  I'm so weak!  I can't protect anything!
Damn it!  Damn it!  Damn it!
Damn it!  Damn it!
Luffy-kun.
Go away!  Just leave me alone!
I cannot do that!  I cannot let you hurt yourself any more than you already have!
It's my own body!  I can do whatever I want with it!
If so, then Ace-san's body was his own too.
He was free to die, regardless of what we wanted!
Be quiet!
The next time you say something, I'll beat the crap out of you!
If that will make you feel better then go ahead and try!
I'm quite weakened myself, but I will not lose to you.  Not as you are now!
Jinbe...
While I was out chasing Teach...
I met my little brother for the first time in three years, in the Alabasta Kingdom.
As soon as I saw him, I felt relieved.
Why do you think that is?
Ow!  That hurts!
I said that hurts, you little brat!
Can you not see anything?!
The confidence that you'll overcome all obstacles... Your strength, that you've never doubted before...
A horde of enemies ruthlessly shattered your beliefs, and rendered you unable to do a thing...
And then there's your brother, who was your guiding light...
You have lost so many things.
The great obstacle known as the world
is blocking your vision!
You can't defeat me with your ability.
You aren't as reckless as I expected.
Go, Pacifista!
Did you really think that I would let you get away?
As you are now, you cannot see anything!
You're being consumed by dark clouds of regret and self-blame!
It might be hard for you, but Luffy!
You have to defeat those feelings!
Don't just count everything you've lost!
What's gone, is gone!
But ask yourself this, what remains?!
Luffy, don't play around up here!
You're disrupting my training!
Luffy, hurry and get everyone into position!
A storm is coming!
Luffy, watch me!  I'm about to catch a huge fish!
Luffy, I'm almost done.  Just wait patiently!
Luffy, no matter how badly you get hurt, it'll be fine.
Because I'm gonna fix you up!
Oh, Luffy.
If you're interested in archeology, do you want me to teach you?
Hey, Luffy!  The Cola Engine is running perfectly today.
You can leave the Sunny to me!
Luffy-san, good morning!  It is morning!
Well then, I shall play a morning tune!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
My crew...
I still have my crew!
Zoro!  Nami!  Usopp!
Sanji!  Chopper!  Robin!
Franky!  Brook!
My friends are still here!
I see.
We agreed on a meeting place...
Everyone, let's meet up by the Sunny in three days!
Right!
I have to go... I'm pretty late, though...
I'm sure they're all waiting for me!
What I saw there...
Jinbe...
Since I have a clumsy little brother,
I'm worried about you as a big brother.
I'm sure he's caused you guys a lot of trouble, too.
Take care of him for me.
I saw that he's no longer the same old Luffy
who'd always chase after me.
He's...
got a reliable crew of his own.
No matter what happens, he'll be alright.
I was relieved.
I want to see them soon...
I want to see them again!
The news of the great war reaches Luffy's crew,
scattered all over the world!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Shock for the Straw Hat Crew!
Receiving the Bad News
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!