Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Straw Hat Pirates have entered the New World, the mightiest of seas, ruled by the Four Emperors.
They captured Caesar, and set off with their ally,
Trafalgar Law of the Seven Warlords.
Now, they have finally arrived at
their next destination, Dress Rosa.
Adventure!
The Land of Love and Passion, Dress Rosa
We're here!  Dress Rosa!
Not so loud, Luffy!  We're in enemy territory.
Oh, come on...
I feel particularly super this week!
I can easily blow up a factory or two.
Let's just find it and get it done!
Again, don't be so loud!
Anyway, we just have to go to town, right?
That's right.
Now remember, don't do anything careless.
If we don't destroy the factory then the entire plan falls apart.
Oh, I know!
Hey, I just had a great idea!
Momo!
Alright!  Let's go, Momo!
Carry me into town!  Fly!
You are heavy!  Move!
I cannot fly, and furthermore
I will not accompany you onto the island!
Father commanded me to stay here.
Can't fly?  What're you talking about?
You were flying earlier.
What do you know?!
I said I cannot fly, and I meant it!
But he flew.  I swear, he did!
But he doesn't have wings.
See, I told you.  I have no memory of such things.
A-And even supposing that I would be able to fly...
What is your name?
I-I refuse to go through such horrors ever again!
I... I refuse to fly!
Huh?  Are you afraid of heights or something?
H-How dare you!
Ow!
Watch your tongue!  A warrior fears nothing!
Ow, that hurts!  Bastard!
Cut it out, bastard!
What do you think you are doing?!
Ow ow ow ow!
Geez, what is he doing?
Luffy-san.  You are fighting an eight year old.
So what if you're a warrior?!
I'll be the Pirate King someday, dumbass!
In that case...
I shall be the shogun of the Wano Kingdom!
The hell you are, you stupid eel!
Conceited monkey!
And what's that supposed to mean?!
Cease this, Momonosuke!  We owe that man our lives!
I apologize, Luffy-dono.  Please forgive us.
He may be a child, but he is a warrior of the
Wano Kingdom.  Thus, he has a great deal of pride.
However, I cannot believe that you would
get so worked up against a mere eight year old.
I hate gutless people, dumbass!
You!
I told you to cease this!
Damn it!
Onamiiii!
Samurai use O- as an honorific for women
There there, Momo-chan.
That insolent monkey was...
There, there...
Why!
You!
Wretch!
Get off her!
What's with you?
Like father, like son!  He must have gotten it from you!
The true motives of the samurai have been laid bare!
Indeed!  Samurai should be a synonym for pervert!
T-This is most unfortunate!
Hey, Kin'emon.  Let's get going to town already.
What kind of kinky costume... err, disguise,
should we wear?
Oh, I had nearly forgotten!
The men wear collared shirts.
The women wear nothing.
All the citizens of Dress Rosa
clothe themselves in this manner.
So to help you blend in amongst the populace, I will disguise you accordingly.
Dress Rosa is the best!
Indeed!
Liar!
O-Onami?
Hey.
I'll leave this with you.
Is this a Vivre Card?
That's right.  It will guide you to Zou, the island I mentioned earlier.
I plan to go to Zou myself after handing over Caesar
and destroying the Smile factory.
My crew is there already.
If something happens to us, then go there.
Huh?  W-Wait!
I-If something happens?  I-It won't though, right?
Who knows.
What's that?
A map that one of my crewmates made.
How crude.
This is where we are now,
the Western shore of Dress Rosa.
Doflamingo resides in the palace at the center of Dress Rosa.
The Smile factory should be somewhere on the island.
We don't have much time.  The team we're sending to destroy the factory has to act quickly.
What's that smell?
I'll be with the team that's handing over Caesar.
We will travel across Dress Rosa
and cross the long bridge on the northern side.
That will take us to Green Bit.
Why do we have to pass through Dress Rosa?
Wouldn't it be easier to just sail to Green Bit?
From what I hear, ships can't get there.
My, how exciting.
P-Please keep me safe, okay?
The Caesar Release Team
My "I mustn't enter Dress Rosa"-disease is acting up.
I hope Kanjuurou is unharmed.
And everyone who's staying to guard the ship
should be wary of enemy attacks.
Don't let them steal the ship.
What are you saying?!
Are you saying that the enemy will come for us?
Are you saying that
staying to protect the ship isn't a safe job?!
Well, this island is the enemy's main base after all...
but Sanji will be staying to guard the ship with us.
The Guarding Sunny Team
Huh?!  Where'd Sanji go?!
Luffy's group is gone too!
The plan hinges on them!  Where'd they go?!
Hey!  Who'll protect us?!
Everyone who visits this country
will surely find their hearts captivated.
First, the heavenly aroma of the flowers.
Then the smell of food
that the country prides itself in.
Smells great!
And then, dancing girls who never seem to grow tired.
And yet one more thing...
Hey wait!  Give that back!
Huh?
I said wait, Mario!  Come back!
Give me back my arm!
What a troublesome dog you are!
The stuffing will fall out!
Wait!
My sides hurt!  Even if they are just cotton!
A-A stuffed animal?
A sight that astonishes the travelers who visit this land.
Good day.
I am a soldier.
Hmm?  By any chance, have we met before?
You look most familiar.
Oh, I remember!  In this morning's newspaper!
Oh no!  My strings got all tangled!  Help!
What is that?  A toy?
Hey Luffy, look at that!
They mingle with the citizens
as if it was the most ordinary thing in the world.
Coexisting with the humans
in a way that's completely natural.
Living toys.
Factory Destruction & Samurai Rescue Team
This is the country of love, passion and toys.
We are in the port town of Acacia.
A man got stabbed!
Again?
What do you mean, again?
Is there some kind of serial killer on the loose?
No, the ladies of this country
are very passionate about love, and extremely jealous.
If their hearts get broken...
they often stab the guilty man to death.
Scary!
The more beautiful they are,
the more murderous they are.
There's toys running around, but whatever!
Let's go get some food!
Alright!  Disguise complete!
I'm so hungry!
Let's go over there!
Let's try this restaurant!
Pardon me.
I heard that there was a casino around here.
Do you know where it is?
Sorry, old man.  It's my first time in this town, too.
How about asking in that restaurant over there?
Oh, I see.  Thank you for your kindness.
What're you doing?!
We do not have time to be sitting around
in a place like this!
I must find Kanjuurou as quickly as possible!
Now now, calm down.
It's true that we don't have much time, but running around blindly won't help.
We should try and get some information first.
So, does anyone else think something is strange here?
The king of this country abdicated this very morning.
I expected there to be panic, but...
Maybe they don't know yet?
There's no way they wouldn't!
Let's ask them.
Hey, old guy!
Cut it out!
What're you doing?!
Your face was on the front page, remember?!
I am...
very sorry to have kept you waiting.
Or not?!
Here it comes!  I've been waiting for this!
Dress shrimp paella.
Rose squid-ink pasta.
And fairy pumpkin in gazpacho.
It all looks delicious!
Time to eat!
Yummy!
Fairy pumpkin?  What's that?
Well, you see...
Here in this country,
people still believe the legends of fairies.
Or maybe they don't!
What's that supposed to mean?
In other words, maybe fairies appear.  Or maybe they don't!
Fairies appear?
That's right.  Mysterious, isn't it?
It's been like this for centuries.
We can't see them, but they definitely exist.
People...
call those fairies...
Dress Rosa's...
guardian...
spirits!
Or maybe they don't!
Will you shut up already?!
Well then, travelers...
please take care.
Or don't!
Seriously.  It'd be easier to believe
in fairies than in these living toys.
He won again!  That's fourteen times in a row!
What's the commotion about?
It's the roulette table.
An old blind man is messing with them.
Old blind man?
Place your bets!
I've decided.
Black, please.
Did you hear that?  Black, he said!
I'm betting black too!
Me too!
Of course I'll bet black!
No more bets!
Black, number 29!
Black!
Amazing!  Fifteen wins in a row!
Thank you!  Thank you so much, sir!
Trusting you has made me rich!
Oh, it was nothing.  Just a lucky streak.
This isn't much, but take it!  Just a tip.
I'll pay some back to you as well.  Please help me next round, too.
Me too.
And me.
You're pretty good at this.
So, would you like to compete face to face?
One on one?
That's right.  I'd like to challenge your luck.
Don't tell me you're calling it quits now!
Of course not.
The other gamblers were so kind as to tip me, so...
I'll gladly compete with you.
Well said!  I like you, old man!
That said, the rest of you can go cash out.
So, what will you do?
Put me down for white, please.
That so?
Then I'll bet black.
So?  Which is it?
Too bad for you!  It's black!
You lose!
I see...
Well, I'll get it next time!
Go!  White!
We'll see.
Again, how unfortunate!  Black twice in a row!
This time it'll be white!
Black again!
White!
Black!
Too bad!
It's black!
How awful!
He's a disgrace to the Donquixote Family.
What are they doing?
Alright, we'll be taking the money you lost.
It's so easy to win when Buffalo-san isn't here.
You can say that again!
It seems my luck has run out.  How unfortunate.
What will you do?  Will you give up now?
No.
I'll give it one last go.
I bet all my remaining chips!
Intriguing!
Then I'll match you and wager everything I've won too!
Let's have an all-or-nothing match, like real men!
Everything you've won?  Are you sure?
Of course.
Alright, here goes.
What will it be?
I've decided.
White, please.
The blind man reveals his true power, astonishing the Straw Hat Pirates.
Meanwhile, mighty warriors from all over the world
gather at the Corrida Colosseum.
The battle of the century,
with a shocking prize, is about to begin!
Next time, on One Piece:
Swirling Excitement at the Corrida Colosseum
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Swirling Excitement
At The Corrida Colosseum