It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has gone to Marineford...
where he's trying to save his brother Ace from execution.
There was an intense battle in the bay when Luffy and the others advanced on the execution platform,
but then the Navy raised encircling walls,
taking away any chance the pirates could escape.
Hey!  What's going on?!
Raise all of the walls!
Well... The walls can't handle the massive weight of Oars' body!
And it looks like his blood leaked into the system and damaged it!
Oars... You...
They may not be closed in...
but proceed with the operation, Akainu!
Why did the video cut out?!
Show us Marineford!
Hurry and show it already!
Something must have happened to their Surveillance Snails, there's nothing we can do!
The Navy and Whitebeard made a deal?  Can it be true?!
Show us something!
Did Whitebeard really sell out his companions?!
What's going on in this war?!
What will happen to the world?!
What an annoying move by the Navy...
I guess the show's over, huh?
We sailed back here just so we could watch the war...
and now they're having trouble with the Surveillance Snails?
There's no way that's the truth.
Huh?  It's not?
You sure are an idiot.  It's obvious that they're hiding something.
Something they don't want pirates, or anyone else, to see...
Captain Bonnie...
Shut up!  Leave me alone!
Whitebeard sold out his companions?
Like hell.  He's a legend because he never does anything like that.
Time to set sail, Bepo.
Aye aye, Captain!
Come with me, Jambarl!
That's right.  It doesn't look like it'll be fixed anytime soon.
Right now, there's no way to tell what's happening in Marineford.
Meteor Volcano!
We're not letting you escape!
Melt the ice and take away their footing!
The ice is melting!
T-The water...
It's hot!
The magma is making the water boil!
Get out of the water, quickly!
Hey, look!
This way is blocked too!
Is there nothing we can do against this wall?!
Whitebeard...
T-The Old Man's attacks aren't working... That's no ordinary wall!
Now, it's time to end this.
The Moby Dick took a direct hit from the magma!
Put out the fire!
Hurry!
You have to hold on!
Don't let the ship sink!
We're gonna travel the seas with our friends, and Ace, once more!
Whitebeard.  Your era is at an end!
The Moby Dick...
Damn it!  Damn the Navy!
That was our pride and joy!
Damn!  They destroyed our ship!  The ship that's carried the Whitebeard Pirates for decades!
Forgive me.
We're losing our only way into the plaza!
What's going on in there?
You don't have to see it to know what's going on...
With no way to advance or retreat, they can only take the attacks head-on.
You could say those walls are the Whitebeard Pirates' coffin!
Their coffin...
The plan is progressing smoothly.
The execution of Portgas D. Ace... will proceed...
immediately!
We can't even see what's going on!
There's no way we'll let them kill Ace!
Yeah...
There's still one way...
One single path...
The path that Oars made for us!
If we go that way, we'll be killed.  The Navy is sure to be waiting for us.
This is no time to stand around and chat!
Yeah... If we're gonna save Ace, that's the only way...
Ace!
Straw Hat...
We'll go, too!
Yeah!
That route is far too obvious!
It's not over yet!  Hold them off as best as you can!
Fire!
There's no way the enemy would ignore the only opening!
It's definitely a trap!
Fire!
Ace!
They're being tortured to death!
Ace...
Ace!
Fire!
Straw-Hat-boy!
Luffy-kun!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Luffy!
Aim for the ones trying to climb over Oars!
I'm saving you, even if I die!
Commence the execution.
Ace... kun...
Little Oars Junior!  He was still alive?!
Oars...
I'm... gonna protect... Ace-kun...
Oars!
Oars...
Oars is alive!
Yeah!
Captain...
What a guy!
Oars...
Captain Squardo.
Captain Squardo!
You guys...
Right!
Are you alright, Luffy-kun?
Really, how reckless can vyou get?
Prepare to fire.
Shoot!
Oars!
Oars is gonna get beaten again!
I've gotta do something...
I've gotta hurry...
They're gonna execute Ace!
Yes, we must act quickly!
Jinbe!
I've got...
a favor to ask!
Ace... kun...
You sure are persistent...
He's already half-dead!  Finish him off!
Oh, don't bother.  I'll do it.
Kizaru-san!
We need to get the execution over with, and fast.
At times like this, it's best to just pierce them right through the head...
Oars!
Captain Oars!
This is the end.
Lu-
Luffy!
Oh, my.  You finally made it here.
Quite an entrance, son of Dragon.
This youngster sure is scary...
Ace's little brother just went straight over the wall!
That kid...
If nothing else, I praise your tenacity.
But you're not ready for this stage yet.
There's no way you can beat us, you know?
Give Ace...
back!
He's just as reckless as his brother.
Oars!  Stay where you are.
We'll need your strength.
Old Man...
Jozu!  Time for our trump card!
Sure!
All men, prepare yourselves!
We're breaking into the plaza!
Luffy has broken through the Navy's defenses and made it to the plaza at last.
However, the three Navy Admirals now block his way, deflecting all of his attacks.
Meanwhile, in the bay, Whitebeard attempts to use his final trump card to turn the tables.
Next time, on One Piece:
Rush Into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Maneuver to Turn the Tides
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!