Let's pile up all the dreams,
Arittake no yume o kakiatsume
And go find the thing we're looking for... One Piece!
Sagashimono o sagashi ni iku no sa One Piece!
Compasses and the like will only slow us down
Rashinban nante juutai no moto
Translation:
DeSiBoY
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Netsu ni ukasa re kaji o toru no sa
Timing:
yibis
Song translation by
Vegard Aune and
CarlosNet
Even an old treasure map covered in dust...
Hokori kabutte ta takara no chizu mo
Isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
Tashikame ta no nara densetsu ja nai!
For our own storms, all we have to do is
Kojin teki na arashi ha dare ka no
Ride someone else's biorythm...
Baio rizumu nokkatte
And pretend that it isn't there!
Omoisugose ba ii!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
Arittake no yume o kakiatsume
And go find the thing we're looking for...
Sagashimono o sagashi ni iku no sa
A pocket of coins, and
Poketto no koin, soreto
We are!
Let's break the tight-fisted night!
Shimittareta yoru wo buttobase!
We have no interest in treasure chests
Takara bako ni kyoumi wa nai kedo
A pocket of romance, and
Poketto ni roman, soreto
We are!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
Arittake no yume o kakiatsume
And go find the thing we're looking for...
Sagashimono o sagashi ni iku no sa
A pocket of coins, and
Poketto no koin, soreto
We are!
A rainbow on the rocks.
Understood.
This is awesome!
To think that immediately after leaving that fog shrouded Florian Triangle,
there would be such a luxurious resort waiting for us.
Seriously.
We are honored that you are enjoying yourselves.
Here on Spa Island, we have 10 heated swimming pools.
3 flowing pools.
Pools dedicated to diving.
Waterfalls for the sake of meditation.
Cola baths.
Milk baths.
We have 50 varieties of spas available.
Additionally, for those who enjoy playing games,
we have underwater table tennis and an underwater casino.
In regards to the food,
we have chefs of the highest quality providing large portions of their specialties in our Restaurant.
If we were able to ease the weariness our customers have endured after long travel,
I, Doran, would know know greater pleasure, since I am responsible for this facility.
Lucky customers are known to see candy raining and rainbows as well.
Ah, rainbows, as in the natural occurrence that is called the "Gem of the Ocean"?
But, I have heard that its existence hasn't been confirmed for many years.
That is why I said "lucky" customers.
What is wrong?
We may soon see some raining candy after all.
Eh?
You jest.
For you to have set up a resort in this section of the ocean,
you must have really had some problems.
Well, over anything else, we are proud to claim a 10 billion beri profit each year,
and we are officially recognized as a resort by the World Government.
There is not a thing to worry about.
The security is highly sophisticated and efficient,
so even civilians can enjoy themselves, in a relaxed manner.
The yearly profit is 10 billion beri?!
Of course, that goes for pirates as well.
I appreciate your hospitality.
I apologize if I ruined the mood.
As long as they pay, even rebels and pirates are our precious guests.
You two are quite similar, aren't you?
10 billion beri!
Beri, beri, beri!
Slow Slow Menace
Return of Foxy, the Silver Fox
Ready, set...
What the hell is this?
It's candy.
It's raining candy.
It's not even windy, and it is only falling here. We are super lucky!
Super Lucky~!
Are you an idiot?!
You guys sure are idiots!
Who are you?
This is a Sea Raccoon, named Munki.
He can turn into anything.
Hey! Hey! Cool!
He said that this girl is named Lina.
The raccoon spoke!
I am not a raccoon! I am a reindeer!
Eh? Eh, but you...
Are you hungry?
Yup.
Do you want my lunch?
It is no pirate lunch box though.
Huh? Pirates?
Are you serious?
I am Luffy. The man who will become the Pirate King!
I am the ship's doctor, Chopper!
Captain Usopp! The sniper.
Eh! There are funny folks like you among pirates too.
Thank you!
Thanks for the mea...
Huh? What's wrong?
I forgot about big sis.
Eh? Big sis?
Big sis Sayo!
You sure can eat.
This guy will eat anything.
Sea raccoons are omnivores.
Will he eat this too?
AS IF!
Ooh!
What is that thing?
What?! It can turn into anything?
Pretty much.
Please, a beauty. The greatest beauty!
What a ridiculous fool... I can't...
Nami who is sitting right there. Become Nami!
Huh?
TOO SMALL!
What a freakin' idiot! I can't...
But, even though she is small, Nami is Nami.
Nami-swaan!~
Idiot!
See, I told you they are weirdos.
Shall we go?
Thanks for the treat.
Oh? You are leaving?
Yes. Thank you very much for the meal.
Are you alright?
It was fun.
Thanks, Luffy.
Eh? You are leaving already, Sea Raccoon?
That?!
I've been looking for both of you.
You're damn persistent.
I can't believe you would have run all the way here.
Your responsiveness is to be feared.
I would like to capture you both immediately, but...
Wait one second. I seem to have come across some familiar faces.
Huh?
So this is where you were, #100.
Straw Hat, its been a while, right?
Huh? Who are you?
You don't know me?
He doesn't remember!
It's ok Boss. Don't get depressed.
Could you possibly be...
the guys that Zoro and Sanji beat up?
He is doing it on purpose. Definitely on purpose.
Boss!
Hey, Straw Hat, you bastard!
You put an end to my undefeated streak, and even stole our pirate flag from us.
I will not let you claim to have forgotten!
Ah! I remember.
Fissure Head Fox!
It's Foxy the Silver Fox!!
Luffy, be careful. If I remember right, he shoots some strange beams.
Really?
Well, we know to avoid it, so it should be alright.
I wouldn't stay the same forever.
Mirror?
High Speed Rotation Mirror Ball!
New Slow Slow Beam!
Crap.
This is against the rules, isn't it?
Th-at is w-hy I sa-id s-o...
Anyone hit by that will become slow for 30 seconds.
I shall be taking this.
Did you remember now, Straw hat?
In another 10 seconds, you will all be upside down.
9.
8.
7.
Ah, that was a great bath.
My skin is sparkling.
Though, I am pure bone, and don't have skin.
What are you guys doing?
FFFFranky, Brook, beat those guys up!
Huh?
Weapons Left!
Hmm?
What is going on?
Luffy!
100 flowers!
Thanks Robin!
You saved us.
Everyone, are you safe?
Ah, that was surprising.
Amazing, Luffy!
Yeah, I am a rubber man.
There is no way I would lose to that fissure head.
Damn! You went and increased your number of comrades didn't you, Straw Hat?!
Boss, it is a revived corpse!
Damn, let's try once more!
As long as we have this mirror ball...
Idiot, what are you doing?
Hurry and close it.
Gum Gum Bazooka!
Chat us up at http://yibis.com!
#yibis@irc.rizon.net
Calm down please!
What is all the ruckus?
I have something I would like to ask the both of you.
W-What?
That notebook. That was Foxy's target, right?
Foxy?
That pirate we just beat.
They know us as well, but if I had to guess, I would say they were initially after that notebook.
Bull's Eye, right?
This notebook has directions on how to create a gem written inside.
Directions on how to make a gem?!
Lina!
It's fine. Leave it to me.
Huh?
These guys are definitely pirates as well, but don't they seem a bit more trustworthy?
Plus they are strong.
Also, if just the two of us continue, we may not be able to reach our goal.
This is our father's notebook.
Wah, amazing!
It's filled with formulas.
Our father was an inventor, and those formulas are the directions for making it.
Do you guys understand this?
Big sis Sayo can read it.
I have no idea though.
Eh! That is pretty amazing Sayo.
This is a sea map for this area.
Next to the steam mark there is an X?
That is the secret memo.
I think it is a hint at the gem creation method.
Heh? This is?
The notebook has the method down to 99% written down.
The last 1% is supposed to be derived from this memo, right?
Yes.
Hmm, this steam is representative of a spa?
Then, this X is somewhere on Spa Island?
That is what we thought too, so we sneaked on to this island.
Nice job.
But, we searched quite a few places, and couldn't find a place like that, or even a clue.
It's really hard to believe that this memo alone contains directions on how to create a gem.
Still, Foxy and his crew followed them this far in order to get the memo.
Thus, it may really be legitimate!
It might be a fake.
Eh?
Lina...
I am sure this is a fake.
He couldn't possibly make a gem.
Eh? What?
Father was a liar and an idiot. He really was an idiot!
I hate father!
Huh?
Note: Lina's village -3 years ago-
Father!
Welcome back.
Sayo! Lina! It's horrible!
What?
It's a golden horned beetle!
According to legends, when this appears, the village will be destroyed!
What should I do!?
Father...
The colors are fading.
Hahaha! He believed it! What an idiot!
Hey!
Seriously.
What a relief! What a relief!
Huh?
Isn't it great? The village won't be destroyed!
Isn't it great that it was a lie?
Father really loved our village.
Because it's where our mother was born.
This research can save everyone in this village.
Everyone will be able to live without any difficulties.
What kind of research is it, father?
It's a gem.
It's about creating a gem.
Gems... aren't something you can make, father.
Your dad is really funny.
He's not funny at all, that horrible father!
3 years ago, he left to go research but never came back.
We were abandoned.
So we lived with each other.
We were made fun of, but we lived on bearing it.
Father isn't here anymore.
"He died", that's what I thought.
And then one month ago...
Munki suddenly came back with this notebook in his mouth.
There was a letter in it, and do you know what it said?
It said, "Dear daughters, please complete the research that I began."
Isn't it stupid?
He left us for 3 years to go researching.
Why do we have to risk our lives and come all the way out here?
He's an idiot! An idiot!
I'll never believe what he says!
I bet he's fooling us with this picture because the gem is fake!
Why is the last clue a stupid quiz!?
Your dad really is funny!
I want to see it too, that gem.
Were you guys really listening to me!?
Hey, there you guys are.
You're late, Zoro.
Hey!
But you're here looking for the treasure, aren't you?
Not me, my sister is!
I'm her bodyguard.
Bodyguard?
Big sis says she'll find the secret no matter what so I came here to protect her.
What are you guys doing?
There is definitely a way to create the gem!
I believe him.
Big sis Sayo...
Everyone, please save...
Big sis Sayo!
I have the girl.
If you want her back, listen.
Doran!
Who's that?
The owner of this ship.
What was that?
I'll have you look for that notebook's secret.
Then I'll give you back the girl.
Crap!
It wasn't only Foxy!
What should we do, Luffy?
Please Lina, complete the research!
Please don't give father's dreams to guys like them!
Father's research is full of lies.
Why does Bis sis Sayo have to be captured because of this notebook?
Please, Luffy, save Big sis Sayo!
Next time on One Piece:
The Grand Treasure Hunt
Collapse! Spa Island
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Grand Treasure Hunt
Collapse! Spa Island
Look forward to the next episode!!