Translations, DeSiBoY
Timing,        Dino08
DeSiBoY
Typesetting, DeSi
Editing, rumble
Encoding, DeSiBoY
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
QCing, mithrandiryod
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
It sure is a calm night, isn't it?
I've been on watch tonight, but it has been completely calm.
Steering is completely meaningless.
This is what I call, "Breaking a bone for no reason".
And I am just bone~
I am so bored.
Laboon.
I have become comrades with Luffy and this crew.
They are good people.
But, that is not all.
I found something amazing during the day.
Hmm?
In it was the recounting of the crew's amazing adventures and battles.
But, as long as I have become their comrade, I must act appropriately.
That is right.
Laboon!
Everyone, good morning!
Then, a waking piece!
~White Handkerchief~
Shut up!
The sun still hasn't risen.
Let us sleep for a little bit more.
Forget about Brook, and stop Luffy's snoring!
Brook's Hard Struggle
The Difficult Path to Becoming a True Crewmate?
What shall we do, Miss. Navigator?
If we use the paddles, we can escape this calm water.
Based on the weather, I would say it should only stay calm for today.
Then, there is no need to waste my precious cola.
Yummy!
Sanji's food is the best, after all.
Huh?
Robin, how about seconds on your seafood salad?
Thank you.
What's wrong, Brook?
Why have you been freaking out since this morning?
Did you see something interesting, Brook?
Yesterday, when he was on watch, he saw the Voyage Journal.
Yes! I just happened to come across it.
Truthfully, I was shocked.
My excitement from the Thriller Bark incident had yet to subside,
but for you, that was just the tip of the iceberg.
You stopped the rebellion in the sand country of Arabasta.
The great adventure in Sky Island, though it's existence was considered a mere legend.
Followed by the amazing feat of making the World Government an enemy at Water 7.
It was so surprising that I thought my heart would pop out.
Ah! But, I don't have a heart.
That's right.
But, from here on out, what will we be writing in it?
Brook will be added to the Voyage Journal too, right?
That is it!
Since I have become your comrade, I don't feel like I have been of any help.
I can understand you getting all worked up, but let me give you a piece of advice.
I shall listen carefully, Nami.
In this crew, you must never let your guard down during a meal.
Yes! If it is about that, this "quick draw" Brook shall be ready regardless of when an enemy attacks.
It seems like it is already too late.
That food is mine!
Wait one second.
Luffy!
To think I let my guard down for even a second.
I understand!
I shall work myself to the bone, so that I can be your true comrade as soon as possible.
But, I was only bone to start out with.
Sanji!
No, you are really helping me out.
Since you are willing to help wash dishes,
I can prepare tea to take to Nami.
I am really looking forward to helping everyone when something major occurs,
but first I'd like to start out helping everyone with even the smaller things.
That is a great of you.
A skeleton who wishes to help out with small things, one at a time.
Then, I shall take the tea to Nami.
Sanji, where shall I put these.
Over there...
Don't drop them even it kills you!
Even if you say that, I am already dead!
Bon!
Don't say "Bon!"!
Hold this.
Magnificent.
Don't say "Magnificent"!
I shouldn't have had you wash the dishes...
Ah! Then I shall give Nami the tea in your place.
Wait!
That is for me to...!
Nami.
I have brought the tea.
Come on in.
Would you mind showing me your panties?
THAT ALL OF A SUDDEN?!
A map?
Well, we have been pretty busy of late.
Now that the ship isn't moving, this is a great chance.
Nami, your dream is to draw a map of the world, right?
Yes.
With my navigational skills, I will travel the Oceans of the world,
and draw a map of the World that I saw with my own eyes.
How superb.
If there is anything I can help with, feel free to ask me.
Would you like a refill?
Thank you.
For now, just the thought is more than enough.
You really are an amazing and considerate person, Nami.
Wait a second, you are going too far.
No, not at all.
H-Hot!
Hey, are you alright?
No, I almost burnt my finger.
Wait, I don't have any skin to burn.
Ah! The map!
I can't believe what I have done. Oh my!
Don't worry.
See, it is so nice and clean.
It really is clean...
THAT IS WRONG, DAMN IT!
Excuse me!
Huh?
At this rate, it feels like I haven't helped at all.
Hey, Brook!
Luffy?
It looks like those two are going to do something interesting.
You, come and check it out too.
Y-Yes.
Chopper, what are you doing here?
The weather is nice, so I am sun-drying my medicinal plants.
Franky is going to test his new weapon.
Alright!
This thing uses cola as energy, and is a high force Super Franky Cannon!
Compared to a regular cannon, its accuracy and strength are many times more powerful.
That added to my Sniper skills creates a monstrous combination.
I am so excited. My heart is beating so fast.
Right?
Umm, if there is anything I can do to help, let me know.
Let me think. Well, just to be on the safe side, get another barrel of cola.
That is an easy request. I will do so happily!
This must be it.
The cola barrel is here!
Alright, pour it in right there.
Yes!
The target is that rocky outcrop.
Alright! I have locked on to the target.
Oh!
Fire!
Alright!
Huh?
That's strange.
Usopp, increase the pressure.
Alright, here I go.
Huh?
Hey, something seems wrong.
Watch out!
Well, that was a huge failure.
That shouldn't be...
Huh? This is kinda salty.
There is something mixed in with the cola.
Ah, this is soy.
Eh?
What is wrong everyone?
Don't act all confused! You mixed up the cola and soy barrels, didn't you!
Ah! You're right. So that is what it was.
This was a huge mistake on my part.
Shut up you bastard!
What were you thinking! What were you trying to do?
This isn't the time for you to be talking like some old geezer.
This guy is hilarious.
My entire body is soaked.
Ah, the plants that I was drying need to be wiped down.
Oh! This meat has gotten a lot better with the extra soy!
How freaking positive can you be?
Everything I have done has backfired on me.
Umm, Zoro...
Huh?
This isn't the time for me to be admiring him.
I too am a swordsman.
Meditation I see.
You control your mental state, and reach a blank slate in your mind.
I shall accompany you.
Umm, Zoro.
Hmm?
I know that I shouldn't disturb you by talking, but...
I don't really care.
Well, the thing is...
What is it?!
I suddenly feel the need to go to the toilet.
You don't need to get my permission for every freakin' thing...
The thing is...
Huh?!
My legs fell asleep, and I can't stand up.
Do you even have any muscles for your legs to fall asleep?!
Zoro, pretty soon I am gonna leak...
W-W-Wait one second!
I'll take you there!
Everything I do has brought inconvenience to everyone.
What bad luck.
Robin, is there anything I can help you with?
Nothing in particular.
I see.
Brook.
Why are you so unsettled?
Unsettled?
It seems like you are afraid of something.
Am I wrong?
You're right.
It is just as you say.
That's right, I am unsettled, scared, and I can't bear it!
When Luffy first invited me to join the crew, I was...
Those words alone made me so happy.
And, when we all defeated Oz together, I felt so proud.
Is it ok for me to become your comrade?
Yeah, it's fine.
EH?!
But, was it really ok for me to join?
Now that we are heading into the New World, it is a fact that ridiculously strong enemies will cross our path.
What would happen if I were not of any help, and was only a holding you back...
If something like that were to happen, I would need to leave the ship.
I would have to return to that lifestyle of living alone for years on end.
I too used to be very insecure.
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
I too used to be very insecure.
I was always afraid that I wasn't suitable to be one of their comrades.
That is why I wanted to give my life for their sake.
I thought that this would make me suitable to have a been with them.
Robin...
I have gigantic enemies, whom I can't escape from, regardless of where I am on the Seas.
My enemy is the world, and that darkness.
That is why I didn't want you to come and save me!
If my life will always come with the risk of death, then I want to die here and now!
Robin, you thought that...
But, that was my mistake.
True comrades aren't that.
Robin.
I am sure that you'll be fine too.
Brook! Food! Food!
It's time for lunch!
Luffy!
Sanji put his cooking skills on the line, and made a huge meal from the sea ingredients he harvested.
It will definitely be tasty!
Luffy!
Huh?
What are you doing? Hurry, and come on!
Am I really good enough?
Is it ok that I have joined the Straw Hat Crew?
Yeah.
That was too easy! But... But...
I decided it, so you will be fine.
Huh?
Forget about that, it's time for food! Food!
Everyone is waiting!
Even the Straw Hat Crew can have such a calm day like this one.
Usopp, lets go catch dinner!
Yeah!
How many years... No, how many decades has it been,
since I have been able to take an afternoon nap so comfortably?
Hey, Brook!
How long are you going to be sleeping?
Wake up, we can see the island!
It is a Summer Island! It has a beach!
While I wandered the seas alone, I would dream of the time I spent with my comrades or Laboon.
I would be so happy, and when I awoke, only the pain of my lonely reality was there for me.
For me, sleep was never a peaceful thing.
But now, if I listen carefully...
Hey, hey, Robin!
What do you think of this clothing?
Let's see.
I think that either of these would suit you.
Ah! I knew it!
Good.
There are comrades so close by.
I died, and am only bones now, but...
I am really glad that I am alive!
This short time we have now is without a doubt just a break that will lead into our next adventure.
Yes. Time to rest one's bones.
Laboon. It seems that next time we are to meet, I will have many stories to tell.
I hope you are still waiting and are looking forward to it.
The wind is back.
Everyone.
Everyone!
It's about time we get going!
YEAH!
I too will work myself to the bone, and put my body on the line!
I am a skeleton though, so I don't have a body.
We're finally here atthe Red Line!
The Island of Mermen is pretty close.
I wonder where the mermaids are?
There are no mermaids, but a sea monster has arrived.
You bastard!
After we beat him, something came out of his stomach.
That is... Could it be?
Next time on One Piece,
Halfway through the Grand Line
Arrival! The Red Line
I will become Pirate King!
Halfway through the Grand Line
Arrival! The Red Line