It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Only four and a half hours remain until Ace's execution.
Luffy made it to Level One as Warden Magellan finally caught up to him,
and the escape from Impel Down has been halted on the verge of success.
What... is going on here?!
There aren't any warships around!
Take a good look!
You can still barely see their shadows through the mist!
Warships coming in hard and fast!
I'll launch you onto the deck of one of the ships!  Hold on tight!
What?!  What did you say?!
You damn fish!
You listening, bastard?!
WHAT IS GOING ON?!
They've come to steal the ship!
Don't let them take it!
If we can push the Devil Fruit users into the ocean, we win!
Hey.
Who are you going to push into the sea?
Seems you don't know your opponents.
Don't hold back!  Throw them overboard!
What's that?
It's Jinbei!
TL Note: Spear Wave
Hey!
Oh, how careless of me.
That's the ship we're gonna use, isn't it?
How's that?!
Alright!  He's almost finished!
Take this, you bastard!
Let's put an end to this pointless stalling.
I've already ordered all warships to leave Impel Down.
The warships you were planning to steal are already gone!
The old Fishman guy went to steal one of the warships!
They'll find a way to do it!
Jinbei, huh?
Then it's all the more important that I finish this quickly!
Oh no!  Oh no!  Run away, Straw Hat!
It's no good!  My wax won't work against him now!
TL Note: Doru Doru Cancellation
That was close!
Let's get out of here!
Hurry!
TL Note: Hell's Judgement
Damn it to Hell!
Hey... Help me!
Take me with you!
You idiot!  Don't touch me!
The poison is... spreading!
Doesn't matter if it's wax or stone...
The poison keeps spreading like an infection!
Damn it!  Now the Doru Doru armor is completely useless!
What happened to Straw-chan and the others?
How's it going with the warships?
I can hear gunfire, but I can't really tell what's happening in that mist!
I'm sure they'll be able to steal one of the warships, but...
In any case, they're pretty far away.
It's going to take a while for them to steal one and then bring it back.
Doesn't that mean that Magellan might get here first?
Straw Hat Luffy is strong and all...
I doubt he'll be able to hold Magellan back very long...
Straw-chan...
Damn it!  Please hurry, Jinbei!
Force them into the sea!  Don't let them take the ship!
How dare you?!
What's with this guy's body?!
His whole body is made of blades!
TL Note: Supa Supa = Slicing sound
It's because of the Supa Supa Fruit.
I just remembered who this guy is!
He's the West Blue assassin, Daz!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
It's only a matter of time before they take the ship!
That would be a huge disgrace for the Navy!
Sink it, immediately!
Yes, Sir!
Prepare to attack!
It's that thing from before!
Damn it, our gunpowder's all wet!
Jinbei, huh?!
Load another battery, and shoot him!
Hurry!  Hurry!  He's right behind us!
Hey!  Guys, are you there?!
That's Straw-chan's voice!
We've gotta run!
There's some monstrous thing chasing after them!
It's Magellan!  There's nowhere to run!
We got a warship yet?!
Straw-chan!  We're still waiting for a ship to get on!
Whaaaaat?!
Vi've managed, somehow, to make it this far with a hormone injection...
But... Vi can go no further...
Iva-chan?!
What a surprise!
It... It seems Vi made it in time...
He hit the back of his head so hard he passed out!
Iva-san!  And Inazuma, too!  You're alive!
Thank goodness!
Iva-sama!
Those two!
Straw Hat!  It's from Jinbei!
A Baby Snail Phone!
Well done, you two!
Why did you even come along?
Luffy-kun, so you made it?
I'm here!  He's still chasing us, though!
We're gonna hit a dead end at the exit!
Forgive me.  We've stolen a ship, but we're too far away from you!
But don't stop moving!
Jump straight into the sea!
Get everyone to throw themselves into the ocean!
What are you saying, Jinbei?!
We're in the Calm Belt, you know!
You can leave the rest to me!
Do what he says!
Wha-?!
Three!  Come help me one more time!
Are you insane?!  If we leap into the ocean, we'll die for sure!
He works for the Government!  He's not worthy of our trust!
That damn Fishman bastard!
He's Ace's friend!
I trust him!
To the sea?  If you think you can, then just try and get away!
The moment you touch the water, you'll be in the Sea Kings' nest!
Be careful!  Don't let even a drop of his poison touch you!
That's impossible!
It's over!
This is a special service!
It's pointless!
Straw Hat!  Hurry up!
I can't hold on any longer!
He pushed him back!
The poison's still coming toward us!
Jumping into the sea is our only hope?!
Here it comes!
Iva-chan!  Iva-chan, wake up!
We're in trouble!
Iva-chan!  Wake up!
Hey!  Hurry and wake up!
Hmm?  What?
We gotta hurry!
Who are vyou?  Straw Hat Boy's son?
Use that move of yours!
The Wink!
Okay then.
Hey, you can't be serious!  If we do that...
Here Vi go!
Hey, wait a second, Iva-sama!
Your plan is pointless!
If you enter the sea without a ship, there's no hope for you!
Everyone, grab on to his face!
His face?!
I will not let you escape!
Alright!
Grab on to Iva-sama!
I will not allow any one of you to escape from Impel Down!
You won't get away!
WE'RE FALLING!
There's something under the ships!
What the -?!
Fly, Ivankov!
You can't pass out now!
What?
W-We landed on something!
Hey!  Look at this!
What is this?!
So you made it in time...
I'm sorry for calling you out to such a dangerous sea!
It's a school of whale-sharks!
Jinbei called them here!
Awesome!
Luffy and the others have finally escaped Impel Down.
However, there is no time to celebrate.
The Gates of Justice are blocking their path, and the marines are closing in from behind.
When the situation seems hopeless, a friend makes the ultimate sacrifice!
Next time, on One Piece:
Produce One Last Miracle!
Break Through the Gates of Justice
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!