Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and invaded Dress Rosa.
Luffy joined a battle tournament to win the Mera Mera Fruit...
and made it through the preliminary round.
Now he's heading toward the palace to rescue Law from Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, Luffy's comrade-in-arms, Kyros, is reflecting on his secret bond with King Riku.
Please step back, King Riku!
Your Majesty!
Come with me.
At last... At last...
He is the first man to ever win a thousand battles straight!
Kyros, you've come here again?
Stay back!
How could you understand?
No matter what I do,
I'll always be a murderer and a beast!
Is there...
no way...
they could forget me?
Her name will be Rebecca.
I can't touch something so pure!
My hands are filthy!  I don't want to corrupt her!
What a funny father you have, Rebecca.
Rebecca, you're like an angel.
I'll be with you.  I'll always watch over you!
What's happening?
The Plan Fails!
Usoland the Hero Dies!?
Father!
The royal palace... it's burning.
What's happening to this country?
I'll go to the palace.
Scarlett, Rebecca, listen to me.
Father?
If the danger reaches here,
then wait for me at the red flower field.
I swear I'll come for you.
I... I don't believe it!
What has happened?
Open the door!  It's me, Kyros!
Is anybody there?
Guards!  Open the door!
I want to speak to King Riku!
Pirates?!
Kyros!
Viola-sama!
My father... King Riku is safe.
What happened?
Well...
The new king is waiting for you, Captain Kyros.
New king?!
I'll take you to him.
What have you done to King Riku?
This way.
Viola-sama, come with me.
No, he wants to see you alone.
Shall I secure your weapon?
I'm not handing it over.
Well done -in.
You won't harm Kyros, right?
Of course we won't -in.
The young master said he could be of use to us -in.
Otherwise, we'd have killed him long ago -in.
You were in league with the pirates?!
He's in here.  Go ahead.
Where is King Riku?
Who are you?
He's here.
No!
Sea Stone?!
Your Majesty!
What have you done to
this country and the king, pirate?!
The king burned the city.  Didn't you see him?
His Majesty would never do such a thing!
Kyros!
Take this Sea Stone chain off me!  I'm not a Devil Fruit user.
Kyros, your reputation precedes you.
It seems you're the Colosseum's mightiest fighter.
Join me.
The king will be replaced, and the old royal family will be destroyed.
My men should already be going after your wife and daughter, who carry the blood of the king.
Watch closely.
Dress Rosa's time under the Riku family is over.
He cut off his own leg?!
Kyros!
A... A toy?
That toy just ran off with the king -dasuyan!
I've been turned into a toy!
What's going on?  Am I dreaming?
King Riku!  It's me, Kyros!
Kyros?
That's right!
I'm sorry.  I've never heard that name before.
I'll forever be in your debt, strange, little toy.
Run, Scarlett, Rebecca!
Wait for me at the promised place!
Two Days Later
Nobody knows my name.
Have... I been forgotten?
I must get to the red flower field.
Scarlett and Rebecca are waiting for me!
Scarlett?
Scarlett!
Somebody's been shot!
The Riku Royal Army again?!
Why?  Why didn't you wait for me?!
Of course.
I must have disappeared from your mind, too.
Both our promise... and our time together...
Scarlett!
Scarlett, hang in there!
Scarlett!  Scarlett!
I don't know who you are...
but my daughter is waiting for me,
and she's famished...
Please...
It's me!  It's Kyros!
Scarlett...
Scarlett!
How can this be our parting?
This is hell!  It's too cruel!
With these tin arms,
I can't even feel your fading warmth!
Scarlett!
Soldier-san.
Soldier-san!
Oh, Viola-sama.
Are you alright?
We're in trouble.  I can see our enemies coming at us from the first floor.
Unacceptable!  So it was just someone impersonating the young master?
Straw Hat and the others must be on the second floor or higher!
Violet's blood was on the wall!
This is bad.
If we're about to be cornered into a fight,
maybe it'd be better for me to launch a sneak attack on Doflamingo right now.
Usoland and the others may not make it in time.
You're all pirates, huh.
I noticed it about Fraland and Usoland after a while.
You got a problem with that?
I used to be an outlaw, myself.
As long as we share a common goal, I'll happily fight alongside you.
Corrida Colosseum
The ceiling in the Colosseum's basement is cracking!
Even before the finals,
hundreds of monsters were fighting here.
This day has taken its toll on the building.
Burgess's attacks are the final straw!
The entire place could collapse!
Surging Elbow!
Elbow!  Elbow!
That bastard!
Don't fire at us!
Good.
I'll tell you as many times as I have to, Rebecca.
It was I who shot and killed your mother, Scarlett.
Hey!  My barrier can't block verbal attacks!
Soldier-san, I can't...
Mother, I'm hungry.
I'll go get us something to eat.
Okay.
I'm so frustrated, I can't even move!
Toys' House
Cyborg Franky has been brought down!
U... Usopp... you can do it.
Hurry and create some panic!
Usoland!  Usoland!
The Underground Trade Port
Sure-Kill Green Star Rapid-Fire!
I Dunno What, But Some Kind of Awesome Move Special!
There's an intense battle going on at the Commanders' Tower.
Hang in there, Usopp from the Straw Hat Pirates!
I've never even seen you, but hang in there, Usopp!
If you win, I'll be indebted to you forever!
Hang in there!
I don't want to be a toy for the rest of my life!
If you can turn me back, I won't hunt Straw Hat any more!
I'd gladly become your underling or anything!
Hang in there!
I'll give you as much money as you like!  Just help me!
Trébol, hurry and get Sugar to the palace.
It's fine, Doffy.  Nothing is gonna happen.
Don't worry, young master.
The enemy isn't even conscious anymore.
Usoland!
You can have this poisoned grape back.
The tatababasco...
That was our only hope!
You eat it...
and die.
Sugar!  What are you doing?!
Get a grip!
S-Sugar...
fainted!
Now, the undefeated winner of three thousand battles, Kyros, challenges Doflamingo to end all the tragedies!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Legend Reborn!
Kyros' All-Out Attack
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!