Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Two years have passed since the great war at Marineford.
Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates have all been training on their own...
and now they've set course for their next stage - The New World.
They finally made it to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea, when...
The pirate-boy wearing a straw hat...
Chase him out of the kingdom, right now!
The human with the straw hat...
Straw Hat Luffy...
By his hands...
Fishman Island will...
be destroyed!
Hurry up, guys!
Quiet... Be quiet!
If they see us, we're done for!
Now's our chance!  Hurry and get aboard the ship!
Everyone grab an oar, and prepare to get going!
Hurry!  Hurry!
They could come chasing after us at any moment!
We can't stay on Fishman Island any longer.
We have to get past the Red Line, quickly!
Damn it!  I really wanted to see the Mermaid Café!
If only I could've seen the cute mermaids, even once!
You'll have to give up on that, idiots!  Now stop talking and row!
Honestly... I can't believe this!
The Kraken was sleeping on the ocean floor,
so we managed to avoid it...
and we made it down ten thousand meters.
Then all those sea monsters surrounded us...
and we couldn't even fight back!
Join the fishmen or die?!
At that time, we didn't have any choice
but to join them!
You've got to be kidding me...
Why should we humans become the fishmen's underlings?!
We're moving farther and farther away
from the Mermaid Café.
Quit your crying!  Keep moving, men!
We'll be lucky if we escape with our lives!
Huh?  They ran away?
That's right, Boss.
We only took our eyes off them for a minute.
So they ran away again -dosun?
They never learn, do they -dosun?
Humans run away all the time.
Maybe I should just tear them apart?
What a bother -hi.
It's fine.
We can use them to set another example.
In that case, should I take a shot at them -hi?
Not necessary, Ikaros.
Muhi, understood.
I'll go myself.
Huh?!
Prepare a bubble.
You can't take that many power drug pills all at once!
Alright, we're here!
This is my house!
It's huge!
Welcome home, Master!
Oh my!  It's Monsieur Pappagg!
The super-celebrity?!  Amazing!  Is it really him?
Huh, I never knew you were so popular.
Yeah, I bet you're surprised now!
Out at sea, I'm nothing more than a stylish starfish.
But here on Fishman Island,
I am the president of the Criminal clothing brand.
A super-popular celebrity designer!
My brand is known all over the world,
and it's sold in stores in every country!
Even the famous Doskoi Panda-
Oh, look over there!  What's that?
Hey, are you listening to me, Straw?!
The Criminal Store is on the first floor.
Really?  Let's go have a look!
Caimie... Caimie...
Sure!
Hey!
Won't you listen... to my story...
Wait, dear customer, you're being unreasonable!
This is a very high-class brand we're selling here.
What's going on?
It sounds like the shopkeeper has a problem.
Perhaps someone's complaining?
Like I said, your prices are too high!  Though the clothes are cute.
That voice...
Alright, drop the price to ten thousand beli.
I can't do that, dear customer!
That's less than half the original price!
I knew it was her.  That complainer.
Hey, Nami!
Luffy!
Nami-chin!
Caimie!
It's been so long!  How have you been?
Great!
Hey, hey.  What's going on here?
Oh, Monsieur Pappagg, perfect timing.
We have a somewhat difficult customer here...
Oh!
Wait, you mean this is your store?
What's with the high prices?  Are you trying to rip me off?!
Monsieur!
Well, the brand's expensive.
I'm a popular designer, after all...
Give me a discount!
No, wait!
Don't be so hostile!
I owe you guys a lot for what you did two years ago!
You can have it for free!  Take whatever you like!
For free?  Really?!
Right guys, let's go all out!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Monsieur!  They emptied the whole store!
You really did go all out!
How nice for you.
Hmm?  What could that be?
There's a lot of noise coming from outside.
Monsieur!  Big news!
What is it?
H-H-He is here!
"He"?
Why is he here?
That's...
Look up at the sky!
He's come down from the royal palace!
Jamon!  Jamon!
Jamon!
What's that?  A whale?
Jamon!  Jamon!  Jamon!
Jamon!  Jamon!
Jamon!
Why would he come to these lowly waters?
This is the first time I've seen him in person!
What's going on?  He doesn't even have an escort!
Unbelievable!  He decided to just suddenly come down here on his own?!
Maybe there's some kind of national crisis?!
Why else would he take the time to come here?!
Who's the old guy?
What the?!  You don't even know?!
That's...
The great king of Fishman Island,
or rather, the Ryuuguu Kingdom...
King Neptune!
Neptune.
That's one huge merman!
I much prefer the mermaids.
Hey, you guys!
What a shaggy old guy!
I'm telling you, you're being rude!
Kneel before him already!
That whale is so cute!
Does he have business with that human?
King Neptune came to see them in person?
Hey, Megalo.  You're sure it's these people -jamon?
Huh?  Didn't we meet that shark on the way here?
Oh yeah, the one wearing clothes!
The guy who'd been captured by Surume!
Human with the straw hat, and his friends.
W-What is it?
I have come...
to take you...
to see the Ryuuguu Palace -jamon!
Whaaat?!
R-R-R-R-R-Ryuuguu Palace?!
Ryuuguu Palace?
Good, your pulse has stabilized.
You should be safe now.
Good thing those two donated blood to you.
Those two...
It's alright, silly.
If you like, we'll gladly give you more, silly.
I'm grateful, but honestly I'd rather forget those guys.
I'm really glad.  If you'd died of blood loss before we found Nami and Robin...
that really wouldn't be funny.
Nami-san...
Robin-chan...
Oh no!  Sanji's in trouble!
Hey, come over here!  Splash!  Splatter!
What is it?  Do you need more of our blood?
Then feel free to ask!  We'll give you as much...
as you want!
You have to stay still, silly!
We'll stay here and...
make you all better!
No thank you!
You don't have to be so shy!
You have to stay still!
Moving in that condition is bad for your health!
Your very existence is far worse for my health!
Hang in there, Sanji.
Stay away from me, you freaks!
R-R-R-
Ryuuguu Palace?!
That's right -jamon.
Taking them to see the Ryuuguu Palace?!
Who are these humans?
King Neptune even came to see them in person!
But they're friends of Monsieur Pappagg!  They must be important!
Look!  They've got the Soul King with them too!
You're right!
What's the Ryuuguu Palace?
You idiot!  You don't know?!
I'll tell you...
To those of us in the Ryuuguu Kingdom, that place is like a holy land!
The heavenly realm,
where normal humans are never allowed to go!
The Ryuuguu Palace is where...
King Neptune and the three Neptune Brothers,
as well as the Mermaid Princess live-
The royal palace of the Ryuuguu Kingdom!
Really...
Caimie, you did it again!
Huh... So, old guy!
Don't call him that, Straw!
Do you have any tasty food in the Ryuuguu Palace?
Straw!
Certainly.  We have already prepared a feast for you -jamon.
Really?  I'm looking forward to it!
I certainly would like to see this Ryuuguu Palace!
My chest is swelling with anticipation...
Though I do not have a chest that can swell!
I wanna go there too!
Ryuuguu Palace... I can already smell the treasure!
So that's your motivation...
Right, let's go!
Very well then, Megalo.
Carry the human with the straw hat and his friends
to the Ryuuguu Palace -jamon.
Can we really ride you?
Awesome!
I wonder if we will get to meet the Mermaid Princess?
I'm so excited!
What're you doing?  Come with us!
No... We really shouldn't...
go to the Ryuuguu Palace.
Right?
Don't say that, let's go!  We should go to the feast together!
We can't just leave you here, can we?
Is that alright, old geezer?
Did you just call him an old geezer?!
Your friends are quite welcome too -jamon.
So that's that.
You're quite reasonable, old geezer.
Again, he's...
Please, you guys...
Right, let's go!
To the Ryuuguu Palace!
Hurry!  Hurry up!
Row faster!
Or else they'll spot us!
We're caught in a deep sea current!  This is tough!
This is why we should've
had a paddle installed on the ship!
Do you realize how brutal the New World is?!
Captain, look!
There's something ahead of us!
That's...
Hody Jones!
N-No way!  He found us!
Huh?  He's...
What's that?  He's wearing handcuffs!
No way!  Isn't he planning to fight us?
He disappeared!
Where did that damn bastard go?!
What... what just happened?!
He pierced through the hull!
He's so fast!
He's on the ship!
Take him down!  There's only one enemy!
No way!  It didn't work!
I've fought against fishmen before.
How many trials do you think I've overcome to get this far?!
You're just a fish!
Don't underestimate humans, you fool!
Captain!
Damn it!
Man, this is a nasty thing we've gotten hold of -hi.
The power drugs... Energy Steroids.
A fishman's inherent physical strength is ten times that of a regular human.
However, your power is doubled again if you take a single Energy Steroid pill.
Twenty times the strength of a human.
Taking two of them multiplies it again!
The price for this dreamlike power is that it shortens your lifespan.
However, we will accept an early death in exchange for furthering our cause!
W-What is that bastard doing?!
What is he planning to do with the mast?!
Now I understand why he's wearing handcuffs!
He's showing us that he
doesn't even need his hands to sink us!
The life of Fisher Tiger was taken by humans!
The will of Arlong, too!
Our generation will end
Fishman Island's dark history of oppression!
We, the New Fishman Pirates, will end it!
Float into the New World.
Oh, goodness... You didn't kill them all, did you?
No, I need them alive.
Live with those wounds and show the world above...
what happened to you here beneath the sea!
Tell them who you met!
Tell the humans on dry land about our terror!
We will take the center of the world, Fishman Island,
from that pathetic Sea God, Neptune,
and drag you humans into the dark depths of the sea!
We'll teach you all that fishmen are the superior species!
The king of Fishman Island, King Neptune, invites Luffy and the others to a feast,
and takes them to the Ryuuguu Palace.
However, the smell of cooking lures Luffy away from the rest of the group,
and he wanders off on his own in search of food.
Then Luffy finds a giant tower sealed by a solid door.
Next time, on One Piece:
Ryuuguu Palace!
Brought by the Shark they Saved
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!