Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and invaded Dress Rosa.
Luffy joined a battle tournament where the prize was the Mera Mera Fruit...
and made it through the preliminary round.
Now he's heading toward the palace to rescue Law from Doflamingo.
Hurry to the second floor!
I just have to keep going, right?
Where are you going?!
Up there, right?
Where did they go?
A-Amazing!  We're right in front of our goal!
Elsewhere, Usopp and Robin have been
helping the Tontattans with Operation SOP...
You're still gonna keep trying?
Making Sugar eat the tatababasco...
is our duty!
Doce Fleur!
Hurry up!
Force the tatababasco into her mouth!
That's as far as you go!
Quit wasting everyone's time!
The Liar
Usoland on the Run!
What on earth is going on over there?
Apparently there's an intruder.
But we've got Trébol-sama on our side.
I feel bad for them, but they don't stand a chance against him.
They just keep getting back up.
I let my guard down and was made into a toy.
That means that everyone must have forgotten about me.
Usopp...
Where's Usopp?
You can do it, Usopp.
You're the only one left.
Turn me back into a human.
Toys' House
Now!  Finish him off!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
He's my prey!
Give it up, Franky!
Stop resisting and turn yourself in!
Shut up.
Shut the hell up!
I've decided to go on a pointless rampage, so prepare yourselves.
If I went underground with these guys after me, I'd get in the gnomes' way.
I'll leave Operation SOP to you guys.
Bring it on!
I'll take on these guys.
I'm counting on you, Usoland.
Royal Palace Second Floor: The Suit Chamber
Just how long do we gotta wait here?
What's wrong?  You're all pale.
The Tontattan gnomes have been wiped out by the Family's top commander, Trébol.
What?!
My crewmates should be with them.
Yes, the long-nosed one is.
Usoland.
But he's...
Then we wait.
If he's with them, it'll be fine.
Usopp's the kind of guy you can count on when you need him.
They were trying so hard to make me eat this.
It's probably poison.
It stinks.
W-We can't do anything anymore.
Don't worry!  If anything goes wrong, I'll save you!
Usoland.
I can't believe them...
Move it!
Where are you going, buddy!
Alright, I've successfully escaped!
Forgive me, Tontattans.
Usopp, where are you?
Okay, I'll write of your bravery in a
picture book for future generations.
"The Trusting Tontattans."  That's a good title.
I must live on.
Besides, this is all Franky's fault.
Why won't he come help?
Like hell I'm dying for the sake of pretending to be a hero!
Now that I've escaped, how do I get out of here?
I can't use the hole we came in from on my own.
Wait, they said there's a port.
Hey, everyone outside!
Hey, hey, are you guys working?
This isn't some show, you bastards!
Oh crap!
Get back to work!
Keep moving those crates!
Don't just stand there!
Hurry the hell up!
Is someone standing up to the Donquixote Family?
It's been eight years since I became a toy, and this is a first.
I don't care who, but please destroy this place!
A show?!  I've seen enough of it!
What are we gonna do about them?
Uso... la...
Hey, hey, are these guys saying something?
Uso...
...la...
...nd.
...land.
Usoland.
Usola...
Dammit, where's the lift?!
Usoland.
Usoland.  Usoland.
Usoland?
There are others, as well, right?
Oh, you mean Usoland?
That's the name he said before.
I've gotta get away from here!
Usoland... Usoland... Usoland...
Everyone...
Uso...
Usoland!
Usoland?
Dammit, don't call my name!
Usoland?  Hey, who's that?
Like I said, it's the name the gnomes said earlier.
You're the one who asked them.
You're an idiot.  Just die.
As if I'd die, you damn brat.
Just die.
D-
Usoland is our hero.
H-H-Hero?
Then he's gonna come save you all?
That's right.
And not just us.
Usoland said he'd save us all.
The toys who are forced to work everyday down here.
Is he talking about us?
Our comrades who are slaving away in the factory.
The toys who look cheerful walking through town as they cry inside.
The poor big folk who don't realize they've lost someone dear to them.
Usoland's gonna save us all.
He's a legendary hero!
Is that all you have to say?
Like hell I'm gonna pretend to be a hero!
Poor you.
He was lying all along.
Were you guys deceived again?
Are you telling the truth?
You're all about to die, and he still hasn't shown up.  That's all the proof you need.
Where's the hero?
Well?  Where?
But he said he'd save us.
He's probably somewhere laughing at how stupid you all are.
You guys are way too trusting.
And if this isn't some dream you made up, and he really did say he'd save everyone,
then he's the kind of guy who
runs away in the face of danger.
Just throw away all hope!
I hate to say it, but he's mostly right.
You guys run away, too.  Good luck.
Th-That can't be...
Shut up.
Shut up!
Usoland would never tell a lie!
Usoland is...
I'm Norland's descendant!
Amazing!
No matter what, Usoland will definitely save us.
That's what he told us!
That's right.
That's right!  That's right!  That's right!
He promised us.
A hero would never deceive us!
If you keep besmirching Usoland's name,
you'll regret it.
You should prepare yourselves.
When Usoland comes, you won't-
What a funny scream.
The Tontattans have such a funny death cry.
Leo!
That's right.  It's as Leo says.
Usoland... Usoland will complete Operation SOP.
That's right.
You should feel sorry for yourselves, not us!  Usoland will-
Just give up already!
A hero will always show up when you're in trouble.
Then hurry up and call him, your hero.
How cruel is he?!
Stop it, just stop, please stop!
Just give it a rest already!
Usoland!
Usoland...
Usopp!
I'm so glad.
Just how long are you gonna believe in me, you idiotic gnomes?!
It's just as he said, it was all a lie.
I'm not a legendary hero, and Usoland isn't my name.
I'm the sniper from the Straw Hat Pirates, the crew that will even scare crying children to silence!
My name is Usopp!
I'm a pirate!
Th-The Straw Hat Pirates?
Why are they down here?
Why...
Why would you say that?
You may be a pirate, but you're a good guy right?
I told you, no!
A pirate is a pirate!
Don't make me keep repeating myself!
I was lying to you all!
And you just kept believing me!
So you came all the way here just to say it was a lie?
If I didn't, these guys would keep waiting until they died.
If that happened, I could never live with myself.
Since they insist on believing in me so much,
I'll have to do the cool thing and risk my life to save them!
My name is Usopp!
Remember it well, Tontattans!
If I die, then build me a statue beside Norland's!
I'm about to become your legendary hero!
Usopp!
Usopp, from the Straw Hat Pirates.
Is he gonna be the one to save us?
How desperate.
It's all or nothing!
Kill him.
Of course.
Sure-Kill Green Star: Platanus...
...Shuriken!
How's that, you monster?!
I'm the legendary hero, the Straw Hat Pirates' sniper, Captain Usopp!
Usoland!
It's Usopp!
I said it's Usopp!
The legendary hero, Usoland!
Long ago, when King Riku appeared before a beast of a man, a miraculous story begun.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Fateful Encounter
Kyros and King Riku
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!