Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Two years have passed since the great war at Marineford.
Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates have all been training on their own.
Now, in order to proceed to the next stage,
the New World, they've had the Sunny coated
and they are headed for Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
Right, that's good.
This is the instant Flutter Kick Coating!
An instant diving suit!
Wait!
You need to keep the lifelines attached!
Here comes another arm!
Are you alright?!
They're good!
Right, now it's my turn!
Color of Arms - Vulcanization
What is that?!
He didn't do that before!
The ocean is... sapping my strength.
Damn octopus, are you trying to stop him
before he lands a single hit?
Sanji-san left his soap bubble!
Never mind that!  Look at his speed!
He's like a fishman!  Amazing!
Running!  Running!
I spent two years running from revolting creatures.
Compared to them,
this thing barely even qualifies as a monster.
It's almost cute.
I'm almost out of breath.
Three Sword Style Secret Technique
Crossing of Six Paths
The demon that roams the seas... You're soft!
Now that I think about it, I should be grateful.
These past two years I've fought every single day...
in order to surpass him.
I can become even stronger!
A-Amazing...
I couldn't even see his swordplay!
You didn't need to do that!
Did you say something, number seven?
I'm gonna fillet you!
Bring it on!
Hey, Zoro, Sanji!  You're destroying all of its arms!
He knocked it out!
Just how strong has he become?!
Even though we're underwater!
Huh?  There's something there!
Huh?
A shark?
Is that shark wearing clothes?
That's a pretty big shark.
What?
Is it thanking us for saving it?
Quite a polite shark, huh?
What's going on?
We're being pulled into the current!
Luffy, we have to get back to the Sunny!
Got it!
They've been sucked into the downflow!
Crap, after them!
We have to stay together!
Right!
I don't wanna die here!
Stop messing around!
Hmm?  That guy's still here?
Why are you so calm?!
My eyes are spinning!  Though I have no eyes.
Keep the yard level!  Steer the ship to the left!
We're going to crash into the continental shelf!
Alright!
If we're not careful, the ship will be destroyed!
Whaaaat?!
Don't get thrown off!
Bring the ship to the center of the current!
Roger that!
We're going so fast!
This is fun!
Usopp.
Ow, that hurts.
So I'm still alive?
Huh?
What's wrong?  Why the long faces?
I swear, you really are helpless without me.
It's so cold here!
We can't find Luffy and the others.  It looks like we got separated.
What?!
I just hope they haven't been
torn to pieces by a sea monster.
Your imagination is too scary.
Still, we won't find them in this darkness,
no matter how hard we look.
I do not like the darkness...
Do any of you feel like we're being watched?
We're probably at least
seven thousand meters down by now.
At this depth, the pressure would even flatten the Shark Submerge like a pancake.
Are we near Fishman Island?
Maybe they're already there?
I think Caimie-chan said
it's ten thousand meters beneath the surface.
We still have to dive another three thousand meters?!
They're only protected by those small soap bubbles.
Even if they're still alive, they'll run out of air soon!
This is why I told them to keep the lifelines attached!
Crying about it won't get us anywhere.
Let's look for them.  I have a light function installed.
Huh?!
Do you mean your eyes?!
Why would you install lights there?!
Oh, my.
Huge!
Scary!
You're kidding!
We've...
gotta get out of here!
Anyway, keep your eyes open!
I'm sure they're searching for us too.
Luffy!  Zoro!  Sanji!
Where did you go?
Come back!
Luffy-san!  Zoro-san!  Sanji-san!
Damn... The ocean floor is way too big!
The range of the Sunny Eyes
isn't all that long to begin with.
How disheartening.
This darkness makes it even more depressing.
This isn't getting us anywhere.
What should we do?
We can't slow the ship down,
so make sure you don't miss anything.
I'm sure we'll find some trace of them.
Let's search!
Yeah!
A jellyfish!  There's a huge jellyfish above us!
It's huge!
It really is massive!
It's sparkling!  It looks like a starry night sky!
It's so beautiful.
Its hand entered!
D-Does it want to be friends with me?
You mustn't touch it, Chopper!
It's probably poisonous!
Huh?!
Not good!  Time for a small...
What?!
The jellyfish was eaten!
The ship seems to have lost some air.
It's better than being eaten, isn't it?
The Coup de Burst is a weapon that uses large amounts of air.
However, we're underwater.  Our air is limited!
If we shoot air out, the soap bubble shrinks!
I understand.  But knowing that
the bubble is getting smaller makes me nervous.
The fish that attacked the jellyfish went belly up!
Neurotoxin, as I suspected.
The deep sea is so scary!  And dark.
And there are so many fish
with white eyes.  They're creepy!
The deep sea is a world of darkness.  Thus,
the eyes of many creatures here have degenerated.
Oh, so they can't see very well?
Stupid!  Try to come over here!
On the other hand,
some creatures will have highly evolved eyes.
What?  How can I see with no eyes, you ask?
Ladies and gentlemen, do you wish to know?
The answer is...
It's a secret!
What are you doing over there, all by yourself?
No need to worry.  I am quite used to solitude.
Hey!  Take this search more seriously!
Why did you hit me as well?
Luffy, Zoro, Sanji!
Where did you go?
Hmm?
These ropes...
Everyone?
Huh?
Do you know what happened to that pirate fellow?
Oh yeah, he was here too.
I'd completely forgotten.
Where did he go?
I haven't seen him since we reached the deep sea.
Maybe he got thrown off in the downflow?
That could be.
His hands and legs were bound, after all.
He couldn't hold on to anything.
No, you see...
It seems his ropes came off.  Look.
T-Then he's still onboard?
Where could he be?!
He could be lurking inside the ship somewhere.
Oh, no.
If you want me to lurk around then maybe I should.
Like in the ladies' quarters?
Damn... So we can't even
drop our guard on our ship?
Don't worry.  He's not all that strong, anyway.
This is great!
The monster trio who fought the Kraken
have gone missing!
They're dead for sure after getting lost down here in such small bubbles!
It's a shame I couldn't take Straw Hat's head, but...
as long as I collect
the heads of everyone on this ship,
that should be more than enough proof
that Straw Hat is dead!
However, don't be hasty, Caribou!
You mustn't act too quickly!
If you kill them now there will be nobody to sail the ship.
These guys are skilled at navigating the sea.
But the moment when we reach Fishman Island...
will be their last!
Here he is!
Dammit!
Now we'll be safe.
I screwed up!
How did he get inside this small barrel?
We were careless.  We might have been in trouble
if this guy wasn't such an idiot.
His body lost its form and became a muddy substance.
Muddy?
Yeah, he's a Devil Fruit user, no doubt about it.
What's more, he's a Logia.
He took our attacks on purpose earlier, and pretended he'd been captured.
Hey!  Please let me out, master!
Master with the speedo!  I'll be your servant!
What is it, Chopper?
I don't know, it got really hot all of a sudden.
I can't handle heat.
So hot!  What's going on?!
Huh, what's this?  Smoke?
It's blocking our view!
Smoke from the ocean floor?  How?
This is...
Could it be?!
Hydrothermal deposits!
Huh?
This is a field of underwater volcanoes!
What?!
Look!  You can see that they were recently active.
We have to get out of here!
If one of them erupts, we'll die instantly!
Hot... Hot!
Something's coming after us!
A carnivorous tube worm!
We've got no choice!  We'll use a small...
Faceless crabs!
Another small...
I have no idea what that is!
Just a small...
The deep sea is scary!
There's no way Luffy and the others could survive down here.
I'm so sad.  We finally met after two years,
and now...
Don't be ridiculous!  They won't die that easily!
We used one Coup de Burst after another... There isn't much air left.
What's that?  It's so bright!
Maybe it's Fishman Island!
Maybe Luffy and the others are there!
We haven't dived down three thousand meters yet.
W-h-o a-r-e y-o-u?
Hey!  What are you sending those signals with?!
Can you see anything?
It's still too bright.
Oh no!
It's an angler!  It tricked us!
We've been caught by a deep sea hunter!
This is not good!
That was close!
It lured us right into its trap!  Can we get away?
What is it now?!
A-A human?!
What is that?!
A sea monster with the shape of a human.
Umibouzu: Enormous monsters that appear to shipwreck victims
An Umibouzu!
He's gonna capsize the ship!
The fish?!
Hey!  Angler!  You can't do that!
No eating ships!
How many times do I hafta tell ya?
Captain Vander Decken's gonna yell at ya!
D-Did he just save us?
L-Let's get out of here!  Who cares what happened?
Both of them are monsters!
What is that?!
Out of the darkness appears a legendary ghost ship,
the Flying Dutchman.
However, the crew has little time to be surprised...
before the underwater volcanoes erupt and
put them in even greater danger.
They dodge the debris and drop into a trench.
There they see scenery that
they never expected to find in the deep sea!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Underwater Volcano Eruption!
Drifting to Fishman Island
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!