Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew find themselves drawn into these events,
and things have escalated into an all-out war.
Surume!
You became his slave... to protect your siblings?
I see, of course you want to protect them.
Are they your younger siblings?  Or older?
Let me protect them too!
Did you forget?
We're friends, right?
Unbelievable... That is...
the ship of promise...
Noah!
W-Why...
Why is it moving?!
Who'd do this... and how?!
T-This is terrible!
What is it, Father?
Yes, this is strange, but why are you so upset?
It's just some old wreckage.  It isn't important.
You're wrong.
We mustn't let anything happen to that ship -jamon!
The ship must not be moved
before its time has come -jamon!
Captain Hody!
He took so many Energy Steroids
that he turned into a monster, but still...
N-No, look!
Straw Hat!
He sure is tough.
Shirahoshi is over here!
Right here!
Umm... What are you all...
We can't let you live or we're going to be in trouble!
Time to die!
Surume!
Surume-sama, you are so strong!
Take care of Weak-hoshi for me!
Straw Hat...
Do you have any idea what Fishman Karate can do?!
He took his head right off!
Alright!  And it only took one hit!
That won't work on me...
'cause I'm rubber!
Compared to Jinbe's attacks, that didn't even itch!
That's right!  It's because you rely on fake power!
Head Armament
Steel Shell Squadron!
You fool!  Your head's gonna shatter!
Bell
Steel lost to his head!
None of them are hitting?!
Does he know where every single one is going?!
You're amazing, Luffy-sama!
That's the Haki of Perception!
Captain Hody!
Luffy-sama... How strong are you?
Straw Hat Luffy is amazing!
So this is the power of a world-famous pirate?
What?
What is that?
Whaaat?!
T-That's...
the Noah, from the Fishman District!
Why is the Noah above Fishman Island?!
It's clearly falling toward the plaza!
It's going to break the bubble around the island!
Fishman Island will be destroyed without the bubble!
We'll all be washed away!
What's that?!
Noah?!
It's super-huge!
If that ship hits us, the entire island will be crushed!
Who's steering it?!
No, the Noah shouldn't even have the power to move!
What is that?!
It's huge!
I don't know what's happening, but we're doomed!
I wonder, if we're all crushed at the same time...
will the ocean become red?
Don't jinx us by saying such horrible things!
Evacuate!
Flee to the waters outside the island!
E-Everyone...
What is that?
Owie... I slipped.
You're... Decken's subordinate, Wadatsumi!
Cap'n Vander Decken!
I fell off!
Pwease stop da ship!
I don' wanna die!
Decken?!  What is going on?!
Captain Hody!
Are you alright?!
Uh, is this... part of the plan?!
It looks like Decken is moving that ship!
Be quiet, you useless worms!
Damn Straw Hat...
Huh?  How is he still standing?
I even attacked him using the Color of Arms.
Decken, is it?  That insane pirate!
This wasn't part of the plan!
Shirahoshi!
Accept... my love!
Can you hear me, Shirahoshi?!
That's...
Princess Shirahoshi!
Don't tell me...
Decken threw the Noah at her,
just like all those letters and axes?!
I've thought of you for ten years, ever since you were a little kid!
Even if you searched the whole world, you'd never find anyone else who loves you as much as I do!
My love.
My love!  My love!
My love!
Why won't you accept it?!
Once I send something flying with my Mato Mato power...
it will not stop until it reaches its target
or crashes into something else!
The giant ship, Noah... This is my love!
Accept it!
And then die, along with all of Fishman Island,
Shirahoshi!
Cap'n Decken!  What 'bout me?!
Wadatsumi?
It's no longer possible to save you!
You will become a sacrifice for the death
of Shirahoshi, just like the rest of Fishman Island!
No way!
We're done for!  The bubble won't hold!
This is the end!
Hey, where'd Princess Shirahoshi go?
She's gone!
What?  The Princess!  Princess Shirahoshi!
What?  Shirahoshi disappeared?!
I-Impossible!
I'm up here!
Hey!
Princess Shirahoshi!
When did she...
Weak-hoshi.
Mermaid Princess?!
Shirahoshi!  What is she doing up there?!
Basically, that ship is flying at Shirahoshi!
Huh?!  Then that means...
The woman I love!
M-My life is your target, is it not?!
If you just want to take my life...
then the people of Ryuuguu Kingdom should not be caught up in it.
Please, leave them alone!
I am right here!
Princess!  Shirahoshi-sama!
Noah is...
Noah is changing course!
It's heading for Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Shirahoshi...
You can't do that... Shirahoshi-chan.
So basically, that insane Decken-guy...
was planning to crush the whole island, and us with it.
He betrayed me!
Ah, she's going to sacrifice herself for us!
Isn't there anything we can do to help her?
Oh, how...
Oh, how completely beautiful you are, Shirahoshi!  Even your heart shines with it!
You're trying to avert this disaster
and save your country all by yourself, Shirahoshi?
Shirahoshi!
Shira... hoshi.
You truly are
worthy of becoming Vander Decken the Ninth's wife!
Die at the height of your beauty, and live on forever in my heart!
Shirahoshi!
Your Highness!
How awful!
Stop it!  Please run away, Your Highness!
That Weak-hoshi...
Even after I told her to stay close to me!
Straw Hat is...
Captain Hody!
H-Huh?  Hody-san isn't here!
Look up in the sky!  There he is!
Under Noah?!
You're completely insane, Vander Decken.
However, this is a great trump card!
That bastard... How dare he harm Shirahoshi-chan?!
Sanji, wait!
I'll jump up there!  You take care of the plaza!
Got it!
But anyway Luffy, the ship is underwater!
Do you think there's water inside the ship too, Jinbe?
I'm not sure, but Decken is a Devil Fruit user...
so we can assume that there must be air in there somewhere since he can make the ship move.
If you're going to go, take this.
It's a coral that creates a bubble.
Okay!
Okay, I leave my beloved Shirahoshi-chan to you!
I'm gonna fling you, Luffy!
Do it!
Luffy chases after Shirahoshi,
but he's at a disadvantage fighting underwater...
and struggles against Hody's overwhelming power!
Next time, on One Piece:
Hurry, Luffy!
Shirahoshi's Absolute Despair.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!