Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and have invaded Dress Rosa.
Luffy joined a battle tournament where the prize was the Mera Mera Fruit,
and has made it through the preliminary round.
Now he's heading toward the palace to rescue Law from Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, at the Colosseum,
the battle tournament finals are about to begin.
Who is he?
He definitely isn't Lucy.
This is Rampart Tower B-2, in front of the dining hall.
There's no doubt about it, the intruder is Straw Hat Luffy!
The Pirate Hunter, Zoro!
And V-Violet-sama!
T-There's also one more.
Lucy's on fire!
Straw Hat Luffy is the intruder?!
Then who the hell is the guy in the Colosseum right now?!
Just what is going on?!
The Moving Castle!
Top Commander Pica Appears!
Where's Mingo?!
Fire!
Are you unharmed, little one?
Thank you.
Kin'emon, you look after her.
I cannot do that!
I must find this Toys' House place where my friend Kanjuurou is!
I have to get there too, to help with Operation SOP!
What?!  Is that so?
Zoro-dono.  We will head for the Toys' House together.
Suit yourselves.
That said, where can I find the Toys' House?
It's beneath us.  So...
What?  It was beneath us all along?
You should probably take those stairs.
Stairs?
Very well, then I am off.
Get inside, and make sure you do not fall out again.
Hey, wait!
Luffy-dono.  Zoro-dono.  Ninja-woman.
I must leave you for now.
Now, if you'll excuse me!
Royal Palace Rampart
Tower B-1
Straw Hat Luffy has entered Rampart Tower B-1!
Which way?
Left.
There's nobody here.  Just you wait, Mingo!
The guards can't keep up with us.
W-What's going on?
There's something in the wall.
A face?!
What is that?!
A stone monster?!
Oh no!  It's Pica!
It's huge!  What is that thing?!
Be careful!  He's one of the Family's top commanders!
That stone monster?
Ishi: Stone
Pica ate the Ishi Ishi Fruit and gained the power to merge with stone!
A stone-merging man?
He doesn't seem human at all.
Are you human?
Hey, I'm talking to you!  Say something!
Can't you speak?
If that thing hits us, we'll be crushed!
Dammit!  We can't move on like this!
I don't care if you're a top commander or whatever!
I'm going to go beat up Mingo!
Get outta the way!
Gomu Gomu no...
Jet Gatling!
Alright, I got him.  Let's go.
That was really anti-climactic.
You don't know when to give up!
It won't be that easy to defeat a top commander.
So he's not just a stone man.
He can merge with any stone he touches.
Meaning, that since this palace is made of stone,
he can control the entire thing!
The walls!
Toys' House
Bring it on, Navy!
Watch out -in!
Hey, hold it Navy!
You've got some nerve, entering the Family's turf wearing shoes!
Our target is Cyborg Franky from the Straw Hat Pirates!
If you don't want to get caught in the crossfire, then move!
You Navy-punks have no right to order me around!
He's brushing his teeth with shoe brushes!
Two of them!
Señor is a commander in the Donquixote Family!
He's really strong!
It's not about being strong or weak.
This is a matter of pride!
Can it, all of you!
Please scold us some more, Señor!
Commander or not, if you defy the Navy, then...
Don't hurt him.
Isshou-san and Doflamingo have reached an agreement about the Navy's involvement.
I don't like this, but if the young master has approved of it...
Señor!
Why are you relaxing?!
I was super-bored.
Please listen to my Pirate Blues!
Like hell!
Men!  We will now resume our attack!
We're giving up on capturing Cyborg Franky alive!
I'm super-ready when you are!
He's swimming...
...in the ground!
Señor, you've done well.
Now take a well-deserved rest.
I've worked up a sweat.
For now, I guess I'll just see what the Navy's gonna do.
He's so hard-boiled!
I didn't expect the Navy to butt into this.
But it's fine by me, I like it flashy!
Weapons Left!
And...
Franky...
Rocket Launcher!
Don't falter!  Shoot him!
That guy's standing firm against all those troops.
He's got guts.
Use the newly-developed cannonballs!
Sir!
Newly-developed cannonballs?  Sounds cool.
Fire!
Cyborg Franky is on fire!
We did it!
His body might be metal, but no one can withstand that heat.
He'll just melt to a puddle!
It's hopeless...
Just kidding!
Whaaat?!
I can't have you underestimating me.
Did you really think you could defeat me with those toys?
Super!
Dammit!
Wait, this won't do!
Now which style to choose?
Please wait at least three seconds.
Maybe this?
Nah...
Not this either.
Yeah, it's gotta be this.
He's just fooling around!
I won't run or hide!
Now...
let's make some noise, Navy!
Fire!
Underground trade port
Usopp's group
Toys keep coming out.
This is clear proof that Sugar is in the Commanders' Tower.
What are those tubes for?
Right in the middle of that tower lies the commanders' private lift.
As for the pipes extending all around it,
big humans and broken toys are sent in through those.
There are numerous entrances to the scrapyard all throughout Dress Rosa,
Get dropped into any one of them,
and you'll reach the scrapyard, located right below the Commanders' Tower.
Help!
Nooo!
I'm fed up with this!  First a mountain of garbage, now this?
Where am I?
You're the pirate Cavendish, right?
Yes, I am.
Then we will begin our checkup.
Checkup?  There's nothing wrong with m-
Huh?  What's going on?
Seriously, what is going on?!
And what is this slimy stuff?
I thought it was weird that they sent me to the medical room when I wasn't injured.
Betabeta: Sticky
It's not "slimy stuff"!  It's "Beta Beta"!
Get back!  Who the hell are you?!
This is the Commanders' Tower.
Inside the Commanders' Tower
But this factory where toys are born...
also has another name.
Sugar!  What is that other name?
The Commanders' Tower.
No!
Oh, snot came out!  My nose is running!
Gross.  Die.
I won't die!  I won't listen to a little kid like you!
Donquixote Family Top Commander
Trébol ♣ (Ate the Beta Beta Fruit)
Child, I can't move!  Please get this sticky fluid off me!
Time to make the contract.
Do not harm humans.
Obey the Family's orders.
W-What are you talking about?
Hey, what's wrong with my body?
Please put me back to-
Be quiet and get to work!
What?  I can't speak!
Why can't I resist his commands?!
Obey the Family's orders.
Contract?!
Nobody remembers you anymore.
Even I've forgotten who you were.
You will work for Doffy or fight for him until you die!
What is going on?!  I've been turned into a toy!
Exit through that door, and you'll be at the port.
Ah, a new worker!  Your station will be...
Where am I?!
Don't drop the cargo!
...right here.  Now, get to work!
I'm a pirate!  This is just a bad dream.  Wake up, me!
Get moving!
No, I don't want to work!
I refuse to spend the rest of my life working with these creepy toys!
So this was where they smuggled the weapons from?
But I can't resist them!  I can't do anything!
I can't believe they had a port underground.
I have to contact the others...
Koala is waiting for my report!
Is there no way for me to move freely?!
Damn you, Doflamingo!  I am the king of Prodence!
I'll be a toy for the rest of my life?  You can't be serious!
Somebody, help!
So that's Trébol and Sugar.
She really is a kid.
That's right.
She loves grapes.  She's always eating them.
What about it?
That's essential to our plan.
Look at this!
This is a lump of the world's spiciest seasoning, tatababasco!
We've disguised it as a grape!
And you're giving that to Sugar?
I'm going to sneak it into her basket.
We've tested it on fifty Tontattans.
Every single one of them fainted, and twenty-eight nearly died!
You've tested it?
The plan is flawless!  We just have to make her eat this.
Alright!  Go, Leo!
I will watch over you!
That's so reassuring.
If a panic breaks out... I'm outta here.
Hang in there, Leo!
Yeah!
Be quiet, you guys!
Be careful of Trébol!
Be careful!
You're way too loud!
No problem.
All of you, prepare yourselves!
Once Sugar screams out...
all the toys in this country will turn back into big humans!
All the forgotten memories will come back!
With all his evil deeds exposed...
the pirate Doflamingo's...
true nature will be revealed!
I'm going.  We will save our friends!
Yeah!
I'm telling you to be quiet!
We will reclaim King Riku's country!
Yeah!
Oh come on!
Shut up already!
The struggle for the Mera Mera Fruit continues.
The Blackbeard Pirates' Burgess's special move, Wave Motion Elbow
and Lucy's devastating dragon power collide.
The true strength of the man who inherits Ace's will is now revealed!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Dragon's Claw Bursts!
Lucy's Menacing Strike!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Dragon's Claw Bursts!
Lucy's Menacing Strike!