It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and came to Marineford...
to save his brother Ace, who is about to be executed.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates have been advancing on the execution platform.
At last, they've made it past the defensive walls...
and broken into the plaza.
During the Navy's fierce attack, Luffy got backup from the Whitebeard Pirates...
and ran toward Ace.
Finally...
Finally!
I finally made it!
Luffy!
You're one hell of a guy...
Fire!  Blast the execution platform and everything with it!
There's a tunnel of fire coming out of the smoke!
You never change, Luffy.
Never listening to a single word I say.
Always doing the dumbest things.
Ace!
F-Fire Fist Ace...
is free!
Alright!  You did it, Straw Hat!
You got Ace back!
It's been one crazy thing after another since he came to Impel Down...
He really is...
One hell of a guy!
Thank goodness!
You've finally managed to fulfill your wish!
Luffy...
Now, if you can just get out of here safely...
We can finally get married!
Look, Coby!
That Straw Hat, he really did it!
Luffy-san really is amazing...
Don't get thrown back!
Resume fire immediately!
Aim for their trajectory!
Yes, Sir!
Stay sharp, Luffy!
Let's take 'em all out!
Right!
A-Are you crazy?!
They're strong!  Be careful!
Can you fight, Luffy?
Of course I can!
Ace-san!  Luffy-kun!
Got it?  Fire Fist Ace is made of fire!  He is a Logia Type!
I never even dreamed that the day would come...
when I would get saved by you.
Thanks, Luffy.
It's all because that old Whitebeard guy and his men helped me out.
Don't think you're safe just yet!
This is your execution stand!
Now!  Take him down!
He's my little brother.
I'd like you to back off of him.
Die!
Get moving, Luffy!
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
Yeah!
They've sure got spirit...
Open an escape route for them!
Yeah!
Don't let them get away!
Execute Fire Fist and Straw Hat!
You've gotten strong, Luffy.
Someday, I'll even surpass you!
Well then, seems I still need to protect you for the time being.
You'll surpass him someday... How could you, when there's no tomorrow for you?
There's no way you'll ever escape from here, is there?
Admiral Kuzan!
He's...
Stand back, Luffy.
Aokiji-san's ice...
Vanished in an instant!
He's our Second Division Commander!
Of course he can handle that!
Amazing...
Those brothers are unbelievable...
This is no time to admire them, you dumbasses!
Hurry up and get the Surveillance Snail to cooperate with us!
Oh, uh, sure!
Now, then... How long can you keep running?
The main event starts now, Straw Hat.
Well, anyway, if I just blend into the chaos and kill Whitebeard, who's way overdue for his death already,
I will be able to become one of the Four Emperors!
Oh!  Such confidence!  Such composure!
I'd expect no less from our Captain Buggy!
Mister Two...
Somehow, I managed to carry out your wishes...
Well then, I need to hurry up and escape from here too...
Whose subordinate is this traitor?!
No!  He's one of the prisoners!
Oh, crap!
Fleet Admiral!
What a disgrace...
How could I have...
Just let them go.  It'll be more fun that way.
Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way we can beat someone who can resist the Admiral's powers!
Don't lose focus!
Admiral Sakazuki!
I will not let them get away from here!
Don't be afraid!  Take them on!
W-What is it now?!
Everyone, get out of the way!  The enemy's ship has started to move!
Don't get any closer!  It's running wild!
Hey!  Who's steering that thing?!
Squardo!
It's the Whirl Spider Pirates!
Old Man!  Guys!  Run away!
We'll stay on the battlefield and cover you!
Yeah!
Those fools...
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Don't be a fool, Squardo!
Are you planning to die?!
Well, of course...
I did something terrible to the Old Man...
Even if this won't atone for my sins...
I'd never be at peace if I didn't do this!
Sorry, you guys...
I dragged you into this...
It's alright, Captain.
Don't worry about it.
We followed you because we wanted to!
We'll decide for ourselves where we're gonna die!
Captain!  We will follow you!
Thanks...
Take Ace with you, and flee!
Squardo!
What an idiot.
That Squardo...
What a showy way of doing things...
Hey!  Hurry and get these handcuffs off me!
Men!  Are you ready?!
Charge!
Old Man...
What was that?
The ship stopped moving!
Old Man!
With just one arm...
He stopped the whole ship!
Don't you realize how painful it is for a father to see his own child die before him?!
Don't you, Squardo?!
Don't get ahead of yourself, now!
I'm not so weak as to die from your stab!
But everyone dies someday!
We've completed our objective here.
We no longer have any business here!
Old Man!
Listen close, Whitebeard Pirates!
The order I am about to give, will be my final captain's order!
Final?!  Wait, Old Man! I don't want to hear anything so ominous!
I don't wanna hear that!
We're going back to the New World together, aren't we?!
Old Man!
You and I will be parting here!
All of you, make sure you survive,
and reunite with each other in the New World!
O-Old Man!
Do you plan to die here?!
I am the one at the top of this era...
There is no ship to carry me in the new era!
Go, my men!
Whitebeard!
No way!  Old Man!
It's the captain's orders!  Get going!
Oldtimer!
Old Man!
Don't turn back.
The era is changing!
It all started on that sea...
This is amazing!
Hey!  Why're you sitting over there by yourself?
Come over here!  We've got plenty of treasure here!
Never mind him.
Huh?  "Never mind"?  This loot belongs to him too, you know...
I said never mind.  He's not interested in the loot.
Now, that's odd!  A pirate who doesn't care about treasure?
What do you want, then?
Hey, Newgate!
I've had quite a long journey...
Now let's settle this...
Navy!
The pirates retreat in sadness after they hear Whitebeard's final order.
Ace stops without thinking when he hears Akainu's cruel words to Whitebeard as he pursues the crew.
Abandoning his friends, Ace leaps forward, as Akainu's fist approaches him!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Power That Burns Even Fire
Akainu's Fierce Assault
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!