Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Two years have passed since the great war at Marineford.
Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates have all been training on their own,
and then they returned to their
promised meeting place at the Sabaody Archipelago.
Now, in order to proceed to their next stage, the New World,
they are headed for Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
Hey, you guys!  Come and look at this!
Fishman Island!
It's huge!
It's covered in an enormous bubble!  And there are clouds on the inside?
Maybe there's air in there!
If that's Fishman Island, does that mean we're ten thousand meters below the surface?
We did it!  We're here!
Hey, what's with those guys?!
Who are they?!
It's a herd of sea monsters!
We're done for!  And we made it so far!
These sea monsters are so...
cool!
Someone's riding them!
Why are you letting those humans boss you around...
Kraken?
What are you doing, Surume?!  Carry us for the last stretch too!
This isn't the time for that!  Hold on!
Don't get thrown off the ship!
My eyes are spinning!
Mine are too!
Though I do not have eyes that can spin!
W-We've ended up right in the middle
of the herd of sea beasts!
You're the Straw Hat Crew, aren't you?
W-Who are you?!  How do you know about us?!
Of course I know about you.
You're the pirates who took out Arlong's crew.
If that's all you'd done,
our reaction would be obvious.
But of all things, two years ago you defended Hachi-san, a former member of Arlong's crew...
and from what I hear, you even beat up
one of those despicable Celestial Dragons!
Acts worthy of Fisher Tiger,
the hero of Fishman Island who we all admire!
Fisher... Tiger?
I can't decide what to do with you.
Hey, tell me...
Are you friends, or foes?
I'll let you choose...
Will you join us, the New Fishman Pirates?
Or will you refuse us?
If you say no, we'll sink you right here and now.
What?!
Franky, refill the fuel.
Huh?  What are you planning?
There's no way Luffy and the others will do what those guys say.
Even so, we're ten thousand meters underwater.
We can't even fight back down here.  There's no chance of winning.
So let's flee!
We'll use up all the air left on the ship in one last Coup de Burst to charge straight toward the island!
Are you serious?!
It's either that, or we came all this way just to die.
True.  I can't see any other way to survive this.
Right!  I'll go fill up the fuel tanks!
Franky!  You steer the ship!
You got it!  I'll handle it superbly!
They've started scurrying around frantically.  Think they're planning something?
Whatever they do will be pointless.
They're just humans, after all.
So, will you become our underling, Straw Hat Luffy?
No way.
Moron!
You refuse... You reject my invitation to join the New Fishman Pirates?!
In that case, you are enemies of the fishmen!  Just a group of sinful humans!
Idiots!
Why should I have to be your underling?!
Luffy!  You really shouldn't taunt them!
What a shame.
There's no way I can let you pass now.
You're gonna sink, right here!
Sea lion!
I've finished refilling the fuel!
Franky, we're good to go!
Roger that!
Sink them!
Wanna fight?!
Do it, Franky!
The Sunny is a lion too!
Let's settle the score some other day, sea lion!
Here goes...
The ship...
The air... is disappearing!
I'm gonna be flattened...
I cannot fill my lungs... Though I do not have lungs...
Endure it!  Until we break through to Fishman Island!
What is with that ship?!
We're breaking through!
Wait for me, my dear mermaids!
The coating came off!
It was absorbed by the giant bubble!
Look ahead!
What could that be?
This bubble has two layers!
A normal ship would plummet to the bottom
in this air-filled layer!
We're gonna use another Burst to get across!
Hold on tight!
Water-
What a strong current!
Help me...
I can't breathe.
We've got four Devil Fruit users here!
Stretch out... your hands!
Nami-san!  Robin-chan!
Dammit!  I can't fight the current!
What a reckless way to enter the country... They might have killed themselves.
Wanna follow them, Hammond?
We can't be sure if they're dead or alive.
We should go, just in case.
I don't want the Neptune Army to find them before we do.
But first, let's return to the Noah, and inform the boss about this.
We should let him know that Straw Hat,
the one who shattered Arlong-san's ambitions, is here!
See?
Look!
I saw it!
I didn't see it!
Didn't you see it?
So what if I saw it?
See, he moved!
He moved!
He didn't move!
Didn't he move?
So what if he moved?
Alright!  He's awake!
Luffy!
Where are we?
Luffy-chin!
I'm so glad you're alright!
How do you feel?
If it isn't Caimie!  It's been so long!
You're even cuter than you were
the last time I saw you, Caimie-chwan!
It's been a really long time.  I'm happy to see you again!
Caimie is here, so that means...
we've arrived at Fishman Island?
Yeah!  Apparently the mermaids saved us
when we were about to drown!
Indeed!  There's no point in hiding it.  We were all unconscious until now.
This is Caimie-chan's house.
Here, your hat.
Caimie's house, huh?
I'm sorry.  I was planning to meet up with you,
but I didn't think you were coming until next month.
Don't sweat it!  Where are the others?
Well... It appears we were separated.
I wonder if they're all okay?
Really?
Yeah... I tried to reach them for as long as I could, but we were the only ones dragged to the bottom.
Well, I'm sure they'll manage somehow.
I guess.
Bones won't be much good in the water,
but they've got Robo and Green with them.
I'm sure they're fine.
That's right!  They're fine, right?
I really want to see the others soon.
Ah, here.  You must be cold, right?
I made some soup, so drink up and get warm.
Ta-daah!  Cold seaweed soup!
It's delicious.
Cold... soup?
Cold soup won't warm you up at all!
What am I going to do?!
I got it wrong!
It's fine, Caimie-chan.
On the contrary, it does warm me up!
What do you mean "On the contrary"?
H-Hey!  Sanji, I want some too!
Your clothes are dry!
They're dry!
They're not dry yet!
Aren't they dry?
So what if they're dry?
You dried our clothes?
Thanks!
Thank you.
By the way, who are you guys?
Oh, they're my friends.
The Killifish Mermaid Quintuplets
I'm Ichika!
"One-ka", "Two-ka", "Three-ka", "Four-ka" and "Four-ka Two"
I'm Nika!
I'm Sanka!
I'm Yonka!
I'm Yonka Two!
Shouldn't that be Goka?!
"Five-ka"
They're fast swimmers, and quite well-informed too.
Oh, really?
This is the bottom of the Mermaid Bay.
We're in the ladies' dormitory of
the city's Mermaid Café, so I have lots of friends here.
L-L-L-Ladies' dormitory?!
Crap!
Caimie-chan!  W-W-What is this M-Mermaid Café you speak of?!
It's the café where I work as a waitress.
There are plenty of beautiful mermaids there.
Beautiful?!  Mermaids?!
Would you like some coffee?  Or perhaps...
Sanji's...
in big trouble!
Like hell!
He's back!
I...
I swore that nosebleeds wouldn't make me
lose consciousness while I was on Fishman Island!
So please... Haven't I suffered enough?
You sure are serious about this.
I know, let's go upstairs!
I'll introduce you to my friends!
It's a turtle!
"Sea Turtle Elevator", it says.
Turtle-chin.  Take us up, please.
These are the underwater Coral Apartments.
My room is on the lowest floor, since it's the cheapest.
The highest levels, where the sun shines,
are the most expensive.
Are you poor?
By the way, what about Hachi and Pappagg?
Hacchin got badly injured about a year ago.
Yeah.  He was protecting the Sunny
on the Sabaody Archipelago, wasn't he?
I heard that his injuries have more or less healed,
but Hacchin was originally a resident of
the Fishman District, so he's recovering there.
Fishman District?
It's kind of a scary place, but if you guys
are with me, I don't mind giving you a tour.
Let's go there after!
I have to meet Hachi and thank him, after all.
Sure, I got it.
Uh... And as for Pappagg...
He's a super-famous designer,
so he's got a huge mansion in Fishverly Hills, the most luxurious part of Fishman Island!
I'm going there to deliver clams for him today.
Why don't you come along?
Aren't you his owner?
Why don't you live together?
I don't really fit in there.
And the clams in these parts taste better anyway.
We're almost there!
Hey, what's that straw-like thing?
Oh, that's...
the Water Road, created by
the bubble craftsmen of the island.
The fishes and merfolk like me ride it.
Just watch!
She's fast!
Cool!
Caimie-chwan, where are you going?!
We've reached the surface!
Luffy-chin!
Look!  I can even swim through the sky!
That looks fun!
Huh?
Hey, wait!  More importantly,
there are clouds and a sky here in the deep sea!
You're right!  How does that work?
Hey, Caimie!
That was a woman's voice!
W-Where are you?
Everyone!
That's...
Are your friends alright now?
The pirates who drowned, I mean.
You're the ones who
didn't come through the entrance, right?
Hello.  You don't look too scary.
Illegal immigrants?  How wild!  I really like pirates.
It's almost like a fairy tale world!
The coral continent!  The mermaids' bay!
Sanji is sobbing?!
He's crying harder than he did when he left the Baratie.
I've finally found it!
This is my All Blue!
Are you really sure about that, Sanji?
I'll introduce them to you.
This is Luffy-chin, the captain!
Hey!  Nice to meetcha!
The crying one is Sanji-chin!
And this is Usopp-chin with the nose!
Nice to meet you!
Chopper-chin the raccoon dog!
I'm a reindeer!
What's wrong?  Why are you crying?
Welcome!  Let's dance together in the ocean!
Oh... I understand now.
There's no way such joy could exist.
I must have died today.
Negative!
Seriously, what happened to you during the past two years?!
This island is the paradise
you've always dreamed of, right?!
Sanji, you're so funny!
This is not funny!
I see.  So Straw Hat Luffy...
has finally come here?
Y-Yeah...
What should we do, boss?
Bring him here... to me.
As Sanji has fun with the mermaids, an unimaginable crisis occurs!
Next time, on One Piece:
Explosive Overexcitement!
Sanji in Mortal Peril!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!