Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy, and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
To defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and invaded Dress Rosa.
They managed to release the toys that were being used as slaves,
but Doflamingo used the bird cage
to trap all the citizens.
Then he put a bounty on twelve people, including Luffy.
Cien Fleur!
Spider Net!
Bartolomeo-san!  Hack-san!
We can climb up here!
I'll squash the lot of you!
Eight Impact Fist Secret Technique: Drilling Dragon...
King Punch!
...Drilling Nail!
Damn you!
Resumed Assault!
Luffy's Army VS Pica!
Pica-sama!
All flash and no bang.
There is nothing my drilling head cannot break!
Run!
This rubble is no match for my drilling head!
This is all thanks to him.
That was close!
Go, Ucy!  To the palace!
Don't get squashed!  I'm counting on you, Ucy!
Hey.  Didn't I tell you to stay away?
Get off Ucy's back!
Please don't be that way.
Please, Straw Hat-san!
Ucy, I'm counting on you!
Where did you go, Straw Hat?!
Hey!  Don't let them pass!
They're headed for the palace!
Get out of the way!
Move it!
Sai and Boo!
We must repay our debt for the glory of the Happou Navy!
I'll take you on!
Ideo, the King of Martial Arts?!
Don't let Straw Hat escape!
Don't get distracted.
Destructive Cannon!
Wanna stop me?  Then bring in some stronger men!
What's with these guys?
A-Admiral Orlumbus!
This is my path!
Admiral...
Hug!
Shoot Straw Hat!
You'll be executed next!
Why are they all ganging up on us?!
By executing you, my debt will be repaid!
Wait, Hairudin!
Kill Straw Hat, and you'll be richly rewarded!
I don't care about that pittance!
I was about to spend the rest of my life in disgrace as a toy...
when God Usopp saved me!
By repaying my debt to him, I will restore my pride!
I'll defeat Doflamingo!
No, I will!
I keep telling you, I'll get him!
Cabbage?!
I have remembered my true destiny.
A chance to kill a Warlord has presented itself to me.
This will put me ahead of all those despicable rookies!
The papers will write only of me for days!
I am fated to become a top star.
"Kyaa!  Cavendish-sama's face on the front page...
makes it look like a work of art!"
Is that so?  Why stop there?
We should fill the entire newspaper with articles on me!
"Great idea!  You're a genius!"
Will they even be able to capture my beauty?
After all, I shine brighter than the camera's flash.
Get lost!
Shut up.
Take care!
Now!  Fire!
Beautiful Sword!
Swan Lake!
We have to capture the outlaws and end this game!
Here they come!
Go to bed, kiddo!
What was that?!  Maybe I'll kill you first?
You guys are far too weak!
What?!
In a hundred years, you'd still be too weak to repay your debt!
I will take down Doflamingo!
No I will, and then I'll have all the popularity for myself!
Let me repay my debt!
I told you not to follow me!  You're bothering me!
Get back!
You get back!
Execution!
My path!
It's not your path!
It's my path to top stardom!
Get lost, already!
I will send Mingo flying!
What's up with this bunch?!
Look up!
Another punch is on the way!
Straw Hat!
He's so persistent!
Want another-?!
Drop it, you two!
He can restore his broken arms.
If you fight him without knowing his capabilities, you'll just waste your energy.
Then what should we do?
You're a strategist, aren't you?  Don't you have any ideas?
Hmm, in that case...
In that case...
Run!
And you call yourself a strategist?!  Come up with a better plan!
Hush!  Running is a perfectly viable strategy!
Get the hell out of here!
Damn!  This is nothing!
This is the end of you!  Get crushed and die!
Straw Hat!
We can't go straight forward.  Our only hope is to find a way around.
That guy is such a pain.
We can't reach the palace unless we stop him.
Hey, where did Straw Hat go?
I don't see him!
Was he crushed along with the buildings?!
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
What is that?
There he is!
This is a shortcut!  Alright!
He's on him?!
Go, Ucy!
What?!
Is he insane?!
Don't steal my thunder!
I don't believe it.
Now let's keep going to the palace!
Yeah!  Go, Ucy!
Hey.
Yes?
Don't you "Go!" me!
Get off!  You're too heavy for Ucy!
Oh, of course.
Pardon the late introduction.  I'm Jeet.
And the big guy behind me...
My name is Abdullah.
I didn't ask!
What's the issue?
Hey!
I told you to get off!
Straw Hat-san...
Straw Hat!
He's freaking pissed!
I won't let you get near Doffy!
His arm!
Straw Hat won't have anywhere to run as long as he's on his arm!
Straw Hat-san?!
Gear Third!
Color of Arms: Hardening!
He's huge!  We're done for!
There's nowhere to run!
Here comes his punch!
There's no way he can dodge in mid-air!
It'll hit him straight on!
Straw Hat!
Gomu Gomu no...
Grizzly Magnum!
He did it!
He smashed him?!
Pica-sama!
He did it!
It seems the high-ranking criminals from the Colosseum...
are now heading toward the palace with Straw Hat.
I see... It should be no surprise they're acting completely counter to our plans,
but I didn't expect them all to team up.
Hate to ask, but could you lend me that?
Vice-Admiral Bastille!  It's an emergency call!
I can't answer them all at once!
The soldiers Pica scattered won't stop calling!
Vice-Admiral Bastille!  It's an emergency call!
From who?!  Save it for later!
I-It's me.
I-Isshou-san?!
Sir!  What seems to be the problem?  Where are you now?
The criminals from the Colosseum appear to have teamed up.
They're wrecking things when the town is already in panic?  Could this get any worse?
Actually, this works better for us.
Wh-What do you mean?
Go provide backup for the vice admirals scattered throughout the city.
It's time for us to take action.
Meet me beneath the palace.
There he is!
Come out, Kyros!  If we don't capture you outlaws, this game won't end!
I have a family!  Please, let us catch you!
I'm still so far from the palace.
Somebody stop me!
I can't control my body!
Please, stop!
This is a nightmare.
Is he planning to repeat the tragedy from ten years ago?!
I will take back Dress Rosa!
The Former Royal Grounds
Everyone, we're almost at the top.
Everybody hurry!
We're almost there, Usoland!
Don't let me down, you guys.
We won't!
Are you alright, Rebecca?
Yes, Robin-san.
What's his deal?
I'm so happy!  Robin-senpai is helping me!
It's like a dream!
I'm going to climb all the way to the top!
Again, what is his deal?!
Amazing!  They're so soft!  I'm so happy!
Once I reach the top, I'll get to meet Luffy-senpai and Zoro-senpai too!
Kill all the outlaws!
Hurry!  They're coming for us!
It's a treasure mountain!
Rebecca!
One hundred million!
Nico Robin!
God Usopp!
Five hundred million!
All combined...
Seven hundred million Beli!
Get them!
Help!
Full speed ahead!
That one hundred million is mine!
Oh no!  Rebecca-sama!
Crap!
Slap!
What the hell is this?
I won't let you hurt her.
Strong and beautiful!
You're amazing, Robin-senpai!
Hey, Bartolomeo!  Put up a barrier already!
Robin-senpai, you're the best!
Listen to me!
Are you alright, Rebecca-sama?
Yes, thank you.
Now we're all at the top.
Robin-san, they're still coming after us.
Once we reach the top, we've won!
We have to take the net down once we're done with it.
You did it!
Pardon me.
Big Sis!
Pica-sama!
Awesome, Straw Hat-san!
Great job!
Alright, now let's hurry to the palace!
Yeah!
I wasn't talking to you!  I was talking to Ucy!
Luffy, the head you just smashed was nothing but stone!
Huh?!
We're just running on a statue now.
Did he disappear again?
Where is he?
He should be close.
He seems quite angry.
Huh?  Where?  Where is he?!
His real body is right ahead!
There's something there!
Huh?  That's the stone-guy?
First time I've seen him looking like a human being.
He's got a huge sword!
Dodge!
If you can't dodge him, then stop!
We won't make it!
The bull is flying?!
That voice is so funny!
Straw Hat!
Here he comes again!
We're going ahead!
What?
Sure!  I got this!
Amazing!
Get out of my way!
That's God's crew for you!
Zoro, I'm counting on you!
I'll go send Doflamingo flying!
Roger that, Captain.
I have unfinished business with Straw Hat.  Move!
My captain has no business with a pebble like you.
You'll have to settle for me, you oversized soprano.
Law begins to reveal his secret motives, and his deep ties with Doflamingo become clear!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Shocking Confession!
Law's Passionate Vow!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!