It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered,
and Luffy has broken into the world's largest prison, Impel Down,
to free his brother Ace, who is being held captive by the Navy.
There are men wanting to escape.
There is one man pursuing his brother.
There is one man chasing after them all.
This unprecedented escape from the depths of Hell...
continues to escalate beneath the surface of the sea.
Four and a half hours remain until Ace's execution.
Newkama Kenpo...
Now all four Demon Guards are here too!
B-B-B-B-Boss?!
S-Straw Hat?!
I-Is that Jinbei, of the Seven Warlords?!
Now that I'm done with the pervert boss, my new priority...
is to take care of YOU!
Magellan...!
No way...!
Iva-san and Inazuma...?!
Crab-chan...
Iva-chan...
Dammit!
You can't, Straw-chan!
We've got no choice but to run from Magellan!
Let go of me, Bon-chan!
I'm gonna kick his ass!
Are you sure?
I understand, but do you really want us to?
Yes.  Follow my orders, and do it quickly!
Yes, Sir!
Right, we have orders from Warden Magellan!
Gather up the rest of the guards for assistance!
Understood!
Oh no, so that's their plan?!
You almost died because of him, remember?!
But I'm still alive, aren't I?
Miracles are called that because they won't happen twice, you know!
You two, hurry to the next floor!
Luffy-kun!
We must hurry to the main entrance!
The situation has gotten worse...
We've been too focused on Magellan!
Right, I see.
We will implement the plan immediately.
Everyone, get ready! Man your positions!
Everyone with guns, help slow down Magellan!
Damn it!
Come on! Let's hurry and get going, Straw-chan!
They won't be able to stop him like that!
Oh crap! Here it comes!
Hurry, Luffy-kun!
Everyone, get out of the way!
Three!
He stopped Magellan's Hydra!
That optimism of yours makes me want to puke!
The second I let my guard down, I start thinking of you as a friend!
Sheesh...
I hate being indebted to others!
I've underestimated you, Brother Three!
I see.  Wax, huh?
That's right.
I ate the Doru Doru fruit.  I'm a candle-man.
Your poison will never be able to pass through my hard-as-steel wax wall!
So even rubbish like him has a use?
You never know how suitable some powers can be.
Now, hurry up and go!
I give up quickly, you know!
Three!
How irritating.
This is no time to be hesitating! I can't hold him back for long!
Right.  Then we'll just get going.
Let's go, men!
Were you always this good?!
Yeah, as long as I'm not on a hot floor...
Now all of you, hurry and get out!
I want to escape too, you know!
Luffy-kun.  We must hurry as well!
Oh, yeah, you said we're gonna steal a warship, right?
I did.
Then you and the others should just go on ahead.
I'll try stopping the poison guy in the meantime.
I mean, it'll be hard to steal one while he's chasing us.
Yes, that's true...
I've got an idea.
Does it stand a chance?
Yeah, leave it to me!
I understand.  Just don't do anything too reckless!
Right, Three! Let's fight together!
No, that's wrong! I have absolutely no intention of fighting!
My only intent was to guard us the best I could and run away!
Brother Three! We'll stay behind and help, too!
I'm telling you, I'm not that motivated!
Hey, I've got a favor to ask.
LISTEN TO WHAT I'M SAYING!
Hydra is coming again!
Can you do that?
It shouldn't be too hard.
Right.  I'm counting on you.
Very well!
Right! If I use this...
THIS IS JUST TOO COOL!
It's perfect!
Pay attention to what's in front of you!
What are you talking about, at a time like this?!
The tears just won't stop...!
Thanks for making me look so awesome...!
Like I care! Hurry up and fight him!
Straw Hat...
If nothing else, I'll praise your tenacity.
What happened to Iva-chan and Inazuma?!
Oh, you mean Ivankov?
I executed him, of course.
Don't worry.  I'll send you to see him shortly!
H-Here he comes!
Three!
Leave it to me!
No matter how many times you try, it won't work!
Alright! I can touch him now!
We've got the cannons ready over here!
The candle wall is shielding us!
Awesome! We hit him!
We can do this!
Alright!
Understand?! We've gotta slow them down here, at least a little bit!
Here they are! Fire!
Don't hesitate! Just charge straight through them!
We're almost there! Push for the surface!
Just a little further!
We can finally get out!
It didn't work?!
We're up against Magellan.
Let's give it all we've got!
What?!
Since we've made it this far, there's nobody left who can call themselves our enemies!
Don't let your guard down, amateur.
What?!
Outside these walls, there are at least ten warships.
There are about eight hundred marines on each ship.
I don't know what kind of plan they've got to intercept us,
but stealing one of the ships means we'll be making the other ships our enemies.
This is no time to take it easy.
I-I see...
That's not the only problem here.
There's no guards left!
Now we just have to get through this door!
We're here at last!
I've never forgotten this door...
The entrance to Impel Down!
All of us entered Hell through this door!
How many years has it been?
Are we really back? I still can't believe it!
I never thought I'd be escaping like this...
Right! Prepare your weapons, all of you!
Let's open the door!
Let's do this! Ready, push!
Finally, we'll see the light of the outside world!
Idiot! We're not out of this just yet!
The navy troops are waiting right outside this door...
If we win, we'll reach Heaven! If we lose, we'll go to Hell!
I see.  Now that you mention it, that's true.
Indeed.  But there's no way we can stop, having made it this far!
We must move forward, as far as we can go!
It's light!
We're getting out of here!
All of you, put some spirit into it!
I don't know how many troops are waiting for us, but we will beat 'em and return to sea!
Now, let's go, men!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Now, let's go, men!
Follow my lead!
What... is going on here?!
There aren't any warships around!
There's not a single warship for us to steal!
There isn't a single marine here, either!
No way... That means...
There's no way out, is there?!
What are we gonna do?
Is there nothing to do...
but wait helplessly for Magellan to arrive?
Damn it! You gotta be kidding me!
I see.  So the enemy wasn't as stupid as I thought.
The great Sea Kings are lurking on the ocean floor.
This Calm Belt here is truly Impel Down's greatest defense.
We finally made it all the way here, from the depths of Hell!
Damn! At this rate, we'll only fall right back into Hell!
We have no time to stand around crying!
Magellan ordered them to set sail just a few minutes ago.
Take a good look!
You can still barely see their shadows through the mist!
Y-You're right!
But how is being able to see them in the distance gonna help us?!
Yeah, no matter what we do...
Don't worry!
I'm here! You can leave this to me!
Seriously?!
He's freakishly strong!
HE BROKE THAT HUGE DOOR ON HIS OWN?!
I can't carry very many of you, but we can go steal a warship using this.
All those who have the resolve to fight, get on!
Steal a warship, he says...
C-Crocodile?!
Just you two, huh? Well, then...!
Wait!
Did you flashily forget about me?!
It should be obvious! I'll come with you!
Such bravery!
I'd expect no less from you, Captain Buggy!
Here's a Baby Snail Phone I picked up earlier.
Take it with you, just in case.
Sure!
Hey.  Hurry and get on.
Right, let's move out!
Very well! Let us hurry!
He's surging forward while carrying that heavy door!
Just what I'd expect from the captain of the Fishman Pirates!
I'm really getting excited here!
I never thought I'd see a Warlord in action!
Not only that, but our savior, Captain Buggy, is with them!
There's still hope for us!
You dumbasses!
It's obviously much safer with these Warlords than staying there and dreading Magellan!
Fools!
They're shooting at us!
So they spotted us.
He dodged it! He's fast!
Don't think he's just any fishman! He's the Sea Knight, Jinbei!
All ships, fire!
If we just sink Jinbei, they're all done for!
Warships coming in hard and fast!
I'll launch you onto the deck of one of the ships! Hold on tight!
What?! What did you say?!
You damn fish!
You listening, bastard?!
WHAT IS GOING ON?!
I see! He abandoned us and ran off on his own!
TRAITOR! TRAITOR! TRAITOR! TRAITOR!
Why did you even come along?
Jinbei! You bastard, where'd you go?!
They'll hit us if this keeps up!
Just calm down, you.
IT'S COMING THIS WAY!
WE'RE FLYING!
What's that water pillar?
It's almost like a living creature!
What could that be?!
I don't know.
But someone's riding it... It's Crocodile!
Here they are!
They've come to steal the ship!
Don't let them take it!
If we can push the Devil Fruit users into the ocean, we win!
After being beaten so badly last time, you still intend to fight me?!
I've already forgotten that!
In that case, I will make sure you never forget it again.
I will carve it into your very soul!
To give Jinbei the time he needs to steal a ship,
Luffy stands up to Magellan.
Cornered, Magellan unseals his strongest technique, capable of destroying Impel Down itself, and attacks!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Hopeless Situation for the Escapees
Forbidden Technique "Venom Demon"
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!