Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew found themselves
drawn into these events.  And now...
The Noah has already...
stopped!
Sea Kings?  Why?
Luffy-sama!  Your wounds have opened!
You're covered in blood!
W-Well... whatever.
As long as... the ship stopped.
I'm just glad... everyone's... safe.
Princess Shirahoshi.
We've waited a long time for you to be born.
Me?
This ship was built so we could pull it.
The tale of the ship has been passed down since the old times, so that we may do so.
Is that why the Noah is so big?!
Yes.
Once every couple hundred years,
our king is born into the body of one of the merfolk.
I wonder why?
Why indeed.
It's you.
Ever since you have been born,
you have been our Queen.
Honorable brother!
Yeah... Shirahoshi... She can't be...
She must be speaking with the Sea Kings!
I can't believe it!
What's going on, Border Police?
Why has the Noah stopped moving?
Right... Well you see, several Sea Kings
suddenly appeared outside of Fishman Island.
Almost as if to stop Luffy-san from destroying the Noah.
They came to protect it.
That's what it looks like, at least.
Perhaps the Noah is somehow important to them?
Neptune-sama!
The Sea Kings.
So, it's finally awakened.
The power that could destroy the world itself.
Look.  The bubble is being absorbed by the island.
Humans can't survive on the ocean floor.
Go to him.
Luffy-sama!
This is awful!
Let's go capture Hody and his men!
Right!  We have to hurry!
The Noah... Why is this ship so important?
Perhaps I was imagining it?
That human with the hat.  He heard our voices.
He couldn't have.
This happened before, a little while back.
Yes, it did.
Rayleigh, did you hear that voice?!
What are you talking about?
We're in the complete silence of the deep sea.
Who's there?!  Who's talking so far underwater?!
Hey!  Show yourself!
I wonder why.
Why indeed.
I wonder if Straw Hat and the others are alright.
They're strong, aren't they?
I'm sure they're alright.
Yeah.  Let's have faith in them, Hacchin.
You're right.
S-Sea Kings?!
T-They're carrying the Noah!
They're gonna eat us!
The ship is badly damaged.
Can it be fixed?  Can it still still serve its purpose?
Who knows?
To fix it, we'd need the skills of that clan...
but times have changed.
Can it be fixed?
Hopefully it will be fixed...
before the promised time comes.
This is Ryuuguu Palace!  Come in, Left Minister!
We have an urgent report for you!
What happened?
The mermaids who were kidnapped...
have been found inside of the castle!
What?!  So, are they alright?!
Yes.  They're a little dazed,
but they say they can
remember the face of their captor clearly!
Unfortunately, the treasure room
was found empty at the same time.
There isn't anything left at all.
Of course, this includes
the national treasure, the Tamate Box!
Your Majesty!
It appears someone has robbed us
while we were away!
Never mind some petty thief stealing treasure.
We could have lost the entire country
just now -jamon.
More importantly,
tell everybody that the girls are safe.
It might be a little late, but we must show that the Straw Hats are innocent.
We've done something terrible.
It's dangerous here!
Hurry up!
If they get us, we'll be killed!
Run!  We humans are outsiders!
Where are you going?!
Help us!
We can just fly above him using bubbles!
If anyone tries to use bubbles to escape...
I'll shoot them down!
Dammit!
Have mercy, Boss!  Let us go!
I was just scared of Hody and his bunch!
We can go, right?!
We don't have anything to do with
the conflict on this island!  We're just humans!
This island depends on tourism and
the money it gets from human pirate visitors, right?!
Let us go!
I never said that we'd kill you.
Wait for the Neptune Royal Family's judgment.
This is an announcement for all citizens.
The Straw Hat Pirates...
had no involvement in the kidnapping of the mermaids.
We admit that we did not check the facts properly.
We truly regret it,
and would like to offer our sincerest apologies.
The Straw Hats didn't kidnap them after all.
I knew they couldn't have done it all along!
Don't lie!
We all thought that they were the culprits.
N-No, we believed in them, right?
S-Sure.
Liars!
Quiet!
You're being unfair!
Yeah!
We must admit it.
We doubted them...
We doubted them because they were human!
That's how it's always been.
We've always seen the humans as...
Super...
Afro!
Franky-san, that is quite stylish!
Super, isn't it?
Hey, Chopper, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Hey!
Sorry.
Sheesh.
I get completely worn out
whenever I use the Monster Point,
and I can't even walk for two or three hours.
But... I can still treat your wounds.
Is everyone alright?
You aren't alright.
Everyone seems fine.
Robin-chan!
I used my ultimate technique too, so I'm completely worn out!
Let me rest on your lap!
Pwease!
Just sleep on the ground.
No, you!
Luffy.
It's the islanders!  Heeeey!
Princes!
Everyone!
It's the Princes!
I'm so glad they're safe!
Hody?!
Vander Decken?!
Father, you must have been worried.
I'm just glad you're safe -jamon.
You did well.
Thank you!
Everyone!  You can rest easy!
These men will no longer be allowed to run wild!
Now we can live without worrying!
I can't believe someone so scary
was in the Fishman District, so close to us.
C-Captain Hody!
He looks like a monster!
That's great!
Hey, isn't that...
He's back!
Luffy-san!
Hey, Luffy!
It's Straw Hat Luffy and Princess Shirahoshi!
Please, help him!
Luffy-sama won't stop bleeding!
Hey!  Luffy, hang in there!
Luffy!
Luffy-sama pushed himself too far for our sake.
Straw Hat.
This is awful!  I've got something to stop the bleeding in my backpack.
I'm counting on you, Robin.
Sure.
I'm really worried about our next fight, Doc!
Right, I'm ready!
I'll move you.
That's a really freaky doctor!
A little to the left... the left...
Can you save Luffy-sama?!
I can stop the bleeding,
but he's already lost so much blood.
He doesn't have enough left!
What?!
Luffy's the only one in the crew with blood type F.
That's terrible!
There must be someone else with that blood type
here in the plaza!
Anyone!
Hey!
Doesn't anybody have blood type F?!
He doesn't have enough blood!
Is nobody here willing to give him some?!
What, not even one?!
I... I've got F.
I have type F, but...
Daddy, you're type F, right?
Uh, well...
Oh, right!  This country has a law against donating blood to humans!
What kind of law is that?!  That's awful!
Please!  Luffy's in trouble!
My blood type is different, but it's still red!
Will that do?!
Uh, no.  I appreciate the sentiment, at least.
Princess Shirahoshi!
I know!  There are some human pirates here too!
Hey, please!  At this rate, Luffy...
Luffy will really die!
Use my blood.
It's type F.  I'll give you as much as you need.
Jinbe!
Jinbe-chan!
But, the law...
I'm a pirate.
Boss!  What a relief!
Jinbe-san!
Thank you!
Jinbe, you-
It's fine -jamon.
Y-Your Majesty?
What's the problem?  Outdated laws...
are just curses.
Alright, let's get ready.
I'm alright now.  I can move a little.
I'll help too.
Right, thanks.
Jinbe, this'll hurt a little.
I don't mind.
Even when you're hurt,
even when you're doing the hurting,
red blood flows through your veins.
This thin, tiny tube,
too small to be considered a path,
is what breaks through the prejudiced fear...
and the battles that tried to
wash away blood with more blood.
So easily it flows.
It is not some fleeting vision in the clouds,
but a clearly visible path that leads to the sun.
Jinbe.
Luffy-sama, you're awake!
Luffy!
What, you were conscious?
Straw Hat!
Luffy!
This is... our new beginning,
Mother!
Hey, Jinbe.
Join my crew!
Peace has returned to Ryuuguu Palace.
A grand feast begins, where the songstresses sing,
and the mermaids dance.
The Straw Hats enjoy the feast to their hearts' content, along with the rest of Fishman Island.
But Robin closes in on a secret that's been
kept hidden on Fishman Island for centuries!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Secret Uncovered
The Truth of the Ancient Weapon
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!