All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
The crew has landed on Punk Hazard,
an island split between fire and ice.
Luffy, who has formed an alliance with Trafalgar Law, finally found Caesar Clown, who controls the island.
But Luffy has been beaten by his mysterious powers.
In the meantime, Law has fallen before the chief of the G-5 base - Vergo.
So I plan to give the weapon
from four years ago, Smiley, a huge treat.
One that will supplement the poison gas
to become a flawless weapon of mass destruction.
Today marks the birth of a new weapon.
Its name will be...
The Land of Death!
Excuse me, everyone.
There appears to be a huge ball ahead!
Hurry up!
Smiley!  I missed you!
It's been three long years!
Oh, yes, Smiley!
This brings back so many memories!
I've prepared a very, very tasty treat for you!
Man, he ate that huge candy!
What is that?
You're a good boy, Smiley.
Nobody can stop him now!
The Most Destructive Weapon of All Time!
The Land of Death
What kind of monster is that?
Doesn't it look like the creepy jelly things?
Just what is it?
He ate it.
He ate it!  He ate the treat!
You ate it, didn't you, Smiley?
Be reborn.
So it'll become something even more terrifying?
A perfect weapon of mass destruction.
That's one big frog!
Now, be reborn!
Smiley!
It's starting.  Something's starting to happen!
But what exactly will happen?
Hell if I know!  But it ain't gonna be good!
Whatever, we just gotta run to the lab,
like Master said.
Dammit!  Why did the sled have to break now?!
Master!
He's acting weird since he ate that candy.
Was the candy really so delicious?
We must make haste!
Even those who defend this island are running for their lives.
It does not bode well for things to come.
I agree.
Well done, Smiley.
Farewell.
Greetings to the newborn...
The weapon of mass destruction, Land of Death!
What?
Change the landscape of this island forever!
Hey... Don't tell me...
R-Run!
Please wait for me!
Hey!  Wait for m-
My legs!
What's going on?
Save me...
What happened to him?!
Does it matter?!  Just run!
My body...
won't... mo...
Run!  Just run!
Master!
Yes!  It was a success!
Not a single soul can escape!
This is perfect.
The problem with the previous experiment was that there were survivors.
The poison worked but they could still move a bit
so they managed to escape.
But!
It would've worked much better
if I had been able to freeze them!
This gas coats the body like ash.
It is absorbed through the skin and paralyzes the entire body.
Now, my perfect weapon of mass destruction,
Land of Death!
Show me more!  Show me the ultimate hellscape!
What is this?
The people are...
Save me!
...freezing solid!
Master!
Hey... what is this?
What is this terrifying video?
The ones who died looked like Caesar's subordinates.
What the hell is that purple smoke?
By the way, what country are they showing?
Well, you better not look behind you.
You mean... seriously?!
No way!  It was happening on this island?!
Master!
Crap!  If we don't run, we'll end up like them!
It doesn't matter!
There isn't anywhere on this island we can run to!
Oh, I see!  That's why they sealed the laboratory!
To keep the gas out!
Open up!  Caesar!  Dammit!
I ain't gonna die out here like that!
Dammit!  Dammit!  Quit messing around!
Open up!
Hey!  He's over here!
Is Brownbeard okay?
It looks like he's breathing, but...
Those are some bad wounds.
Thanks to you, we...
Caesar!
Brownbeard.
Anyway, Sanji, get this iron pipe off of him!
I'm Nami!
What?!  Why is that disappointing?!
But...
It's gonna take a lot of strength to move this!
We're just gonna have to do it!
Dammit, it won't budge an inch!
Move!
Hang on just a little longer!  Hang on, Brownbeard!
That's right!  Hang on!
You guys...
Don't die on us, Brownbeard!
You think I'd die from that?!
I'll never forgive that damned Caesar!
Brownbeard.
But first, I must save my men, or else...
I could never rest in peace even if I did die!
Hey, are you...
I've got to get to the laboratory where my men are,
and we don't have a second to spare!
But your body's completely torn up.
We're going to the same place.
We gotta save the children from that gas bastard!
I think it's best if we work together, at least for now.
Then we can kick that gas bastard-
Hmm?  That smoke...
That's a lot of smoke.
It doesn't look like ordinary smoke.
It might be poison gas.
Poison gas?!
It's coming this way!
H-H-Hey!  What're we going to do?!
Don't ask me!  You do something about it!
What can I do against something that huge?!
We need to move quick-
Both of you, get on me.
Run away!
Things don't look good!
You guys run as fast as you can!
If you get caught, I'm leaving you behind!
Zoro-san!  At this rate, we're all going to...
We're done for!
It's on our heels!
Run faster than the wind!
Perhaps we've gained some distance?!
Don't look back!
Just think about running as fast as you can!
We can't run like this forever!
Unidentified object spotted at 12 o'clock!
What is that?!
It's a...
dragon!
A dragon?!
Don't be stupid!  Dragons aren't real!
They have them on this island!
But this one is a lot smaller than the first one.
Hey.  Maybe we can capture it and fly away!
That's a splendid idea!
It's decided!  We can't keep this up forever!
We're gonna capture him!
Hold it right there, Dragon!
It's my crew!  They're being chased by the smoke!
Dragon!
What are they doing out there?
And what kind of running do they call that?
It seems the samurai's body is complete again.
Hey, you're right.
So I guess he won't be giving me his legs again.
Hey Robin!  This isn't the time for that!
Hey, you guys!  That smoke's bad stuff!
Run awa...
It's impossible.  If I try to yell...
Damn Sea Stone.
Oh, are they your friends, Straw Hat Luffy?
As I'd expect from the great Straw Hat Pirates,
they're quite tough.
But they're just seconds away from being killed
by the gas.
And it'll continue to spread...
until nothing can live on this island.  A land of death!
Nobody outside of this laboratory will be able to survive.
Of course...
that will include you, too!
What?!
Now, let's show the world...
that against my weapon of mass destruction,
The Land of Death...
a 400 million bounty,
a Navy Vice-Admiral,
and even one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
are all helpless to save themselves from dying!
What should I do?  What should I do?
He's doing something with Luffy and the others!
What should I do?
I want to save them, but with this injured body
I'd just get captured.
If that happens, then all my efforts to investigate the drug and get the sedatives, will be wasted.
What should I do?  What should I do?
That was dangerous.  I almost got caught.
Hmm?  Paper?
"Don't do anything"?
Who threw this?
What's that, a cage?
Could it be?
Smokey!
Tashigi-chan!
Thank goodness you're okay!
No... They're still captive!
Dammit!  We're all gonna get killed after all!
Smokey!  Tashigi-chan!
Our men?
Captain-chan!  Smokey!
But more importantly,
That really is a well-equipped laboratory.
You're right.
I bet a facility like that
would have the means to transport large machinery.
Why would you discuss such things
at a time like this?!
Hmm, alright!  At any rate, we're stuck.
I hadn't anticipated Vergo's arrival, but nonetheless...
Straw-hatter.
We don't have time to dawdle about in here.
The plan hasn't changed.
Make sure you don't mess up from here on out.
It's time for our counterattack.
Yeah!
Eyes all over the New World watch...
as The Land of Death
closes in on Luffy and his companions.
But just as it appears that death is inescapable...
Law's plan begins,
which requires a glorious escape from certain death.
Next time on One Piece:
Begin the Counterattack!
Luffy and Law Break Out!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Begin the Counterattack!
Luffy and Law Break Out!