Translations, Vegard Aune
Timing,        Dino08
Typesetting, DeSi
Editing, mithrandiryod
Encoding, SoCkPaIn
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
QCing, mithrandiryod
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
Holy Land, Mariejoa
Master Bartholomew Kuma has returned!
You've got to be kidding me!
Bartholomew Kuma, are you telling me that they managed to escape from your powers?!
I want a better explaination than that! I'm the one who has to report this to the higher-ups!
Just what I expected from my grandson!
Garp, be quiet!
I gave you a special Government order to eliminate the whole crew,
yet you couldn't even bring back Straw Hat Luffy's head? This is a disgrace!
Don't worry about that, Sengoku!
Luffy isn't the kind of guy who would go around bragging about defeating Moria anyway!
Hmph! Kuma, I hope you didn't take pity on those pirates just because they were injured.
Because you've failed to take it seriously, this game of cat-and-mouse will have no end.
If they continue blindly following the Log, as they are now, they will draw ever closer to the Navy HQ.
Oh, yeah, by the way... I brought the new tea!! Get out the crackers!
Garp, will you be quiet?!
Halfway through the Grand Line
Arrival! The Red Line
What exactly is going on?
This is no good...
Indeed...
I can't catch anything!
This is strange.
We've hit a rough patch.
Ah, this is so boring!
Well, let us be patient.
Aah, Nami! Are we gonna reach Fishman Island soon? Are we?
Oh, shut up! We are definitely getting closer!
Fishmen... Mermaids!
Those beautiful mermaids! We're going to meet the mermaids I've always wanted to see!
Aah, I'm tired of this! Sanji! Food!
Huh? Is that...?!
Awesome! It's a fish school!
See? Good things happen to those who wait!
Now we'll get something!
Wow, they're heading straight towards us!
Nami, do you want to try?
What's wrong?
Something feels off here...
Hey, wait up, fish!
Those are...
Could it be...
What's up with that overt "This is bad, Captain"-face?!
Serpent-Currents!
Serpent... Currents?
Everyone, be careful!
It is almost like they are alive.
This is really bad, all right!
Well, well...
Awesome~!
Sanji!
Leave it to me, Nami, dear!
It won't move...
Weapons Left!
Hey, what are you doing?! Steer the ship!
Shut up! With all these waves, it's impossible to navigate properly!
Gum Gum Pistol!
Are you all right?
You saved us!
I must say, I have heard the term "playful snakes" before...
What a perfect sense of naming!
Hey, you! Is this really the right time for you to be impressed?!
Gum Gum Gatling Gun!
Star Shield!
I can't keep cutting them forever!
How long is this storm gonna continue?!
How far does it go?!
Should we try to escape with the Coup De Burst?
We can do that, huh?!
It won't work!
I can't see an end to the currents.
Even if we used the Coup De Burst...
We wouldn't be able to escape!
No way!
Shall we sing a song?
At times like this, you just have to remember that no matter how dangerous a storm or current is, it will pass eventually.
So let us just sing our way through!
Great idea, Brook! Let's do it!
Well then...
We're rising!
Hey, is this...?!
We're falling!
Chopper!
I thought I was gonna die.
Look at that!
That's...!
I can see it... I can see it!
It's the Red Line!
The Red Line!
We've finally made it here!
There was a nasty storm back on that day, too.
I'm gonna find All Blue!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
I'm gonna be the best swordsman!
I'm gonna draw a map of the world!
I... I'm gonna become a brave warrior of the sea!
Let's go to the Grand Line!
Hey! I can see the mystery-mountain!
It's freaking huge!
That's the entrance to the Grand Line!
Wow! So that's the Red Line, huh?
You can't even see the top past the clouds!
I has taken me fifty years...
Let's go, you guys!
That's...!
It's huge!
Make sure to steer properly!
I don't want you to give me any orders!
Think we can avoid it with the Paddle?
We wouldn't make it on time.
Sanji! Ride that wave!
Understood!
Hey! What do you mean, ride it?
Leave it to me! When we went to Sky Island I experienced a much more amazing one!
The Knock-Up Stream, huh?
That sure was fun, huh?
It wasn't fun at all!
Of course... We'll make it... This time, too!
Let's go!
I'm sure the Coup De Burst will work now!
Everyone, pull in the sails!
Let's go!
Coup De Burst!
We're saved...
Man, that was dangerous...
We're here... We've finally made it this far!
I can't see the top! It's huge! So this is the Red Line?
It feels kind of nostalgic...
I wonder if we've matured since then?
I kinda feel like crying! A lot of stuff has happened, huh?
Anyways, now we're halfway there!
The Twin Capes on the other side of the world, where we met Laboon, is connected to this spot!
Note: Current location
It's great that we've all made it this far, huh?
Apparently, I came over Reverse Mountain from South Blue when I was just a kid, but I guess that is a 30 year old story.
I came to this sea from West Blue, five years ago.
When we've crossed the other half of the world, and see this wall again...
At that time...
I'll be the Pirate King!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
But we've got to be careful now.
This place is close to the "Holy Land" of the World Government and the Navy HQ, Mariejoa.
This "surprise-pool" is the best!
I'm too weak.
Have a try.
Hey, are you alive? Where is he? What happened here?!
N... Nothing... happened...!
I have to become stronger!
I'm still far too weak!
I'm still...!
How is it, Robin, Brook, Luffy?
No use. It's completely black.
It's totally black out there! Hey, I think I saw something there!
Was that the eyeball of a monster?
A monster?
We are going to die!
Although I am already dead!
Oh, by the way, Miss Nami?
I have a question...
What panties are you wearing today?
SHUT UP! TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY!
Scary...!
He's a plucky guy, huh?
Hey, you guys! The Shark Submerge can't go any deeper than five thousand meters, so be careful!
Hmm? The hull seems to be creaking.
Yes. Because we're deeper than five thousand meters right now.
Ah, that means...
But that is terrible! We are going to be crushed by the water-pressure!
Oh! The monster from earlier! It's still here!
What a big mouth it has.
Watch out!
It's gonna eat us!
Here it comes again!
This sounds pretty bad...
I don't want to ride the Shark Submerge...
Me neither.
NAMI-SWAN~!
The "Horror-Nashi Tarte" from Thriller Bark is done!
Oh, it looks good!
Oh! Look behind us!
Here it comes! We're gonna be eaten!
But this is a problem...
It tastes great!
It's good!
It's the same problem we had with Sky Island.
That's right...
We know the direction we have to take, but we have no idea how we're gonna get there.
How are we gonna reach Fishman Island?
We're back!
That was fun!
Welcome back! Good work!
It's no use! We can't see anything on the bottom of the sea at all. Is Fishman Island really there?
That was my first time riding a submarine.
If we'd have gone further down, the pressure would have killed us.
The Log Pose is certainly pointing straight down, but...
This is no good... I should have gotten some more info from Lola and the others.
IT'S THAT THING FROM EARLIER!
IT FOLLOWED US!
Don't think you can beat me when we're above the water!
Gum Gum Rifle!
Somehow, he didn't seem all that huge.
Because we dealt with Oz! Seems like we're fine.
Something came out.
A fish?
A person?!
No, that is wrong...
That's a...
Could it be?!
We're here!
We're saved!
That was incredible!
Don't act impressed! A little longer in there, and we would have been goners.
How could you not run away from a monster like that?!
Well, I didn't notice it...
How could you possibly not notice something as huge as that?!
Hey, not like it matters to me, but there's something under you...
AAAH! I CRUSHED A HUMAN!!!
I'm so sorry! Are you OK?
Oh, don't worry about it~! Anyway, who are...~
Please pull yourself together! Are you OK?
That's...
I can't believe I did something like that! Please pull yourself together!
Could it really be...?
A mermaid?!
Please save my friend, Hacchin!
Leave it to us! We just have to beat up that masked guy, right?
He's the leader of the Flying Fish Riders, Duval!
I can't wait... I will kill that man who screwed up my life!
Next time, on One Piece,
A Grudge Against the Straw Hat Crew
Iron Mask Duval Arrives
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A Grudge Against the Straw Hat Crew
Iron Mask Duval Arrives