It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy had learned that his brother, Ace, was captured by the Navy, and was about to be executed.
He snuck aboard a Navy ship with Hancock's help,
and is heading for the great prison, Impel Down.
If you were to go on a vacation, where would you want to go?
Zoro!
Brook!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Franky!
Nami!
Chopper!
Robin!
Luffy.
Just a dream, huh?
It seemed like a very bad dream...
I was dreaming about my friends.
I see.
What can I possibly say to him...?
Luffy...
Don't worry.
Your first priority needs to be rescuing your brother.
You must have faith in your friends.
Don't you agree?
You...
Besides...
Even now, you are not alone.
Huh?
I am here with you.
Hancock...
I'm such an idiot.
How could I not realize that a Goddess was this close to me?
Luffy...
Hancock...
What am I thinking?
No!
What're you doing, Hammock?
And now, we will travel back in time a little...
W-What's going on?!
Oh dear, oh dear...
Where am I...?
Are you awake?
What?! Who are you?!
What is this place?!
I-It's my house...
Please, calm down...
This is serious!
Yikes...
I-It's reckless to try and move around in your condition.
Besides, at the moment, it's-
Stay away!
I don't care if it's reckless! I have to get going!
If I'm not there, those guys won't get anywhere...
Stay away!
Umm...
I'm curious...
I told you to stay away, didn't I?!
Hey...hey...hey...young lady?
Where did you come from, young lady?
Quit repeating yourself.
What is it?
Have you calmed down?
You're not gonna attack me any more, are you?
It's good!
Isn't it?
After all, you've been sleeping since you arrived two days ago.
That long?
It seems you've gotten yourself into quite a mess.
Ta-dah!
Now, have a look...
at these firmly tied "knots of wind"!
Untie one and...
...it summons a gentle breeze.
Untie another, and...
...it summons a strong wind.
Untie the third, and...
...it summons a storm!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
I thought it would cheer you up...
I feel better now, thank you very much!
Anyway, I'm leaving!
Leaving? Where to?
That's just reckless, young lady!
I can handle this much!
A terrible cyclone is coming...
I told you, didn't I?
You're completely soaked.
Feel free to use the shower.
I'll wash your clothes in the meantime.
Old man...
Hmm?
This isn't just rain...
a huge cyclone is headed this way!
What'd you say?
I'M SAYING THAT A STORM IS COMING! A HUGE ONE!
Oh, is that so?
Maybe someone else is gonna come flying?
Man, he's so rude!
I don't care what happens to him!
What's this?
Turn the handle, and the water will come out.
The handle?
The clouds are raining...?
What's going on?
How do you like it? If you turn the handle, rainclouds come out.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Tastes good...
HEY, WHY ARE YOU SO CALM?!
I TOLD YOU, A STORM IS COMING!
BE A LITTLE MORE CONCERNED!
I think you ought to calm down...
Will we really be alright?
I guess it's about time...
I'm going out for a bit. Young lady, please stay here.
What? W-Wait!
How can he walk around so calmly in this weather?
There it is!
Cool Ball
Heat Ball
Here I go!
Amazing...
Hey...hey...hey...young lady!
Quit repeating yourself.
What is it?
Oh, you can use the knots of wind after seeing them only once?
That's pretty impressive.
It was easy!
Well, I've got to go.
Huh? What's this?
Where...are we?
This is Weatheria, a small Sky-Island.
It's a country dedicated to researching weather.
S-Sky-Island?!
The cyclone earlier was one of my experiments.
I don't know why it vanished so suddenly, though...
Who could have done that?
Nami has landed on an island in the sky.
Will she be able to return to her crew?
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
That was quite a loud crash we heard earlier.
It must be around here somewhere...
Right.
Huh? What's wrong, Taroimo?
It's huge!
Stand back, Kitton!
Wait!
Stop it, Taroimo!
It's a human!
W-What do we do?
Um, are you alright?
He mistook you for a monster...
Yeah, I'm fine.
How can you be alright?!
Oh, so you're alright?
That's great, isn't it, Taroimo?
Still, this is bad...
How far did I fly?
Ugh, it's cold! Is this a snow-country?!
FRANKY!
This is bad!
He's walking around in the snow wearing only a speedo!
Did someone rob him?
Here, put on this loincloth.
Loincloth?! Get real!
Mind your own business!
If I'd...
...put that on...
...I'd be a disgrace...
...to all perverts!
Follow along!
Move your butt to the right!
Right hand on the hips...
...and thrust your left hand out!
Slide...
...to the left!
Right! Left!
And again!
Yeah!
One! Two!
SUPER!
Whew, this is the best!
I'm still cold!
Where is this?!
You don't know?!
How should I know?!
This is Karakuri Island's future kingdom of Bulgemore.
The kingdom where geniuses are born.
Hentai: Pervert, Tensai: Genius
Perverts?
No, geniuses.
Fran...pervert?
Geniuses.
Old man!
Hentai: Pervert, Taihen: Terrible
Pervert! Uh, I mean, this is terrible.
We'll have to carry him to the hospital, Kitton.
Yes!
So he's a cyborg?
He's powered by cola...
What do we do? We don't have any cola here right now!
We must hurry! Let us begin.
Yes.
Old man!
...Old man?
Oh, you must be the young man I met earlier.
I am deeply sorry to have kept you waiting.
H-Haven't you changed somewhat?
Indeed. It appears that, unfortunately, they did not have any cola at the time.
Because of this, it appears that they charged me up using tea...
Darjeeling tea.
Tea?
It has a super flavor.
It is super calming.
Uh...old man...
Oh! How inconsiderate of me!
Here.
It is hot, so be careful.
No, that's not what I meant!
Old man! You were a lot funnier before!
Is that so?
What was I like?
Like this!
SUPER!
Boy...
Are you not ashamed?
You're the LAST person I want to hear that from!
On the island of science, Franky was turned into a gentleman.
Will he be able to return to his former self?
What will be the fates of the scattered Straw Hat Crew?
Chopper has been kidnapped by an enormous bird.
And what will be the fate of Sanji, who is lost in paradise?
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew's Whereabouts
The Island of Giant Birds and the Pink Paradise!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!