Having seen the purity of Luffy's heart,
and having learned of his conflict with the Celestial Dragons,
Hancock began to trust Luffy.
Really?! You're really gonna lend me a ship?!
Don't worry about it.
I would not lie.
Then, please lend me a ship!
It doesn't matter what kind of ship it is as long as it can sail.
The departure will be tomorrow morning.
The Kuja Pirates will carry you to the Sabaody Archipelago.
On the pirate ship?
Thanks for your trouble.
You should rest well tonight to prepare for the journey.
I'm getting off this island tomorrow!
I wanna see everybody as soon as possible!
He really is a strange man...
Sonia, Mari.
Make sure Luffy has a seat for tonight's banquet!
A man?
Big Sister, that's...
Understood?
Y-Yes...
What kind of banquet is it?
It's a banquet we hold to celebrate the Kuja Pirates' safe return with a big haul.
And I get to eat?
I haven't eaten in so long!
Yes!! A banquet!
You're gonna come, too, right?
No, I am a little tired.
I'll be going to bed early today.
I see. So, you're gonna give me a ship and food...
Man, when it rains, it pours!
Perhaps you meant to say "you're generous"?
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
I would never have imagined that the Snake Princess would trust him so much.
I like you!
Food! Banquet!
I'm gonna pig out!
Delicious! And this one's delicious!
There's lotsa delicious food! Aren't you gonna eat anything?
Then I can eat yours too, right?
This one, too.
That man saved our lives.
I heard he's leaving the island tomorrow morning.
I guess it's true that men's bodies are strange?
I saw it at the arena. Their legs can stretch really far!
I wonder how far can he stretch?
I know, I'd like to try touching Luffy-sama's body myself...
Luffy-sama?
Yes, it seems that's his name.
Oh, Luffy-sama!
Watch your mouth!
It is outrageous of you to address a man that way!
Don't forget the laws of Amazon Lily!
Then why is Luffy-sama here?
Right?
Why is this man here, Ran? He was sentenced to death just this morning!
And all of places, he's at our celebration!
I can't believe that Snake Princess has truly forgiven him!
Maybe...
This is a trap that Snake Princess has set up.
A trap?!
He fought surprisingly hard at the arena.
She's letting him have a feast and relax,
so we can catch him off guard and take him down.
It's our duty to take him down, right?
Are you ready?
Let's finish that man off!
Hold it!
He is acting strangely.
He can't have realized?
Quit screwing around!
Cut it out already!
I guess he saw through the trap!
Regardless, is he seriously going to fight us with a wok and a ladle?
This just shows how stupid that man is.
Don't lose to him!
Why aren't you singing?
What are you doing?
Listen up, y'all!
You gotta do this to have a banquet!
Going to deliver Binks's sake!
Following the sea breeze, riding on the waves!
Far across the salty deeps, the merry evening sun~
Painting circles in the sky, birds singing along!
What is that?
Farewell to the harbor, to my old hometown!
Men are funny!
That's funnier than Sweetpea's drunken dance!
Let's all sing out with a DON, as the ship sets sail!
The saga of "I Hate to Admit It, but I Lost to Him".
Waves of gold and silver dissolve to salty spray~
As we all set sail to the ends of the sea!
Just like I showed you, you do it like this!
Like this, like this!
That's right!
Like this!
Is it like this?
That's funny! Luffy-sama!
So men put chopsticks from their nostrils to their mouths and hold...
What an undignified dance...
Amazing!
TL Note: Rubber Stomach Painting
Gomu Gomu no Hara E
Here.
This is the specialty of the Isle of Women.
Specialty?
Penne Gorgonzola with Sea King meat.
I eat Sea King meat all the time, but this is really wonderful!
He really does stretch!
It's so soft, like he's made of rubber!
Your time's up!
Let me do it one more time!
No, if I let you continue, you'll never stop!
This Sea King meat is delicious!
It's getting kinda hard to eat, though...
W-What is with you?!
You're poking and stretching me!
It can't be helped.
You're leaving tomorrow, aren't you?
There are a lot of girls who want a chance to touch a man.
Look!
Hurry up! I wanna touch him now!
You're very popular!
Luffy-chan!
Luffy-sama!
Hey! I'm not your sideshow!
It's okay, Luffy-chan!
We won't have a chance to touch you after tonight!
Hey! S-Stop it!
I can't eat!
Margaret...
Where is Luffy-sama?
Oh no! He ran away!
He must still be somewhere close!
Let's find him and touch him!
What's with them?
Stay hidden!
This is all the food I could bring!
It is great that you will be able to return to where your crew mates are, isn't it?!
Yeah. I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused you.
I was really scared when you turned into a statue!
But you defended us, didn't you?
I heard what you did for us.
Thank you, Luffy!
What is the matter with Big Sister?
She hasn't eaten anything.
Although she says she is tired, it seems she can't sleep.
She must be thinking about what happened today.
Tomorrow morning...
Big Sister!
Elder Nyon!
What is the myatter, Margaret?
Luffy turned out to be quite popular among the women of the village.
Well, men are unyusual beings here after all.
Hi, Granny Bean!
This place is at the cyorner of the village. Take your time here.
And who are you cyalling "Bean"?!
He is hyaving a meal. Bring him some tea or syomething.
Okay!
Granny, you like reading newspapers, huh?
The News Coos don't deliver to the Calm Belt,
so it's hard to get thyese.
The empress of this kingdom is a Warlord,
so we should at least kyeep up with what's going on in the world.
Who's a Warlord?
Snake Princess.
She's a Warlord?
Does that mean she's a really strong fighter?
You are a pyirate, yet you did not know that?
Nope, didn't know.
Don't you read the nyewspapers?
Nope, don't read 'em.
What a surprise!
Snake Princess became the empress of this kingdom,
and captain of the Kuja Pirates, eleven years ago.
She was still so young,
but after just one voyage,
a bounty of 80 million was put on her head.
Just one voyage?
That, along with the bad reputation the Kuja had already earned,
made the World Government wary of Snake Princess right away,
and they offered her a position as a Warlord.
But now that title is in danger of being lost,
because...
WHAT?!
The Seven Warlords and the Navy HQ
are gonna battle against the Whitebeard Pirates?!
What's going on?!
How can this be happening?!
W-W-W-Wait a second!
That's more than I can take in all at once!
What a hopeless man.
There is a limit to how ignyorant you can be!
Although this is only speculation at the moment,
the battle will certainly happen sooner or later.
The World Government has made the first move.
Whitebeard is a man who would never allow his mates to be killed.
Even though they know that,
they have announced the public execution of
Whitebeard's elite subordinate, Portgas D. Ace!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
...they have announced the public execution of
Whitebeard's elite subordinate, Portgas D. Ace!
What's wrong?
Who?
Ace... Fire Fist Ace.
Ace is gonna be executed?!
I heard that a pirate called Blackbeard
managed to join the Warlords by capturing Fire Fist Ace.
Blackbeard...
The World Government intends to take full advantage
of this large chip they've gained against Whitebeard.
Granny!
He's my big brother!
Ace is my big brother!
What?!
Is it true? Is he your older brother?!
I didn't even know that he'd been captured!
What do you mean, "executed"?!
Does that mean he can't get out of it?!
If Whitebeard wins that battle,
perhaps he can be saved.
What do I do?
Where is he gonna be executed?
It says it will take place in the plaza of Marineford,
where the Navy HQ resides,
in a week, which would be six days from today.
That's too soon!
How long does it take to get to the Sabaody Archipelago from here?
Well, I think it takes more than a week.
If it takes that long,
it's all gonna be over for Ace before I meet my crew mates!
Then how long would it take to get to where Ace is from here?!
Impel Down is where he is imprisoned.
It would take a week by a pirate ship.
It would take four days by a navy ship.
Why?! Are the navy ships that fast?!
There is a current that is being used exclusively by the World Government.
Enies Lobby...
Impel Down...
Navy HQ...
This giant spiral current connects those three facilities.
When they open the giant gates,
the Gates of Justice, which lie outside each,
the current runs inside, allowing ships to enter each facility.
In other words, if the gates aren't open,
you would just keep drifting on the current.
The pirate ships take an extended detour in order to avoid that current.
What should I do?
What do you want to do?
Could that be your older brother's Vivre Card?!
Is that the moving piece of paper that was so important to you?
That's a different piece.
This is Ace's piece.
It's also known as "paper of life".
It shows you the direction and vital energy of its owner.
Then, it must be so small because...
When I first got it, it was ten times bigger than this.
Ace has his own adventure.
I wanted you to have this.
Here.
Carry it with you... always.
What? It's just a piece of paper.
Yeah, that's right. That piece of paper...
will bring the two of us together again.
Don't you want it?
No, I'll keep it.
Since I have a clumsy little brother,
I'm worried about you as a big brother.
Me wanting to save my strong big brother...
will just make Ace angry...
But...
Sorry guys.
I'm gonna take a short detour.
I wanna go save Ace!
You know how reckless this is,
and how big this battle is gonna be, right?
It is as futile as a single ant jumping into a storm.
You might get cast aside without even a chance of doing anything.
I don't care about what may happen!
I wanna go anyway!
I can't just sit around and let this happen!
Alright, understood.
So you're going to save the most important prisoner in the world.
If there is any chance at all,
you must go to the Great Prison where he's being held without delay.
Once he is moved to the execution ground in Marineford,
he will be guarded by the Navy Admirals and the Seven Warlords.
Even so,
since your big brother is now the most important prisoner...
The prison itself should also be heavily guarded by military forces.
It is impossible to break in.
I don't care what happens once I'm there.
Right now, I just need to get there!
I have to get there while Ace is still there!
If I had a big enough oar, I'd just paddle there...
Wait! Wait!
This can't be solved just by using brute strength alone.
This is a slim chance as well, but...
Until now, Snake Princess has obstinately refused to answer the call for the Warlords to assemble.
If Snake Princess were to respond,
she could take advantage of it and sneak you in aboard the battleship.
Battleship?
There's a Navy ship here?
Then I'm gonna go ask her!
Elder Nyon!
What's wrong, Enishida? What is your rush?
Thank God.
I was just on my way to get you, Elder Nyon.
What's happened?
Well,
The Snake Princess...
has collapsed from some unknown disease!
Collapsed?
Whyat did you say?!
Big sister!
Am I...
Am I....
...going to die?
Hancock has contracted a terrible disease!
Next time on One Piece:
Love is a Hurricane!
Hancock Madly in Love
I am gonna be the pirate king!