It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew,
and in order to rescue his brother Ace from imminent execution,
he is now hurrying toward Navy HQ.
Meanwhile, at Marineford...
the curtain has lifted on the great war between the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates!
Hmmm, well... It looks like...
I won't be able to take the "head" that easily.
What is he planning to do?!
Try stopping THIS!
If we're not here...
then WHO will protect this area?!
Get out of here!
These flames are too flashy.
Why don't you go light some candles on a birthday cake instead, magma-brat?
You don't like flashy funerals, Whitebeard?
Apparently, there's room for huge men on this wide sea.
Wow!  He's a true demon!
If I can get my hands on his corpse, I will once again possess the world's strongest zombie!
Hurry to the execution platform!
The giant squad is coming!
Don't falter!
They're targeting Little Oars Junior!
Stopping that thing...
is our duty!
His size is unbelievable...
He's more than twice as large as any ordinary giant!
Keep shooting!
He's only flesh and blood... he can't be invulnerable!
They brought one hell of an ally.
Fire!  Shoot him down!
Oars!  Forget about it!
Your size makes you too easy a target!
Ace-kun!
I'm coming for ya!
This is bad!
Stop him!
Oars opened a path into the bay!
Invade the bay!
Fall back!  Fortify the shoreline!
Don't let them reach the plaza!
Where should we run to?!
Go to hell, marine!
Don't get in my way.
Slayer of a thousand men, Rear Admiral Yukimura!
You... What are you doing?!
What?
This is a battlefield, boy!  If you're not prepared to fight, you're only a nuisance.
I'm so powerless!
I've never had to look up at someone before!
You said it!
Hey you!  I've gotta get to Ace!
So don't get in my way!
This is as far as you get!
Vice-Admiral Lacroix!
That Oars... No point trying to hold him back...
There's a difference between being a hero and throwing your life away!
Old Man, please don't stop me!
I wanna save 'im!
I wanna save Ace-kun as fast as possible!
I hear ya.
Men!  Wipe your asses!  Let's give Oars some support!
Yeah!
How do we fight a guy this big?!
How dare you hurt Vice-Admiral Lacroix!
Don't fight alone!
We all have to attack at once.
If you get distracted by Oars, I'll take you down!
H-Hey!  Guys!
The Pirate Empress, I'm guessing?
My body's... crumbling?!
Hey!  What do you think you're doing, attacking marines?!
I agreed to fight against Whitebeard...
but I never said I would be your ally.
Whether enemies or friends, all men are the same!
All but one man...
I want to leave here with my promise fulfilled.
What are you saying?!
Can you forgive this beauty?
Y-You...!
Ace-kun!
Come!  Quickly now!
Oars!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
You!
I'll save ya now!
Oars...
Ace-kun!
Oars!!!
That's enough!  Stop this!
You won't make it this far!
Hey Oars?
No biggie, I'm just curious...
Isn't it hot,
being so close to the sun?
It's hot.
Really?  So even for you... it'd be nice to have shade?
Captain Oars!
He can still move?!
That's awesome!  He even inherited his ancestor's toughness!
Me?
I learned how to make it in the Wano Country.
Try it on!
Ace-san burned the darn thing twice trying to make that hat.
A fire man like him shouldn't be weaving straw.
Whoa!  It's much cooler now!
Really?  Great!
Aim for Oars!
Oars!
I guess there was no chance.
He's such a ready target!
Captain Oars!
What are you doing outside?
Hmm... I don't even get wet by the rain...
It's really sturdy.
This is great!
Still... not there...
At the very least...
Even if it's just one of the Warlords...
Is something wrong, demon?
My legs won't...
Captain!
Captain!  Why are you outside again?
The snow doesn't even reach me.
I'm not cold at all!
This is really good!
Thanks, Ace-
What a riot!
Oars!!!
It's the monster!
He's breached the plaza!
Just a little more...
Just a little further to Ace...
That Doflamingo bastard!
He's gone and cut off a leg!
Even though I said I wanted the corpse...
Go!
Oars!
Save... Now...
Ace-kun!
Oars risked his his life and opened a path forward.
The Whitebeard Pirates now surge toward the execution platform.
But just as the winds seem to blow in Ace's favor,
Sengoku reveals his next move.
Next time, on One Piece:
Victory is Justice
Sengoku's Plan in Action!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!