It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and came to Marineford...
to save his brother Ace, who is about to be executed.
Luffy was striving for the execution platform,
and he managed to make it over the walls with Jinbe's help.
Following him, the Whitebeard Pirates boarded a paddle ship they'd hidden underwater,
and charged into the plaza.
Too slow.
Cross the water and head for Oars!
Big trouble!
Another coated ship has emerged from the bay!
Sink it!  Just like the Moby Dick!
No, not the ship!
Shoot Oars!
He pulled the whole ship in!
The intruders have breached the walls!
Old Man!
Stand back, my sons.
Men!
Rescue Ace, and destroy the Navy!
Garp...
Yeah.
It looks like even we have to take part in this!
If vwe Devil Fruit users fall into the sea, it's over at once!
At this rate...
Vi really will...
will...
not fall!
"Vyou won't fall?  Vyou got vme there!"
What are you doing, Ivankov?
Vyou're too noisy.  Vi can't hear what's happening in the plaza.
Huh?  You're the noisy one here...
It hurts!  It really hurts!
Without a doubt, a battle far more gruesome than we've seen before is unfolding in there.
Perhaps Straw-Hat-boy is already...
Boiled?!
Or grilled?!
Or frozen?!
This is horrible!
What can vwe do-
What are you doing?  We must hurry!
It's all your fault, Jinbe!
What?  Mine?
Indeed!  If vyou'd just hurried up and killed those guys,
and taken Ace-boy back, none of this would have...
That's impossible.
Destroy Navy HQ!
Oars...
Thank you.
Stay out of my line of fire.
Here he comes again!
Guess I've got no choice.
He froze Whitebeard!
You did it!
Old Man...
Oh, my... Looks like
I can't freeze a quake man...
Ice
Admiral Kuzan!
He stabbed him with Haki!
Is Aokiji dead?
No!  Don't be ridiculous.
Ice Block Partisan
Old Man, get going!
I'm counting on you.
Diamond Jozu...
We're almost there!
I can see the execution platform!
We've just gotta break through in the confusion!
I won't let you!
You're all gonna die here!
Ace...
I thought the battle was over when they raised the walls...
but both Whitebeard and
Straw Hat made it over here!
Next time, I will capture you!
I'll become much stronger, and someday, I will...
become...
one of the Navy's Admirals!
Despite my promise, I haven't changed one bit!
Luffy-san...
I...
Straw Hat Luffy...
I, Momonga, stake my pride as a Navy Vice Admiral on stopping you right here!
Vice Admiral... So you're the same as Gramps, huh?
Gear...
Secon...
Looks like you're out of energy!
Shigan: Finger Gun
I'm not surprised.  He is just a rookie, after all.
But...
He's as persistent as ever.
Garp.  Consider your position!
You gotta have more than just courage...
Straw Hat Luffy,
without enough strength, you can't
save anyone, no matter how hard you try.
A-Ace...
He's no match for them!
N-No way...
Luffy-san!
Kill Whitebeard!
We won't let you!
Now will you please just disappear?
Ace's little brother!
Ace...
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Oh, Whitebeard's command has been dulled...
To think that a man like you...
would let such reckless trash...
lead your attack.
We won't let you touch the Old Man!
Oh, how admirable...
There he is!  It's Straw-Hat-boy!
There he is, Jinbe!
Who's that?!
Where's that voice coming from?
Don't vyou see me?!
Vi'm Ivankov, dammit!
Up there!
What's with the size of his face?!
It's Ivankov, from the Revolutionary Army!
Luffy-kun!
Are vyou still alive, Straw-Hat-boy?!
Vi'm... Vi'm...
not falling!
He fell!
What are you doing?!
Vi'm sorry...
What a noisy guy.
Iva-chan... Jinbe...
Let me go, Oldtimer!
I'm... I'm... Let me go!
He's done more than enough.  Treat his wounds.
Yes!
I don't need that!  There's no time!
I've gotta go save him!  Don't get in my way!
Ace is... Ace is...
Ace is my only brother in the world!
I'll...
I'll definitely...
definitely...
save him!
Luffy-kun!  Hey!
This is awful...
Please, Doctor!  Do whatever you can to keep him alive!
Luffy-kun!  Luffy-kun!
Hang in there, Luffy-kun!
A bundle of spirit, who only knows how to talk big...
Young and clumsy...
I like fools like that...
Those with no regard for their lives, advance!
Here he comes!  It's Whitebeard!
If we just let you run wild as you please...
the island won't be able to take it!
Then try to protect it!
Take care of Luffy-kun for me.
Jinbe, what about you?
I've chosen this as the place where I die!
Get back!  We'll get caught in it!
Die!
Damn it!
N-No way!
What a weak blade.
We've gotta clear a path for the Old Man!
These are swordsmen as well... However...
Such pitiful weaklings!
Move!
Clear a path!
I must go to where Luffy is!
Do not interfere!
This is awful!
Boa Hancock has started attacking indiscriminately again!
The corpses keep piling up!
I won't let you get in the Old Man's way!
I don't think I'm very tasty, actually...
I-I'm not done... Not yet...
Push them back!
That's...
The pirates' allies from the shore!
Sorry for the wait!
Yeah, we've been waiting for you!
Dammit!  We let far too many of them get into the plaza!
Uncle will yell at me!
Under the circumstances, some casualties will be inevitable,
but try to avoid hitting our own allies.
Pacifista!
Wait for me, Ace!
He's flying!
What are you doing?!  Shoot him down!
Our guns won't work!
I don't care!  Keep shooting!
This is bad...
Go!
Commander Marco!
Nobody told you to jump in on your own!
The hero, Monkey D. Garp!
The legendary marine has finally made his move!
Vice Admiral Garp!
The Vice Admiral's in!
He's the best guardian we have!
Gramps...
Garp...
If you want to get past, you'll have to kill me!
Dumb kids...
The Whitebeard Pirates keep falling against the Navy's fierce attacks.
Seeing his fallen comrades, Ace thinks back to why he was born and cries.
Meanwhile, Luffy makes a dangerous decision to save Ace!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Power that Shortens One's Life
The Tension Hormones Return
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!