It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has finally reached Marineford,
where he's trying to save his brother Ace from execution.
An intense battle rages as the Navy tries to stop the Whitebeard Pirates...
in their advance on the execution platform where Ace is held.
Ace!
He defeated a giant!
You're amazing, Straw Hat!  You took down a giant in one hit!
I'm back to normal!
Hey Straw Hat, you're attracting too much attention.
Don't let them move an inch.
Don't let a rookie wreck our plans!
Luffy!
Charge!
Let's break through the Marines,
and meet up with the others in the bay!
We're gonna save Ace!
Take out the Navy's forces!
The Vice Admirals from Navy HQ... They're so strong!
It doesn't matter who they are!
We've gotta rescue Ace!
Those idiots!
Bazooka unit!  Aim for Whitebeard!
Old Man!
Dammit... Please stop!
Get him!
I'm...
gonna save Ace!
Get outta my way!
Luffy... Why did you come here?!
Why are all of you here?!
This is my own mistake!
There's no need for anyone else to get hurt!
We, the pirates from Whitebeard's Second Division, will save Commander Ace!
Yeah!
Stop this!
Why are you all doing this for me?!
I'm your little brother!
You're so stupid, Luffy...
You too, Old Man!
Become my son!
What is it?
I'm...
ready to accept whatever the future gives me.
I'll take the outstretched hand that saves me...
or bow to the blade that punishes me.
I'm...
done fighting.
Everyone, I'm sorry.
Resume the attack!
Fire!
Right away, he's the center of attention!
That Straw Hat!
Captain Buggy!  We can't let him outshine us!
Let's take Whitebeard's head already!
Very well, my friends!  Let's do this!
But still, what's up with this crazy battlefield?
The marines and pirates here are all world-renowned!
It'd be better if I just lay low here...
Hey, Red-Nose!
Who're you callin' Red-Nose, you bastard?!
You wanna die or somethin'?!
Whitebeard?!
I thought I'd seen you somewhere before...
You're that brat who was on Roger's ship, aren't you?
That sure takes me back... So you're still alive?
Oh, crap!  He's spotted me.  I'm gonna die!
We're done for!  We have no choice but to run!
W-Whitebeard!  The great Whitebeard...
talked to the Captain!  Amazing!
You really are a legendary pirate!
Don't act so impressed!
You'll catch the same hell as me!
Judging from all the prisoners you've brought along...
I suppose you've come to take my head?
Yeah, that's right!
Oops.  I guess that's the captain's line?
Tell him what we're gonna do!
Damn it!  Now, it's all or nothing!
Sure!  Long time no see, huh?  Now prepare yourself!
There's a limit to how far you can take this!
Really, now?  I don't mind if you wanna take my head, but what're you gonna do afterward?
The Navy's forces are far too big for you to handle.
Actually, they're a bit much for me too.  I've got my hands full here.
So, you wanna join up with me, and we'll take out the Navy as fellow pirates?
You can take my head after that.
Hang on a second!  How much respect does Whitebeard have for you?
It's like they're equals!
I don't think he'd refer to his equal as a brat...
It's reckless of you to try and fight the Navy!  Do you really think we can win?!
Well, if I get serious, yeah...
What happened to his common sense?
Seriously?
Ooh, I'm getting goosebumps!
I'm starting to feel like I can do this!
I can do it!
I can see it now!  Buggy, king of the world!
If the two of us join forces, we can crush the Navy.
Please, stop it!  You're so cool!  Too cool!
Alright, Whitebeard!  We'll back you up!
I will back you up!
Who is he?!
That's right!  He is our Captain Buggy!
Could they possibly be more dense?
I can't believe how simple-minded these guys are.
Disregarding Red-Nose, the others behind him are pretty strong.
It'd be a pain to have to fight them.
So, now...
Bring up the rear guard!
We're on the offensive!
Reporting in!  Pirates from the rear of the fleet are steadily pouring in!
I guess it's time...
Attention front line troops!
Get into formation according to Fleet Admiral Sengoku's orders!
Men!  Continue to return fire and begin falling back.
Their attacks stopped!
They're retreating!
They're breaking formation!
One more big push!
Warships are flanking us!
You're too late!
Charge into the bay!
Alright!  This is our chance to meet up with the Old Man and his men in the bay!
This is Whitebeard.
Is Squardo there?
Old Man!  Captain Squardo is...
Huh?  He was here a minute ago...
Seems we've lost sight of him.
He got carried away trying to impress you, Old Man...
That's too bad.  Then, DeCalvan Brothers!
What is it, Old Man?
Old Man, what should we do?
Take command of all the pirate crews, and pass my orders on to them!
Very well!
Understood!
What are your orders?
Destroy the the warships surrounding you.
What?  But Old Man, we were just getting ready to enter the bay...
Are we giving up?
This situation makes me uneasy.
Alright, Old Man!
Old Man, got it!  I'll pass on the message to the other captains!
What?  The Old Man?  Alright, then I'll start on the right.
We'll take the left.
Sure.  Got it.
We'll go to the right.
If that's what the Old Man says...
My ship will go anywhere you want it to.
Squardo?  I don't see him anywhere... Is that right?
I'll go to the left.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!  The New World pirates are changing their attack pattern!
Yeah, they've scattered off in every direction.
They've started attacking the warships!
Well played, Whitebeard!  He saw it coming.
Seems he's not falling for such an obvious trick.
Suppose I was too crude.
But sharp intuition won't be enough to stop fate!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Dammit, there's too many of them.  We can't break through!
Iva-sama, you're alright!
Iva-chan!  I wanna make a straight line to Ace!
Jinbei!
Advance!
Ace!
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Straw Hat!  You're not getting past me!
Moria!
Fight me, Moria!
Jinbei!
I'm more than a match for you, Moria!
You wanna fight me, Jinbei?
Very well!  I can't use my Zombie Warriors with you around, after all!
Keep moving, Luffy-kun!  Don't waste any more time!
Thanks, Jinbei!
I hate letting Straw Hat go, but...
Jinbei!  Do you really think you can defeat me on land?!
You're kidding.  Moria's up against Sea Knight Jinbei?!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea are a vital part of our defense!
What good is it if they just kill each other?!
What's wrong?
Our shadows are acting strange.
Marine shadows, give me your strength!
Did you know that I grow even stronger when I absorb people's shadows?
You don't stand a chance against me, Jinbei!
So you've gotten bigger.
However, your own skills will never increase by stealing others' strength, Moria!
Be silent!  As long as I win, nothing else matters!
Now then, I'll be taking your shadow!
You'll spend eternity in the gloom at the bottom of the sea, Jinbei!
Hand over your shadow!
You move pretty fast for a man of your size.
You're one to talk about size!
All that work and your shadows have left you...
You don't have enough skill.
Now step aside, Moria.
I'm in a hurry.
Wait, dammit!  The battle isn't over!
It's Straw Hat!
Get out of the way, Tashigi!
That hurt!  You're...
Smokie!
At last we meet again, Straw Hat!
Straw-Hat-Boy!
Kuma!  Vyou're so persistent!
H-Hey, w-wait!
That's right!  His jutte has Sea Stone in it!
Damn you...
I will finish you!
He's a lot stronger than before!
Straw Hat!
He disappeared!
He's fast!  Where'd he go?
Seems we've both grown stronger since we last met.
You can't defeat me with your ability.
Commodore Smoker's pinned Straw Hat!
Amazing!
Damn, it's that... jutte...
I finally understand...
why Dragon saved you...
back in Loguetown.  Straw Hat.
Dragon got in my way back then, but this time, you're not getting away!
D-Damn it...
Get your filthy hands off him!
She managed to hit me, even though I'm smoke...
But kicks shouldn't touch him...
That's...
The Pirate Empress protected Straw Hat!
Hancock!  What are you playing at?!
Do you intend to quit being a Warlord, too?
Silence!
I am so infuriated, I don't care what you say!
How dare you beat and hold down my dearest?!
I will not let you live!
I have never been this angry before!
I will rip you apart and feed you to a beast!
So that was the Haki of the Kuja Tribe...
Hancock!
Yes!
You called me "Hancock" again!
Kuma!  Kuma, come to vyour senses!
It's vme!  Have vyou forgotten vmy face?!
Come to vyour senses, or Vi will fight back!
There's a limit to how much Vi can take!
I don't know what sort of history you two have,
but just give it up.
There's no point in talking to him, Emporio Ivankov, Commander in the Revolutionary Army.
Vyou're...
What are vyou saying?!  What's going on?!
The man you know was probably named Bartholomew Kuma, right?
If you're thinking of the man once called Kuma the Tyrant...
he's long dead.
What are vyou talking about?!
Kuma...
is dead?!
Ivankov and Bartholomew Kuma were once allies.
Kuma coldly continues to attack, ignoring Ivankov's desperate cries.
Then, Doflamingo reveals the shocking truth of what happened to Kuma's body.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Change that Befell Kuma
Iva-san's Furious Attack
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!