Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
After bidding farewell to Fishman Island,
the Straw Hats have finally reached the New World...
where they met Lily,
a giant girl who's eaten the Mini Mini Fruit.
The crew decided to help free her father, Panz Fry,
from a Navy ship convoy...
but then a mysterious organization called the Neo-Navy
attacked and put them into grave danger.
The Straw Hats narrowly managed to free Panz Fry...
but they were followed.
The rescue mission was a complete success!
Alright!
Now, bring the ingredients over here!
I'll cook up some of that Heaven food!
Seriously?!  Thanks, Old Frypan!
Shuzo-san, the target has been spotted!
They're hiding in the reef!
How impudent.  All ships, prepare for battle!
We'll blow up that entire reef!
I-I'm sorry to say, but...
we used up all our torpedoes in the earlier fight,
and we're running low on cannonballs too.
No, we do have torpedoes!
This submarine is a torpedo!
We are proud soldiers of the Neo-Navy's raiding squad!
We've made it this far
by believing in Z-sensei and Shuzo-san!
Shuzo-san, let me fight for you!
Please!
I'm proud of you.  I'll care for you until you die!
Fight to your hearts' content, as soldiers of the Neo-Navy!
Yeah!
All torpedoes, fire!
Pops!
Daddy!
W-What?!
It's them again!
How could this have happened?!
Ch-Charge!
Damn bastards!
Those aren't torpedoes!
There are people in them!
Glory to the Neo-Navy!
What are they thinking?!
They're using themselves as torpedoes!
They must be out of their collective minds!
We meet again, pirates!
You'll never get away!
It's him!  How'd he know where we are?!
Because of this!
A Vivre Card?
When you escaped earlier, I stuck one onto the raft!
Your deaths will not be in vain!
He's super-weird!
You filthy pirates...
are at the heart of this rotten New World.
All of this is to exterminate you!
No!  If you strain yourself, your wounds will-
Daddy!
Lily!
S-S-Stop!
You're still alive?!
Then you die now!
Daddy!
I'm your opponent!
Luffy-sa!
Get him, Luffy!
I won't let you lay a hand on Pops!
The rubber-man...
Right, you're a pirate as well.
So the order in which I kill you changes, that's all.
As you wish... I'll begin with you!
Moon Step
Arming
Alright!
He got him!
Haki that weak won't work on me!
What?!
Haki VS Haki, huh?
He's a formidable foe.
Those arms of his are a real problem.
I've seen through all your techniques!
Gear Third!
Luffy!
You're still standing?
Surely a cannonball infused with Haki
must have hurt you?
My adorable companion, Alpaccachino the Cannon.
He's a bazooka who's been fed a Devil Fruit.
Luffy!
I have killed your captain!
Luffy-san!
That bastard!
S-Stop it.
Daddy!
Usopp-san, would ya do me a favor?
Shoot me inside his body!
What?!
I'll grow big inside him, and make him explode!
A-Alright, I got it!
Here goes!
Yeah!
Alright...
Go!
Luffy-sa!  No!
Luffy-sa!
I can see straight through your plan.  Pathetic!
I'll send you all straight to hell!
H-Hey!
Not yet.
What?!
The fight... isn't over yet!
Impossible!
You...
I'll...
I'll defeat you, and eat Pops's Heaven food!
Luffy-sa, here goes!
A-A-Amazing!
This is super!
What's this?  There are horns growing out of my head!
What's up with you guys?  You've shrunk!
You're the one who's grown huge, Luffy!
Lily went inside your body
and reverted to her giant size!
Lily did?!
That's right, Luffy-sa!
Oh, so that's what happened.
I thought it was weird that only I could hear her.
Giant Luffy, you're so cool!
Awesome, I've turned into a giant!
Ridiculous!  No matter how big you get...
you're still only you!
Oh, you guys!
I forgot about you.
You forgot?!
You bastard!
Don't get cocky!  The sluggish movements of a giant
can't possibly keep up with me!
Hang on!  What's going on?!
What a strong burst of hot air!
Do you really believe...
Do you really believe I'll let myself be beaten by you miserable pirates?!
You overdid it.
I thought I was gonna die.
Luffy!  Lily!
Thanks a lot, Lily!
Don't mention it.
I'm glad I could finally be useful to you.
Thanks a ton, Luffy-sa!
Alright!  Now I get to eat Pops's Heaven food!
Yeah!
T-The food...
Well, it's your fault.  There's nothing for it.
Time to set sail.
What?!  But, the food!
We'll get ingredients along the way!
Our destination will be somewhere with a volcano.
Sound good?
I guess we can do that.
Alright, let's go!
What do we do about Pops's raft?  He can't ride it anymore!
Looks like we don't have to worry about it.
Oh, my.
Super!
It seems like he's already done.
Great shipwright Franky, thank you!
Don't mention it!  Super!
You're still alive?!
How did you know where we were?!
The same way you tracked the Straw Hats.
I just secreted this on Panz Fry's body.
It's a method to track down pirates
that a certain instructor taught me years ago.
Even if you are trying to exterminate pirates, putting innocent marines in the line of fire is inexcusable!
We will take you to Impel Down.
Impel Down?!  Preposterous!
You can put us through any torture, but we will never talk!
If you're gonna kill us,
then do it here, in the New World!
No, that is for the law to decide.
This is the Navy's justice!
Luffy-sa!  All ya'll!
Thank you!
We'll never forget what ya'll did for us!
It wasn't a big deal.
See you later!  Thanks for the food!
Don't push yourself too hard, Hero Chef!
Of course!  Thank you, great doctor Chopper!
Great doctor?  Me?
Even if you call me that...
Lily!  Let's fight together as a giant again!
Of course!  You were the strongest giant ever!
Let's meet again!
Now, let's go!
Yeah!
I was afraid that this would happen.
If I had just been able to convince him, maybe...
I'm so sorry!
Do you think the Navy has learned about our plans?
You needn't worry.
But...
No matter how much they torture him,
he will not talk.
He is a member of
the relentlessly indomitable Neo-Navy.
I understand.
Z-sensei, we are about to land on Firs Island.
Now, the time has come for our rally!
They should tremble...
for the final days of the New World are here!
We will crush all of the pirates with our own hands!
Next time, on One Piece:
Landing!
The Burning Island, Punk Hazard
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!