Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has come to Marineford to save his brother Ace, who was to be executed.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates headed for the execution platform,
broke into the plaza.
Amidst the Navy's fierce assault,
Luffy, with the help of the Whitebeard Pirates,
has finally succeeded in freeing Ace, but...
Now, take a good look...
Wait!
Luffy!
Ace...
Ace!
Ace-san...
He's been hurt...
Damn it to hell!
Stop Akainu!
Seriously?!
Hurry!
Do something about these shackles!
I know, but...
Damn!  It won't come off!
Oh, wait a sec!
That guy is here!
What guy?
You know, the guy who unlocked Ace's shackles!
I'll make a key!  Those shackles will be off in no time!
I see... Alright!  Get him over here now!
Right!
Fire!
What's gonna... happen?
That's what you get for hurting Ace!
Have you learned your lesson, Akainu?!
It can't be... Is he a monster?!
Seems there's still some life left in you,
Fire Fist Ace.
Stop it...
Stop it!
Ace!
Didn't expect to get you with that one, Whitebeard.
I won't let you interfere.
You little brat!
Jinbe!
I will not let you...
hurt him any more!
Quit the pointless stalling, Jinbe!
You are a former Warlord.
I'm sure you know how strong I am!
If letting my body burn away will buy us some time, then I don't mind!
I've already accepted my death!
Jinbe!
Marco!  We've got him!
Oh... You saved me...
I thought-
Whatever, hurry up and remove these shackles!
V-Vice Admiral Garp...
What are you...
Garp!
What are you trying to do?!  Have you gone mad?!
You'd better not let go of me, Sengoku...
Otherwise, I'll kill that damn Sakazuki!
You fool!
So I need to punish you too, traitor...
Jinbe, Get down!
How annoying!
You're Haki-users?
How can this be?!
How shameful... we failed to stop him!
Can't you see that it's too late for Fire Fist?
Take a good look!
Ace...
Hey?  Can you hear me?
You'll be fine, right?
Ace...
We have to hurry and treat your wounds...
I'm sorry... Luffy...
Just for me...
you did all that crazy stuff...
but I still couldn't be saved.
I'm so sorry.
W-What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous!
Someone, help him!
Ace... Please save Ace!
Hey?  Isn't there anybody who can save Ace?  Come on!
Hurry!  Over here!
Hurry and give him some emergency treatment!
Straw-Hat-boy...
Ace, are you alright?
Hurry!  Help Ace!
Sure.  Show me his wound.
I'm begging you!
This is...
Hey...
What's wrong?
Hurry up and save him!
Forgive me...
What... do you mean?
What are you saying?!  Do something!
Hey... Hey!  You're a doctor, aren't you?  Aren't you?!
It's no use... He fried my insides...
I won't... last much longer...
I can tell... my life is at an end...
Don't say that...
Oh, I know!  Iva-chan!
Hey, please!  Use that...
Inject Ace with it!  Okay?
Inject Ace with that stuff you saved me with!
Save Ace!
Okay?  Please?  I'm begging you!
Ace... Ace...
Give Ace some of it too!
Give him a shot of it...
Straw-Hat-boy!
Ace-boy is beyond saving...
That can't be...
Didn't you promise me?
You...
said you'd never die...
didn't you?!
Ace!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Ace...
What are you saying?
What do you mean you won't last?
You promised me!
You said you'd never die...
didn't you?!
Ace!
Was it...
good that I was born?
Huh?  If Gold Roger had a child?
Ain't it obvious?
He'd be beheaded, no doubt about it!
Nah, just beheading him wouldn't be enough for me!
How about sticking one needle in him for every person in the world with a grudge against Roger?
No, why don't we burn him half to death first?
And then we could make sure all the criminals in the world saw what he looked like just before he died!
Great idea!
And then everyone'd say, "serves you right!"
His last words should be something like this:
"I'm so sorry I was born!  I'm just garbage!"
Well, it's not like he could have had a kid anyway!
Nobody...
wanted me to be born...
Ace!  You caused another incident in town?!
Man, what a mess!  Don't go causing trouble for me all the time!
Hey!  Are you listening to me, Ace?!
Shut it, Dadan!
What?!
If I was strong enough...
I'd have slaughtered them all!
I...
probably wouldn't even have wanted to live...
if it weren't for that whole deal with Sabo...
and having an unruly little brother like you.
Oh, right...
If you ever...
see Dadan, then give her my regards.
For some reason, now that I know I'm gonna die...
even her name sounds touching to me.
I keep telling you...
Don't die!
I only have...
one regret.
That I couldn't see you...
fulfill your dream.
But... I'm sure...
you can make it.
You're my little brother.
On that day...
Listen up, Luffy!
We will definitely live life without regrets!
Yeah!
Someday, we will set out to sea,
and live life the way we want to!
With more freedom than anyone else!
Just like... we promised on that day...
The way I lived my life...
I have... no regrets about it.
That's not true!  Don't lie to me!
I'm not lying.
What I truly wanted...
wasn't fame or anything like that after all.
Was it... good that I was born?
What I wanted...
was just the answer to that question.
Become my son!
I take it my beloved son...
is still doing well?
I'm...
your brother!
Say whatever the hell you want!
I'm saving you, even if I die!
Men!
Rescue Ace, and destroy the Navy!
Give Ace...
back!
Finally!
I finally made it!
Ace!
Just answer one question for me, Ace...
Was I a good father?
I...
can't speak loud enough for the others to hear it.
Please... pass on...
what I'm about to say.
Old Man...
Everyone...
And you, Luffy...
Even though... I'm so worthless...
Even though... I carry the blood of a demon...
Thank you...
for loving me!
Gramps.
What?
Was it...
good that I was born?
Well, you...
As long as you're alive, you'll figure it out eventually.
Ace...
In the midst of this never-ending battle, Whitebeard's fury shakes Marineford.
Next time, on One Piece:
Navy HQ is Destroyed!
Whitebeard's Silent Anger!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!