Translations: Vegard Aune
Timing: SockPain
Typesetting: Itachi-san
Editing: DemonRin
Encoding: SockPain
Song Translation: Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX: jaga01
Quality Checker: Desiboy
SockPain
AFX Title: Bun-chan
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
In order to get to Fishman Island...
Luffy and the others ended up looking for a coating mechanic on the Sabaody Archipelago...
however, on that archipelago there were...
a group capable of summoning people from the Navy HQ and the Government...
the World Nobles, known as the Celestial Dragons...
as well as a fearful group of rookies with their sights set on the New World.
But if there are so many in town, I'm kinda worried...
about the old mechanic dude.
You don't have to worry about my people.
He's a hundred times stronger than you boys, after all.
Did you get on?
Yeah!
Well, be careful then.
I should tell you, of course, the Navy already knows...
that there are so many high-level rookies gathered on this archipelago.
That is bad...
Then, they could come at us at any time?
Oh, that shouldn't be a problem.
I wonder if this will speed up the meeting among rookies?
Right now, the Navy HQ is so busy with something else,
that they don't have the time to worry about you.
Or at least, I assume so.
As long as no huge problems pop up on the archipelago,
The Navy shouldn't send any major force here to deal with you.
So in short, just take care not to start any kind of uproar alright?
Oh, so that's how it is?
Gotcha! Thanks!
We're off to look for the old mechanic dude!
I hope they find him...
We've reached Sabaody Park!
Yay!
Awesome!
It looks so fun!
You're not even gonna LOOK for the old guy, are you?!
But the old lady said the old mechanic dude likes it here!
But that was only if he wasn't in the lawless zone!
The ferris wheel!
This is the first time I've been this close to it!
Right!
Then, you guys, let's go have fun!
Yeah!
You're not gonna look, huh?!
Yay!
Caimie!
You can't go in there!
No way I'd let you go in!
We are rising quite slowly, aren't we?
What a nice view...
Awesome!
Let's go again!  Again!
That wasn't scary was it, Caimie?
It was really scary, but it was REALLY fun!
My heart is still racing...
I've never had so much fun!
It felt as though my head had been squeezed into my back!
It felt as though my heart would stop beating...
...although I have no heart...
That's right.
I truly prefer slow-moving attractions like this one...
Such a really nice view...
Look at that!
There we go!
Hey, you guys rotated it too fast!
What did you think would happen when you did that anyway?!
You can't do that!
Wow!
We're so high up!
Ah! There's an ice cream stand down there, Luffy-chin!
Seriously?
Everyone looks so small!
Oh, it's the sea! Luffy-chin, it's the sea!
Yeah!
Awesome!  Amazing!
I can see it all from here!
You're so happy that you're crying?
Yes, because...
this has been my dream since I was a child...
This is the first time I've been to a place as high as this!
I'll remember it for the rest of my life! Thank you!
Hacchin and Pappagg let me come here because you guys are so strong!
It's like everything I dreamed of as a kid came flooding back!
All young fishmen and mermen dream of coming here!
Super-high!
Let's ride that next!
A gondola!
Yeah!
A horror show!
Let's go!
A sk-sk-skel-sk...!
Who'd have thought they were this strong...?
Yeah...that's a problem, huh?
But are you sure about this?
Yeah, Peterman-san...
That woman who was with Straw Hat Luffy and the others was probably...
a mermaid!
When I remember what I saw...
Shoot! Caimie! Pappagg!
The woman's shoe fell off at one point, and there wasn't a foot, but a fin!
Really now?
But it'll be a problem as long as she's with those strong guys, huh?
That being said, a mermaid on land gives us a huge chance!
After all, you can't catch'em underwater.
Thanks a lot for telling me, you guys!
As a reward, you can have 10% of the fee we fetch for her, all right?
Ah, if possible, could we have 20%?
Huh?!
No, 10% is enough! Thanks a lot!
Caimie, wait here for a minute, Ok?
Sure!
You'll pick out something tasty for me too, right?
Captain Urouge... Is that...?
Oh, my...
A Celestial Dragon, huh?
Casually taking a stroll in the lawless zone...
He's just asking for trouble.
Let's get on our knees and wait it out, guys.
Sharlia and Father hoof just left me behind...
Where did they get off tooo?
We know where they were going, so you need not worry.
Brat! Yoo walk as slowly as a toortle!
Alsoo, yoor ride is the woorst!
This guy, he makes me sick!
Hey! Yoo guys, wait!
Why are you mooving?
Yoo're just hoomans and all...
We're sorry!
Please, let this slide!
This man is bleeding terribly!
It seems like he's been caught up in a fight!
The hospital is right ahead, too...
It's troo, this is quite an injoory...
Then, I suppose I'd better hoorry...
and put him to rest!
Please, stop!
Oh, no!
Oh, my...
Just doing as he pleases, huh?
My well-deserved respect or the lives of lower-class citizens...
Which is moore important?!
It is only through your mercy that they are given life.
I've decided!
I shall make yoo my wife!
What?!
Then, I shall start the paperwork to have her brought to the Holy Land as Lady 13.
Ooh, I am tired of wife 1 to 5, so yoo may return them to the lower classes.
I understand.
Please wait! I...
Please wait, you people! She's my fiancee!
Another one dares too stand up before me?!
Mary...
No!
No, you murderer!
How could you?!
Someone, please...
Please help him!
He's just messed up...
Even more so than they said he was...
What?
Doo yoo have any complaints aboot me?
Please let me go!
I'm begging you!
Take her too the port!
Yes!
Who's that?
Captain Apoo!
He's the Pirate Hunter from East Blue!
Why is he walking in the middle of the road?!
Doesn't he know anything?!
He'll get us all in trouble, that guy!
Huh?
You want me to give you directions or something?
Hey, hey! What's he planning to do?
A kid...?
Brother!
Why'd you die?
Brother, stay still.
Brother!
You tried to attack the Celestial Dragon-sama?!
Then of course you'd die!
I hit him?
For a moment, it seemed as though he had dodged it...
Was I imagining things?
Well, as long as he's dead, then it's fine.
Why'd you get in my way?
Huh?
Don't say we got in your way, you dumbass!
What the hell were you trying to do?!
Do you WANT the admirals to come to this island?!
Tomato juice...
Even pirates have their own unspoken laws, you know!
You just caused us a whole lot of trouble too!
Trouble?
You're...
Huh?
Wasn't there a kid here?
Are you even listening to me?! Are you right in the head?!
Uh, I'm not hurt or anything...
Idiot, I'm talking about what's inside!
You're such a moron!
Completely brain-dead!
Thanks to Jewelry Bonney, it seems we avoided the worst outcome...
That man is from the Straw Hat crew, Pirate Hunter Zoro.
I heard that crew has done nothing but anger the Government,
But I didn't think they'd be so stupid as to attack the Celestial Dragons.
Of course he was spared.
I do not see the mark of death upon him.
That bastard...
For a moment, he really was ready to kill him...
What a beast.
A second-in-command worth 120 million...
He doesn't seem like the type who'd follow orders...
I guess that's saying something about his captain, huh?
Hey, where's the hospital?
The hospital?
I'll bring this guy there. He got shot.
Just leave that stranger alone!
I don't believe it.
A pirate helping someone?
Never heard of that before...
I just had a look around town.
People were flying around on these bubble-bikes!
Oh, I saw it, I saw it! Those were cool, weren't they?
Let's buy one!
We've gotta find out how they ride'em!
Oh, maybe that's from Nami-san?
HI, NAMI-SWA-
Hello?!
It's me!
It's Chopper!
Um, there were so many different kinds of ice cream...
We got reckless!
Hey, what are you so upset about?
Sanji?!
Something terrible just happened!
What do we do?!
You're not making any sense!
Calm down and tell me what happened!
Caimie has been...!
What's up, Sanji?
Caimie has been kidnapped!
What did you say?!
It's probably that team of slave-traders who did it!
I don't understand the reason, but mermen and fishmen get sold off at the market,
regardless of whether they've actually done anything!
They took Caimie away, and if she ends up being a slave
for the rest of her life, it'll be our fault!
There are so many human shops on the archipelago,
so we have no idea where they're taking her!
And we don't even know who took her!
The archipelago is too big, but if everyone lends a hand, then maybe...
Tell me where you guys are right now.
We'll meet up there.
Huh? But...!
We'll contact a guy who's a pro at this stuff.
I'll call the Flying Fish Riders!
A young mermaid!
This one will catch quite a price!
Let me go!
She's quite lively, too!
Alright, let's welcome our customers and start the auction!
This time, we're sure to get a lot of high bids!
Save me, Hacchin!
Next time, on One Piece:
Rescue Caimie
The Remnants of the Archipelago's Dark History
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!