Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew find themselves drawn into these events,
and things have escalated into an all-out war.
Now, launch the fireworks!
Alright!  You've been cut.
Soldier Dock System...
Channel Four!
FR-U 4!
Leave it to me!
The New Number, Channel Five!
Brachio Tank 5 has arrived!
Show yourself, Kraken!
They're just ten people.  Flatten them!
That'll be the end of it!
Hey, Surume!
It's me!
Surume!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Listen up, Surume.
You stay here and protect Weak-hoshi!
Uhm... I'm very pleased to meet you, Surume-sama.
They think they're so strong!
I'll make them scream and beg before us!
Wha?  Where 'm I?
Gyoncord Plaza.  Don't you remember?
Looks like we've got some worthy opponents here!
Get outta my way!
Please stop, Hyouzou-san!
Retreat!
Run!
Huh?!
What is this?!
Everyone is taking evasive action!
They must be afraid of our military strength!
Now then, let's target the enemy commanders while we have the chance!
Forward!
Enemy commander spotted directly ahead!
Prepare to fire!
Roger that!  Preparing to fire!
Huh?  He disappeared!
He's reappeared!  Prepare to fire!
Right, I'll get him this time...
He disappeared again?
Over there!  Fire!
Again?!
No, he's over there!
Damn it!  What a tricky guy!
Hey, Commander Chopper!
The vehicle is trembling!  There must be something wrong!
It's a pitfall!
Serves you right!
How'd you like that?!
Ow...
I just used my fangs to dig the ground full of holes!
Hey!  What's going on?!
Usopp?!  Chopper?!
Now, I'm gonna drop that idiot on the bike as well...
Oh, crap!
It's a pitfall!
Is he a complete bonehead?!
H-Hey!  Are you alright?!
Damn you!  This is super-unforgivable!
Everyone out!
Why?!
A quarrel among the crew?
Hey!  What are you doing, Franky?!
Why'd you throw the tank commander out?!
Because this is a one-man vehicle!
Time to transform!
You're already are a pervert!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Stand by!
A transformation!
I'm not done yet!
Brachio Tank 5!
Head Change!
Brachio Tank 5!  Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Docking!
What?!  Docking?!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Alriiiiiight!
What the hell is that?!
Awesome!
Yay!  Yay!
It's the mecha combination of our dreams!
Vegapunk, you genius I never met.
I saw the theoretical design that you had sketched...
and spent two grueling years of trial and error working on it.
By making use of
the shape-adapting alloy, Wapometal,
I've made it a reality!
D-Don't be fooled by his bluff!
So strong!
Don't be impressed yet!
Have a good look...
at the Sword of the Plunderer!
Franken!
A sword!
Attacking from below?!
That's cheap!  It's too dangerous!
Now that you're in the air,
my shoulder cannons will attack you!
Shoulder cannons?!
You're firing them?!
But...
You're so cool!
It sends tingles down my spine!
Damn!
What a tricky guy!
I've still got more new weapons!
Be careful!
Come on, new weapons!
We're being crushed!
You're so cool, General!
How is that cool?!
What?
Have I found some weaklings?
Weak?  How rude!
I'm just a scaredy cat, that's all!
Be careful of gusts.
Do you understand now?
This is the weather science of Weatheria.
Don't underestimate it!
Eh?  Huh?
Where'd Chopper go?
Get him!
Damn it... I was thrown out of the tank.
Guess I've got no choice but to fight.
But there's no reason to fear!
I'm not the same weakling that I used to be!
Heracles'n-sensei!
I spent two years in that forest, fighting for my life.
I couldn't drop my guard for a second!
I won't forget that!
Now it begins!
The second chapter of Usopp the Man's Adventure!
I'll rig the entire plaza with pitfalls!
They can bring robots or whatever they want.
When they're trapped in a hole, it's all over for them!
What?
I can hear someone else digging through the earth...
Daruma-san went flying!
W-Who are you?!
It's me!
I'm good at digging through the earth too!
Chopper!
Awesome!  You've learned how to turn into a stag beetle?!
I'm not a beetle!
I improved my transformation points over the past two years.
Now only one of my transformations needs a Rumble Ball.
I can change into all the other forms whenever I want!
You cheeky coral bastard!
I'll tear you to shreds!
This isn't coral, they're horns!
And I...
am a cheeky monster!
The entire crew is fighting so passionately!
It's like they've just been
dying to fight this whole time!
How many did you kill?
Z-Zero...
Kraken!
Well done, I didn't think you had it in you.
They believed you and you captured Shirahoshi.
Now crush her!
Your brothers still live in the North Pole.
I know exactly where they are.
We could kill them any time we like.
You are legendary creatures...
so even your corpses should fetch a high price,
don't you think?
Are you telling me that's what you want...
Kraken?
Unbelievable... He's been forcing him to obey
by threatening his siblings?
I'm telling you for the last time!  Crush Shirahoshi!
Surume-sama!  I-I can't breathe!
Surume!
You became his slave... to protect your siblings?
I see, of course you want to protect them.
Are they your younger siblings?  Or older?
Let me protect them too!
Did you forget?
We're friends, right?
Surume-sama!
Here comes Straw Hat!
Kill him!
You can't -dogon!
Leave it to us -hi!
Straw Hat!
I won't let you get to our captain -hi!
You're mine!
I won't let you...
Get in his way!
Stop Straw Hat!
Huh?  He disappeared!
What?!
Now I'm really fired up!
Amazing!
When'd he move?  I couldn't even see him!
I-Is that...
Oh no!
That is...
the ship of promise...
Noah!
In order to save Fishman Island,
Shirahoshi stands against the enormous Noah
all on her own!
Next time, on One Piece:
Noah Approaches!
Fishman Island on the Verge of Destruction!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!