All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After their victory in the battle at Punk Hazard,
the Straw Hat Pirates, along with their ally Trafalgar Law of the Seven Warlords,
finally captured Caesar and set off
for their next destination, Dress Rosa.
Let's make a deal.
Give up your position as a Warlord.
You have until tomorrow's morning news.
Later.
Hey wait, Law!
You cursed little brat!
I've found you.
Caesar Disappears!
The Pirate Alliance Moves Out
Doflamingo!
I know that he'll strike under the cover of night!
If you're gonna attack, then just do it!
On second thought, don't!
I-I can't go to sleep!
Nothing to report on the horizon.
Now.
What's that?
What's this?!  Nooo!
What?  Who's there?!
What's going on?!
Bastard!
What are these guys?!
There's thirty of them!  Be careful!
Thirty?!  Impossible!  I couldn't tell in this darkness.
They are quite formidable foes.
Who are these guys?
Huh?  What did you say?
Hey you guys!  We're trying to sleep here!
What are y-
What now?
Huh?  What?  What was that?!
It is a pleasure to meet you, my fine fellows.
Who's there?!
My name is Breed.
Peto Peto: Pet Pet
I possess the power of the Peto Peto Fruit.
Peto Peto?!
Petopeto: Sticky
Are you like a slime-man or something?
So you're...
not Doflamingo?
Oh no!
Caesar!
You fools!
Did you really think you could keep me captive?!
Don't underestimate Doflamingo!
So he's Doflamingo's man?  Thought so.
Wait!
Luffy!
Ow...
That hurt you?  But you're rubber!
No way, he...
He can use Haki?!
Bastard!
I have taken Caesar.  Now farewell!
Damn him!
What now?!
It's a giant wave!
This must be... a Rabbit Wave!
Not good!  The ship's getting tossed around so much that the rudder isn't working!
What is that?
Everyone, look!
What is that thing?!
An enormous island?!
A pirate flag?  That means it must be a ship!
So he was a pirate?
After him!  If Caesar gets away then we're done for!
Luffy!  Use the Shark Submerge Mk. 3!
It can only carry three people
but it'll let you chase them underwater.
Alright!
Luffy, I'll come with you.
There's something I want to find out.
Okay!
Hey Luffy, what should we do?
Protect the Sunny!
Alright, I've got it covered!
You can leave the Sunny to us.
Noser!  Don't let your guard down.
Doflamingo himself might ambush us.
So be careful!
Ambush us?
And hey!  Who're you calling Noser?!
They're already gone?
I hope they'll be alright.
All three of them are Devil Fruit users.
Should something happen...
Will they really be safe?
There they are.
Alright!  Hurry after them, Chopper!
Luffy.  Don't they look like Lapahns to you?
Lapahns?
Those giant rabbits from my homeland,
Drum Kingdom.
Oh.
Those giant bear-like rabbits.
Granted, they're not exactly alike, and Lapahns can't swim.
They're probably Sea-Lapahns.
You know about them?
I've encountered them on my travels in North Blue.
I've never heard of them in the New World before.
Was that the reason you came along, Raccoon Dogger?
Well...
Hey!  Who're you calling Raccoon Dogger?!
I'm not a racoon dog, I'm a reindeer!
Don't forget it, you jerk!
And stop laughing, Luffy!
Sorry.
That wasn't the only reason I came along.
He said, "I don't want to do this"!
You can understand what animals say,
Raccoon Dogger?
That's right.  I can speak to anim...
Again!  I'm not a raccoon dog!
That man, Breed,
was the one giving orders to the beasts.
Is he really one of Doflamingo's men?
We're already in enough trouble without something new.
They're going in!
We're in the enemy's base.  Be very careful.
Hey!  There's light over here!
Idiot, don't shout!  Weren't you listening to me?!
He's right, Luffy!  Listen to what he says!
Whoa, this is amazing!
What a huge aquarium!
It's like we're underwater!
Look at that, Chopper!
Even the ceiling's an aquarium!
Straw Hatter.  We didn't come here for fun.
Look, Chopper!  Glittery shrimps!
Awesome!
All that aside...
Alright, bring it on!
Room!
I'll match you arm for arm!
How'd you like that!
The sun will rise soon.  We have to keep going.
Whaaat?!
I knew it!  He does use Haki!
We've still got a battle to finish!
If you can use Haki, then I'll go all-out too!
Let's fight!
I won!
W-W-W-What's going on?
What is this?
He's saying "master, I've missed you."
Oh, aren't you...
The Kung-Fu Dugong
who became Luffy's apprentice back in Alabasta?
Hey, what's going on?!
I am the brilliant scientist, master Caesar Clown-sama!
Hey, will somebody open this cage?!  Listen to me!
Hey!
Good morning.
How do you do?
Oh, thank you.  You saved me.
Can you release me from here now?
Where is Doflamingo?
Shut your trap, stinking human!
W-What are you doing?!
Do you mean that you don't work for Doflamingo?!
You gotta be kidding me!
Do you have any idea who I am?!
Caesar Clown.  Joker's prodigious scientist, correct?
Did you just say Joker?!
You mean you've got underworld connections?
Now you must obey me, the great Breed-sama!
I will use your scientific skills to build a kingdom!
Huh?  Like hell.  I'm a scientific genius.
Why would I listen to a lowlife like you?
How long do you think
you'll keep saying stuff like that?
What are you playing at?!
Hey, cut it out, you bastard!
Oh, now I remember!
You're the Kung-Fu Seal from Alabasta, right?
"It has been far too long, master!"
...he says.
That sure takes me back!  How have you been?
Well you sure got friendly real fast!
What is the meaning of this?
That's a Kung-Fu Dugong Luffy befriended back in a country called Alabasta.
The Kung-Fu Dugongs are obsessed with battle and will challenge everyone they meet.
But then Luffy...
I won!
...won a fight against him.
Kung-Fu Dugongs' law states that if you lose a fight, you have to become the winner's apprentice.
And that's what happened.
I see.
So, what are they doing now?
Pay attention, seal!
One!  Two!  One!  Two!
Pull your arm way back, and strike!
Lower your hips!
Now with more force!
One!  Two!
Those two sure are perfectly in sync.
You really are the seal from before.  You've gotten so much stronger!
What's this?
"I saw you in the newspapers
and decided to imitate you, master!"
You mean you intentionally injured yourself?
"It's painted on."
Who'd do that?
So, what is Straw Hatter's apprentice doing in the New World?
You stole our precious hostage.
"I'm very sorry, master.
I attacked your ship before I knew it was yours."
"I have my reasons.  You see..."
"After I met you in Alabasta..."
Pirates are free!
The ocean is a vast, fun place!
"I was moved by your words,
and set out to sea to become a pirate!"
"Enormous enemies stood in my way."
"I met several companions."
"We became the Sea Beast Pirates
and overcame many trials and tribulations."
"And at long last, we made it to the New World!"
"But then..."
"That man, Breed, showed up!"
A pirate crew consisting entirely of sea-beasts?
How fascinating!
I will make all of you part of my crew!
"Now we are his slaves."
"It was Breed who ordered us to capture that man, Caesar."
So, Breed is the mastermind behind this.
Judging from what we just heard,
it doesn't sound like Doflamingo is involved.
I don't get it.
If you're so strong, why are you his slave?
"You see-"
Form ranks!
What was that?
Wasn't that voice...
What's up?
"Get out of here as fast as you can"?
What?
How do you do, stinking humans?
It took you too long to get in position.
Listen, the first thing a pet must learn is obedience.
The second is obedience.  Third and fourth, obedience.
Obedience is fifth as well!
If I call, you must respond within three seconds.
Do you understand?
Hey, Kung-Fu Dugong!
You're supposed to be the leader of the group.
You set a bad example by dawdling about!
Anyone who fails to meet my expectations is a failure as a pet!
No different from those stinking humans!
You're Breed, I take it?  We want Caesar back.
Can it, stinking human!
Oh, it's you.
Indeed, I am Breed the pirate.
Pirate?
Trafalgar Law from the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
What's more, you're accompanied
by the 400 million bounty, Straw Hat Luffy.
How remarkable of you to pursue me this far,
bothersome stinking humans!
You won't catch us with something like that.
We'll see about that!
Peto Peto!
What's this?!
I can't get it off!  What's going on?!
Are you alright, Chopper?
Trafalgar.  Straw Hat.
You are strong.  Far stronger than me.
However, do you honestly believe that'll be enough to defeat me?!
Now, you!
W-What?
Tear Trafalgar and Straw Hat to pieces!
What's this?
Chopper, what's wrong?
My body's moving on its own!
What's this?  What's going on?!
H-Hey!
Outstanding!
Chopper!  What happened to you?  Hey!
That was close!
What happened all of a sudden?!
He's...
Get away from me, you guys!
What's happening to him?
Looks like he's still aware of what's happening.
My body won't obey me!
Please, run!
There's no choice.
Room!
Cut it out!
What are you doing to Chopper?!
Idiot!  I won't kill him, I'm just calming him down!
Oh no!
I am the man who ate the Peto Peto Fruit.
Peto Peto... You don't mean...
Indeed!  Using the Peto Peto Fruit,
I can make any creature do my bidding!
In other words, I can make anyone my pet!
Pet?  So that's what Peto Peto means!
Any living creature is at my beck and call!
I can draw out every last bit of strength they possess!
It's time you learned how terrifying that power can be!
Luffy and Law have fallen into Breed's trap.
Now they are forced into a fight to the death.
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy Dies at Sea!?
The Pirate Alliance Crumbles
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Luffy Dies at Sea!?
The Pirate Alliance Crumbles