Translations, Vegard Aune
Timing,        Dino08
Typesetting, DeSi
Editing, rumble
Encoding, SockPain
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
QCing, mithrandiryod
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
As Luffy and the others continued their journey towards their next destination, Fishman Island,
they finally arrived at the Red Line, the half-way point of the Grand Line.
It's the Red Line!
I can't see the top. It's huge! So this is the Red Line?
Anyways, now we're halfway there!
However, the path to the Red Line, which towered high above them, was blocked.
The route to Fishman Island had been lost.
We know the direction we have to take, but we have no idea how to get there.
Gum Gum Rifle!
Something came out.
A fish?
C-Could it be?!
It was no illusion. Caimie, a mermaid, and the starfish Pappagg had appeared before Luffy and the others.
A Grudge Against the Straw Hat Crew
Iron Mask Duval Arrives
Are you alright? You're not hurt anywhere, are you?
Yeah~
WHAT A SHOCK! THERE ARE SO MANY HUMANS HERE!!
What?
W-We're surprised too!
I thought I was going to be digested. Thank you for saving me.
I keep getting swallowed by monsters. This was probably the 20th time.
You get eaten too much!
I have to repay you somehow. Oh, I know! Would you like some takoyaki?
Takoyaki?! That's my favorite food!
Really?! Then, that'll be 500 beli per person!
Hey, you're selling them?!
I SCREWED UP!!
Mermaid~! Mermaid~!
Mermaids, the dream of all mankind! Mermaids, the jewels of the ocean!
Yes, I've finally gotten to meet one of them! She's so cute~!
This is the first time I've ever met one! Caimie, was it?
It's not the first time. You met old lady Kokoro, didn't you?
Thriller Bark? No, that wasn't scary. Not scary at all. The scariest thing we've encountered so far was...
Uh, that's right, Sanji! Let's just pretend that never happened! This is the first mermaid we've ever met!
You guys are so rude!
Huh? Old lady Kokoro was a mermaid? But she could walk, couldn't she?
I see... You didn't know, huh? Well, it happened while you were fighting that Lucci fellow after all.
Don't you die now!
Imagining old lady Kokoro as a mermaid is for some reason really gross.
You are two freaking blunt!
That hurt! What's up with you, Nami?!
Geez, when it comes to these guy's expectations of mermaids...
But she seems like a cute mermaid, doesn't she?
This is my first encounter with a mermaid, too.
Excuse me, would you please lend me some money?
Why would she?!
A SKELETON!!!
See?! How are you gonna make it up if you scare her?! Get lost!
I can open my head as well. Isn't that funny?
Why you...!
That's so funny!
She sure got over that quickly.
By the way, can you poop?
What are you trying to ask, damn you?!
Ah, well, I...
DO NOT!!!
She does not poop!
Caimie? Caimie? This is just weird... Aren't you missing someone?
Who's the one left out of this fun group?
Answer: me.
That's right. I was wondering about that... Hey, Caimie, what's this? This talking glove-thingy...
Oh, sorry. I completely forgot. He's my pet, Pappagg.
He's a starfish, and he's my master.
Master?!
Yes. My master.
This guy?
Yes.
Nice to meet you!
Can starfish talk?
Isn't it strange for her pet to be her master?
Well, I was taken in, and with reason.
~Caimie always feeds me clams~
So she feeds you?
Hito desu ka? Hitode su kedo hito de wa nai yo
Am I a person? I'm a starfish, yet I'm not a human.
Hito de nashi? Hito de nai kedo hitode da yo
Am I not a person? I'm not a person, but I am a starfish.
Isogashi ssu ka? Ii ya ii ya
Are you busy? No, it's fine.
Hito de wa tariteru yo
We've got enough hands around here.
Yay, thank you!
This is where you're supposed to laugh!
So, this T-shirt is of the "Criminal" brand, and it's really popular on Fishman Island these days.
Oh?
That's pretty cool.
Pappagg designed it! I want to become a designer one day, too!
You'll become one! You'll definitely make it, Caimie!
Thank you, Sanji!
Nobody listens to me...
Oh yeah, you. How can you talk?
I'm glad you asked!
He sure got over that quickly.
Back when I was a kid, I always thought I was a human.
By the time I found out that I was actually a starfish, I was already speaking the human language!
Does it really work like that?
Ah, the world works in strange and frightening ways. That's just how the world is!
Anyway, I'm Pappagg the starfish! Up-and-coming designer. Thanks for saving me!
But this is a relief! We were having trouble figuring out what to do. I want to ask you something...
Hey, Nami! The takoyaki comes first!
Ah, that's right! The takoyaki to show my gratitude! Well, I've got to meet up with Hachi somewhere.
Hachi?
Hello, Hachi? This is Caimie! Sorry I got kinda lost. Where are you right now?
Oh, that voice must be Caimie, right?
Hachi?
Do you know who you're talking to? This ain't Hachi, y'know!
YOU'RE NOT Hachi?!
This is Makuro! From the simple-minded Makuro Crew! Wait, I shouldn't say that myself...
Seems like trouble.
Why do you people have Hachi's Snailphone?
'Cause we beat up that Hachi! Isn't it obvious?!
Liar! There is no way Hachi would lose to you guys!
Yeah, you have a point. Usually, we'd be no match for him, but this time, we had the Flying Fish Riders on our side!
The Flying Fish Riders?!
Caimie, you're still alright? Thank goodness.
H-Hachi! Did they really beat you?
I let my guard down. Don't come here! I'll take out these guys and come straight back! It'll be fine!
Hachi...
Y'know, Caimie, we're just about to sell this guy.
Octopus Fishmen are pretty rare, so he should fetch us quite the price. Feel free to come and save him!
We're at the Sabaody Archipelago, in the waters five kilometers east of grove 44.
This is where the Flying Fish Riders' base is!
No! Caimie, don't come here!
Shut up, you damn octopus!
See ya!
Hachi...
Hey...
Caimie...
So, where's the takoyaki?
This isn't the time for that!
Wait... The voice of that Hachi guy we just heard on the Transponder-Snail. It seemed kinda familiar...
It's just my imagination, right? There's no way...
Sorry, Luffy. Can we do takoyaki later? I've got to go save my friend!
Huh?
Hey!
Wait, Caimie. I shouldn't be meddling here, but if you want to save your friend, then we'll help you!
No, that's wrong. I mean, they'll help you!
Why, you...!
And in exchange, how about you help us get to Fishman Island?
Really, Nami?
Of course! Right, Luffy?
Huh? Sure.
You're gonna help me save Hachi, Luffy?
Well, I'm fine with it. But who is this Hachi anyway?
He runs the Takoyaki store I work at. Our takoyaki is the best in the world!
That's important! Men! Even if it costs you your lives, we're gonna save the takoyaki!
YEAH!!!
TAKOYAKI! TAKOYAKI!
They say it's okay. So, do you know where they are?
Grove 44 is an island at the very eastern edge of the archipelago.
5 kilometers west from there. I guess the Flying Fish Riders' base would be about here.
Seeing how we're about here right now,
if we head straight for the Sabaody Archipelago from here, we should pass it on the way. So, let's head west!
Afterwards we can ask the fish, and figure it out.
Yeah, that's right. Let's hurry and go!
HEY!!!
Wow! The fish are sticking their heads out!
We want you to lead the way!
They say they're afraid of the Flying Fish, so they won't take us all the way there. But, they'll show us where to go.
Incredible! You can talk to fish? I had no idea mermaids could do that!
Caimie, if you were around, we could eat as much fish as we wanted!
Watch your mouth. I'll beat you senseless.
But how do we follow the fish in the sea anyway?
Well, just take a look!
Awesome!
They can do this? I don't believe it!
The fish are drawing an arrow on the sea!
Fantastic! We just have to follow this, right?
You're awesome, Caimie!
No, I have a long way to go.
No, this is really impressive!
Alright! Then, I'll take the helm!
Turn it around to 4 o'clock.
Right!
Let's go, you guys!
YEAH!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com!
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net!
So, that's how it is, Master Duval. We've managed to lure the mermaid here! Everything went according to plan!
Got it. Hey, you guys!
Yes, Master?
Go meet them.
Understood!
Umm, she is a precious product, so try not to injure her, okay?
This is looking promising. Hey, Hachi! This time, both you and Caimie are done for!
Well? Are you ready?
How's that? You can't do anything here, right?!
Zoro!
Are we already setting off? Does it look like we can make it to Fishman Island?
Forget that, and look here. It's Caimie the mermaid! She's real! Awesome, right?
Hello!
A mermaid, huh?
First time I've seen one.
He erased it! He just... erased his memory!
We're taking a short detour to save her friend's takoyaki.
But I'm worried. Hachi sounded like he had trouble talking. I'm sure they've done something awful to him.
Well, he's tough, so it should be alright.
Anyway, you guys were pretty quick to offer your help, but are you sure you can handle this?
Yeah! We're strong, you know!
I should warn you, there's not just one gang of kidnappers around here.
There are plenty of these guys on the Sabaody Archipelago. Human trading is big business around here.
Selling human lives? That's horrible!
And seeing how mermaids are particularly valuable,
the Makuro crew, a gang of three fishmen, have been after Caimie for a while now.
Hachi from the Takoyaki shop, probably thought we had been kidnapped by the Makuro Crew and
went after them since we'd been missing for a while, after being eater by that monster.
That's probably it. Hachi is a kind, straight-forward person, after all. It's my fault.
Hearing about this octopus named Hachi, I can't help but think of that stupid fishman.
If it's really him, then we're not gonna help.
Well, there's no way...
Usually, Hachi could beat those guys easily, but who'd have thought the Flying Fish Riders would help them?
Who're they?
Another kidnapping gang who started causing a lot of trouble around these parts recently.
They say that if they target you, you're doomed.
Their boss, Duval, is a guy with an iron mask. Nobody knows what he really looks like.
It seems like they're looking for someone. They check every single ship that passes this area.
What an annoying guy.
Well, anyway, there's no need for you to worry, Caimie. We'll definitely save the takoyaki!
It's the takoyaki seller!
Thank you, Luffy!
Sure! Well then, Brook! Play a song to get us in the mood!
With pleasure!
Huh? Is that...?
Hey! We're in trouble!
What's wrong, Caimie?
The fish said, "We're sorry, but we can't take you any further."
What?! What's wrong?
They're here! The Flying Fish Riders!
Where? I can't see anything!
Caimie! Where are you going? You have to hide!
Wrong! They're not in the sea, but in the air!
The fish are flying!
So cool~!
Is this the time to be impressed?!
Damn, they're gonna attack us!
So the "Flying Fish" really CAN fly?!
Hey, did you see that?!
I saw it! No doubt, that's the Straw Hat Pirates!
Contact him right now!
Understood.
We only came here to find a single mermaid, but this must be our lucky day!
Master Duval is gonna be overjoyed!
Here they come again!
Don't come any closer!
Bombs, huh?
Damn those guys!
Gum Gum...
72 Pound...
Pistol!
-Cannon!
That was close.
Be careful! Once the flying fish jump out of the water, they can stay in the air for five minutes!
There's no mistaking it, Master Duval! It's them! Sure... What? What did you say?!
Return! He told us to pull back!
What?! Don't be ridiculous!
It's Master Duval's orders.!
Fine, but I don't get this!
What the...?
Hey, Makuro!
Yes, Duval, my lord.
It seems that the mermaid you were luring to the base is on a pirate ship right now.
Huh? Caimie's on a pirate ship?!
I'm sick of waiting... I really was sick of waiting! That pirate ship is the one I've been waiting for!
I'll kill him! That man who screwed up my life!
Caimie, run! This is a trap!
That voice, and that silhouette... Hey, what do you think?
Huh? It was him all along?! There's no way we'll try to save you, now that we know, you damn squid!
Next time, on One Piece,
The Fated Reunion!
Save the Imprisoned Fishman
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Fated Reunion!
Save the Imprisoned Fishman