It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered,
and Luffy has infiltrated the world's largest prison, Impel Down,
in order to free his brother Ace, who has been captured by the Navy.
Ace-san...
What did that woman say to you?
She said that my brother...
is coming here.
Long time no see, Straw-chan! It's me!
Spinning, spinning!
The prisoners we suspect are aiding Straw Hat Luffy are as follows...
Prisoner number E 8200,
the pirate, Buggy the Clown...
Prisoner number D 0464,
former Baroque Works agent,
Galdino, alias Mister Three.
Prisoner number C 9915,
another former agent of Baroque Works,
Bentham, alias Mister Two Bon Kurei.
At the moment, Straw Hat Luffy and Mister Two Bon Kurei are causing an uproar in the N-sector of Level Three.
The Blugori can't restrain them!
Hey, Bon-chan! How do we get to the lower levels?
There's a staircase just at the other end here.
Really? I sure am glad I ran into you, Bon-chan!
Thanks a lot!
Straw-chan, you needn't thank me. It was nothing!
Our reunion was inevitable!
It seems the two of them are headed for the stairs to Level Four.
However, we've yet to locate the pirate, Buggy the Clown and Galdino, Mister Three.
A riot in Level Two,
and intruders running wild throughout the prison...
Things've gotten pretty interesting around here.
Great way to kill some time.
It'll all be over for'em anyway, once they get caught.
Thank you for cooperating.
You're welcome.
You can put your mantle back on.
I must have caused you trouble...
Oh, not at all...
Come to think of it...
Yes?
I heard that someone had broken into the prison.
Yes, that's right...
Still, this is the impenetrable prison, Impel Down.
Warden Magellan is currently taking action,
so it should only be a matter of time before they're caught.
I see.
To think that someone would sneak into this Hell on Earth...
There certainly are all kinds of people in this world.
Magellan...
His ability is dangerous.
You must not let him find you, Luffy.
What happened to Saldeath?
The Blugori couldn't stop Straw Hat Luffy and Mister Two, so...
...he's gone to suppress the uproar in Level Two.
Why did nobody report the situation to me before it got this bad?!
You were the one who was so focused on Hancock-dono that you ignored the reports, remember?
I ignored the reports, you say?!
That's right. This is ALL your fault.
Warden...
I would like to go see the prisoner as soon as possible.
Right, let's go! Going right now!
W-Warden! This is a major incident, you know!
Sheesh, if you'd just looked into the situation back there...
Warden, your breath...!
I ignored the reports, you say?!
Ah, no, maybe you didn't...
Did the guests leave, Warden?
Oh, Sadi-chan.
Salute the Jailer!
We've finished preparing for the hunt...
So, what should we do?
Perfect timing. Is anyone on Level Three?
The Minotaurus...
went there.
I see. But there's a way out of Level Three.
I suppose he won't be able to pursue them.
I'll leave the fracas on Level Two to Saldeath...
Send all remaining Impel Down staff here to Level Four!
Understood, Sir!
If they manage to escape from the Minotaurus and fall down here...
I'll finish them off personally in Inferno Hell!
They've underestimated this Great Prison, Impel Down!
The air here is so unbearably hot...
Well, tough, we don't have a choice.
This is the absolute safest place to be right now...
Still, we've gotta think of a way to get back up to Level One...
...or we won't last long...
I haven't even a drop of spit to save my life...
Are we going to die like this?
What's going on here?
Where are all the Jailers that were running around just now...
It's so quiet...
Could it be that we're no longer in the world of the living?
This atmosphere is giving me the willies...
S-Straw-chan! This is really bad!
W-What's with this thing? It sure is fast!
It's the Minotaurus!
The Minotaurus?
A cold-blooded Demon Guard!
A monster that tosses people like trash!
That's what it is!
A monster? A Devil Fruit user?
How would I know?!
Bon-chan!
That hurt!
That thing's fast!
Straw-chan, watch out!
I'm...gonna die...
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
You alright, Bon-chan?
I-I thought I was dying...
I saw a field of Okama before my eyes...
You really are strong...
I'm sure that monster is still alive, but he must be hurt.
Huh? What?!
I'm so angry!  This is just awful!
My makeup is ruined!
Cosmetics, cosmetics! I need cosmetics!
That, and my toe-shoes, clothes, weapons, and...
booze, tears, and Okama Way!
I wanna get down from here now.  I'm thirsty and hungry!
There's no cause for concern, Straw-chan!
Getting from Level Three to Level Four is as easy as puke!
Seriously?!
Yep! Too, too easy! So easy! Way too easy!
There it is, Straw-chan.
Just climb the great, big wall over there.
The wall? You mean up there?
That's right.
But don't get so excited that you leap over it.
Right!
Hot hot hot hot HOT!
What's with that wall?
It's as hot as a frying pan!
A frying pan, huh? That's exactly right, Straw-chan!
So, you alright?
Ready, and...
Hot!
See this, Straw-chan? Look down there.
What's with this place?
There's so much hot air and smoke!
It's too hot to stand up!
Right?
However, the place below us is, indeed, where you wanted to go: Level Four, the Inferno Hell!
The Inferno.  That's below here?
Indeed.  As you said,
Level Four is a massive frying pan.
A sea of boiling blood and fire wait for you down there.
The heat on this floor is nothing compared to down there, huh?
You can try jumping down there, if you like,
but if you don't take care in landing, you won't escape with just a burn.
Beyond this point, every move forward is risking your life.
Bon-chan,
you said there was someone you wanted to see, right?
I'd like to know who this guy is you're risking your life to see.
People call him a "Miracle Man".
Locked away for a crime he didn't commit, he is known as Iva-san!
The Queen of the Drag Queendom on Momoiro Island in the Grand Line!
The great Okama Queen, admired by all Okama in the world!
Okama Queen?
Okama have queens? Awesome!
That's right!
I want to meet him!
And if I can, I'd like to save him!
Hey wait!  We were in such a nice mood here, and you go and bring THAT thing back here?!
I thought you were trying to escape!
STRAW HAT!
So you wanna come along after all?
As if anyone'd wanna go to Hell!
We were just hiding, and this thing just came flying at us!
I dunno why, though...
Oh, I sent him flying at you.
Oh, so it was you then?  WAIT JUST A MINUTE?!
I've had enough of this...
I'd rather just get caught...
Minotaurus, you... damn monster...
My life's at stake here...
I've got no choice but to reveal my trump card!
Hey, Straw Hat!
You remember my super-powerful weapon
that I used to strike fear into your heart, my Special Buggy-ball?
Nah.
"Nah"? How can that be...?
LIKE HELL! I'm talking about the
Buggy-ball, y'know, the Buggy-ball!
Don't you remember me blowing up a whole town in one blow with it?
KA-BOOM! Y'know, the whole town just went KA-BOOM!
Don't you remember that powerful attack?!
Nope.
Well...What? Uh...
I had this really powerful cannonball called the Buggy-ball, you see...
It was like, my favorite weapon and stuff...
The Buggy-ball...
If you gave it your own name,
that must mean that you have a lot of faith in this Buggy-ball of yours, right?
Exactly!
And I've developed a new weapon, which allows me to store a miniature-version with the same power in my own body!
The "Muggy-Ball"!
You changed the name?!
Take this!
Awesome!
It worked!
Well, that's how it works.
How's that? Remembered it yet, Straw Hat?
SHIT! It's still conscious?!
Let's do it, Straw-chan!
Hey, Three! You really can't use your Doru-Doru powers here?
It'll melt in just three seconds!
Then I'll have to do it in three seconds.
Flying, I'm flying! My flying Okama Kenpo!
Here I go, Straw Hat!
Right!
WE DID IT!
WE BEAT A MONSTER FROM HELL!
Right! Now let's get going down to Level Four!
This is Level Four.
All our forces have assembled here except Warden Magellan.
Stay away,
Luffy...!
As Buggy and Mister Three continue their attempt to escape, and Luffy strives to travel deeper into the prison,
chaos and a bad twist of fate send them plummeting into the fiery bowels of Level Four!
Elsewhere, Warden Magellan, along with the full forces of Impel Down, are lying in wait for Luffy!
Next time, on One Piece:
Preparations for War!
Decisive Battle in Level Four - Inferno Hell
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!