It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has come to Marineford to save his brother Ace, who was to be executed.
Amidst the Navy's fierce assault,
Luffy finally succeeded in freeing Ace,
but Admiral Akainu dealt a lethal blow to Ace.
Old Man...
Everyone...
And you, Luffy...
Even though...
I'm so worthless...
I carry the blood of a demon...
Thank you...
for loving me!
Ace...
Did you think I was dead?
But...
What're you crying for?!
Don't just kill me off like that, you idiot!
I promise you, I will not die.
Do you really think I could die and leave behind such a weakling of a little brother?
Garp.
Take care of my child.
This child's name is Gol D. Ace.
Didn't ya know?
When you exchange sake cups, you become brothers.
From today onward...
we are brothers!
This can't be!
Ace...
Ace!
Fire Fist Ace is dead!
Straw-Hat-boy!
His mind has shattered...
His life is in danger!
It's Akainu!
Now...
you're next!
Straw Hat!
I won't let you kill him!
Luffy-kun!  Luffy-kun!
Pull yourself together!
Get out of my way!
The fight... isn't over yet!
Get Ace's brother out of here, Jinbe!
Understood!
Straw Hat's survival was Ace's final wish!
Commander... Marco...
We will absolutely protect him in Ace's place!
If we let him die,
it will be the Whitebeard Pirates' greatest shame!
Luffy-kun!  Hang in there!
I thought I said...
I wouldn't let either of them escape?!
Straw Hat!
Akainu-san!
The Old Man is pissed!
All of you, get away from here!
Meigou: Dark Dog
Old Man!
This is the end for you!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Old Man!
Old Man...
Old Man.
Old Man!
Navy HQ is crumbling to pieces!
Damn you...
Whitebeard!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Don't fall!
Hold on!
Is it over?
What about the Old Man?
Old Man!
He split the entire plaza in two!
The pirates are on the other side of the gorge!
We've been completely cut off from the Old Man!
Old Man!
Even with his innards roasted, he's still this powerful?!
I'm not done yet!
From this point forward...
I will take you on!
Come!
All men, get aboard the ships!
Old Man!
Think of the reason he stayed behind...
of the dreams he's entrusted us with!
If you're gonna grieve him, then do it on the ship!
Old Man!  Ace!
Hurry!
Gather all seaworthy ships by the coast!
Do you really think we'll let you escape?!
Everyone, hurry!
Please!  I am worried for Luffy's safety!
Please let me be selfish enough to watch over you a little longer...
Old Man.
Hey, look!  What is that?!
There's something hiding in the shadows behind HQ!
Ah.  They saw me.
And that's not all!  Who are those people on the execution stand?!
They've finally noticed us.
How did you get here?!
What are they doing here?!
You little brat...
They're all criminals so villainous that their very existences have been erased from the records!
There's nobody else that huge!
It's the pirate... The Giant Battleship, Sanjuan Wolf!
Ah.  Not only did they see me, but they figured out who I am.
The Corrupt King, Avalo Pizarro!
How refreshing it is to be back outside!
The Great Drinker, Vasco Shot!
C'n I kill them guys down there?
The Crescent Moon Hunter, Catarina Devon!
I like you, too.
And that's the Head Jailer of Impel Down...
Shiliew of the Rain!
It's the Blackbeard Pirates!
Long time no see!
Glad I could see you before you die...
Old Man!
Teach!
It all started because of this man.
Blackbeard challenges Whitebeard, for the sake of his hidden ambitions.
And Whitebeard, hoping to avenge Thatch, strikes back at Blackbeard.
The showdown of destiny begins, at last!
Next time, on One Piece:
Settling the Score
Whitebeard VS The Blackbeard Pirates
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!