It has been a while.
The legendary capital with many mixed cultures, Grand Jipang...
is in the middle of summer.
Everyone seems to be more energetic than the sun.
The reason for that is...
Big news! Big news!
Big news!
Grand Portable Shrine Race?
That's right!
The whole town is excited because of this event!
A race that takes place every 100 years, huh...
I've heard of that before.
I heard there's an incredible prize.
I heard the winner can make a wish on the sacred treasure in the Grand Shrine.
Will anything come true?
Here's your cold water.
Thank you!
Delicious!
You're nice!
Wait, who is she?
She's our new waitress.
My name is Omao. Nice to meet you.
Another bowl!
Here you go.
Wow, an extra serving!
Awesome! The service here is great!
Delicious!
You don't have to spoil him with that much service, Omao-chan.
He's just gonna put it on his tab and not pay for it anyway.
Okay.
Oh, and what's that sacred treasure-thing about?
Well...
It is said that the sacred treasure which is shown only once every 100 years...
has the mysterious power to grant any one wish.
A certain detective who's wish came true became a samurai.
And a certain cook was married to the most beautiful woman in town...
and lived happily ever after.
That sounds nice.
That sounds interesting.
Okay! Let's enter that Grand Portable Shrine Race!
No way!
I don't want to enter that race and get myself
drenched in sweat for such a stupid reason.
And it seems that the winner is rewarded with one million beli.
Okay!
Let's hurry up and get ready!
We're going to win the Grand Portable Shrine Race!
Ah, she came to life.
Before that, we need a good Portable Shrine built to win.
So where are we going, Nami?
A lumberyard.
Lumberyard?
I heard there's a really skilled carpenter there known as Jipang's best.
Excuse me!
Is nobody home?
W-W-W-What is this?
Oh, what a nice cloth.
My bad, my bad.
You picked it up for me?
Thanks, Sis.
It was blown away when I was drying it with Franky Workshop's special super dryer machine.
Master!
Going out in public dressed like that...
is a really bad idea!
That was close.
You didn't make it in time!
Well, can you give it back to me, Sis?
That.
This?
That's my loincloth.
Super!
L... L... L...
LOINCLOTH?!
Wow!
What is this machine?
It's my creation, the super dryer machine,
Fan-Fan Sunny Wind.
So cool!
Loincloth...
A loincloth... touched my face.
So, what kind of super Portable Shrine do you want me to make?
Well, of course it's-
One that can win!
That's right.
Make us a really cool one that can win for sure.
You say that so easily, but the other racers seem tough.
The legendary rider team that's known as the fastest in Grand Jipang,
The Flying Fish Crimson Squad.
The company that's keen for love and quick on the job,
Rolling Post Office.
Oh, I love you.
Marry me. Marry me.
Marry me!
Run away!
They're all very well known teams.
There are other rivals too.
Thriller Company?
What's that?
I've never heard of them.
Who are you guys?
They're the guys you were just talking about.
They're Thriller Company, a company that only deals with import products in that newly built 13 story building.
Then you guys came to ask for a Portable Shrine too?
Our Portable Shrine is already completed!
We just came to warn you guys...
that it's useless to participate in the race.
What did you say?!
What do you mean by that?
That's right!
We won't know until we try!
That's a good attitude.
She's my type of girl.
Anyways, it's best that you listen to us.
You don't want to get hurt, do you-
Hey, Cindry-chan, why are you in front of me?
There's no use threatening us.
We have the detective, Boss Luffy with us!
Well, we'll leave for now.
But don't think you'll be safe after standing up against Thriller Company!
Hey.
Your friends already left.
They left only me...
W-Well, I warned you!
What's with that guy?
What a weirdo.
He's disgusting!
They might be planning something on us.
Okay, listen.
Don't lose to guys like them!
I'll make a super Portable Shrine for you guys.
One that will definitely win.
So win!
Of course!
Let's win, guys!
Go!
Go, go, go!
You aren't shouting loudly enough!
So noisy.
What's goin' on?
Stop, stop!
What a lame shout.
But Boss, there isn't anything else that comes to mind.
There's one isn't there?
One that's perfect for the fastest group,
the Flying Fish Crimson Squad.
Handsome! Handsome! Handsome! Handsome!
That's good!
Keep going!
They're just idiots.
With this, victory is ours.
And then...
Duval-sama, you're wonderful!
Marry me!
Those who want a kiss, line up, line up!
Wait your turn!
You shouldn't do that!
W-What happened?
Boss, four of us vanished all of a sudden!
What?
Count again.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Bear.
What, you're all here.
You're right!
Who the hell are you guys?!
We're just zombies passing by.
Z-Zom...
Where did you take our friends?
I'm sorry I got carried away.
I'm sorry we're so noisy every night.
I just wanted to be known.
Please use me as soup base.
Why are you guys so depressed?
That's because I did this.
Useless!
I'm useless!
I'm so useless!
Boss!
Even if we carry Portable Shrines...
Even if we win the race...
Nothing in life is going to work out the way we want!
This thing...
This is all just a farfetched dream!
Boss!
That's one down.
Not even a nibble...
Oh, I got one!
It's big!
I won't lose!
Help~
You sure eat a lot.
You're right.
This guy doesn't have any manners.
Sheesh, who is this guy?
You sure eat a lot.
I want more!
Don't eat with him!
Pay up, please.
Why me?!
That was very delicious.
Thank you very much for the me-
Oh, excuse me.
You're seriously rude!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm sorry for the late introduction.
Nice to meet you.
I am dead and only bones, Brook.
I was born in...
Born in...
I forgot.
What's that supposed to mean?
If you're going to introduce yourself, do it all the way!
It makes me feel uneasy!
I only remember my name.
Can it be that you lost your memories due to shock?
Hey, isn't there something in his head that's making noise?
Maybe a screw came loose?
That's not good.
It opens?!
Wow!
This thing came out.
It's... a flute, right?
A flute?
Here we go.
What's going on in your head?!
You're an interesting guy.
That looks pretty good on you.
The Flying Fish Crimson Squad is out.
All that's left is Rolling Post Office and Restaurant Kazaguruma.
If we can get rid of these guys, victory will be ours!
The race is tomorrow.
Let's go finish the job, Absalom.
You don't have to tell me.
Tonight will be fun!
My, Cindry-chan, why are you in front of me?
Everyone, here's some food.
Oh, thanks!
Lucky!
Who's moving our Portable Shrine?
I don't know.
Is it a thief?
I-It's floating!
I ate a lot.
That was good!
I can't help myself but to eat a lot when I'm with Boss.
You guys seriously eat too much.
W-What is that?
A Portable Shrine is flying.
Wait!
Portable Shrine!
Let's go after it!
Oh, you're handsome!
Marry me!
No.
Rejected!
It's the 4,450th rejection!
This is... really heavy.
Hold it!
That Portable Shrine, stop right there!
What are you guys?
Those guys...
Scary zombies!
Wow! Great job, Brook!
Why do I know this move?
Boss!
What's going on?
Nami, Sanji!
This is...
Marry meeeeeeeee.
How terrible.
This isn't good.
We can't enter the race like this!
We have no choice but to forfeit.
When will I be able to marry?
If this is an action against race contenders, then our Portable Shrine is in danger!
No, before that, Omao-chan is in danger.
Omao-chan?
She hasn't come back ever since she went to deliver lunch to the Franky Workshop.
So we were on our way to see what happened.
Watch out!
Move, move, move!
Omao-chan!
Boss, Franky-san and the others are...
Get Dr. Blue Nose right away!
Yeah.
Hey, what's wrong?
My head hurts.
My eyes are getting blurry.
Even though I'm only bones and don't have eyes...
You're too relaxed.
I remembered.
Did your memories return?
Yes.
I remembered everything.
W-What's with that outfit?
Where are you going?
I can't stay here.
That's because...
I used to be a member of Thriller Company.
What did you say?!
Brook-san...
Hey hey, that's a tough joke.
Thank you for your care.
H-Hey...
To be continued...
We'll win this fight!
Get them, everybody!
Do it yourself for once!
Next time, on One Piece:
Special Historical Arc.
Destroy! Thriller Company's Trap!
I'm gonna be a detective!