Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew find themselves drawn into these events, and things have escalated into an all-out war.
Due to Hody's ruthless scheme,
an unprecedented crisis looms over Fishman Island.
Weren't you listening?
I told you, right?
Both Fishman Island... and Shirahoshi...
Luffy-sama.
...and my promise to my friends...
Straw Hat.
I...
will protect them all!
Squid!  Squid!  Squid!
I will  stop the Noah!
Fall... Noah!
Kill all the... fishmen...
who have lost their pride!
Those terrifying commanders...
didn't stand a chance!
Just how strong are these people?!
Wake up!
Look out below!
This is gonna be dangerous!
Wadatsumi is...
falling on us!
You should've dropped him further away,
you clumsy cook!
Shut it!  Or else I'll drop him on your head next time!
You're amazing, Sanji!
Hey, Chopper!  Shrink down a bit!
You're making my giant robot look small!
Franky, that beam was awesome!
Was that robot actually good for anything?
Nami-san!
What?
Please wear a miniskirt!
Shut it!
Exactly what I'd expect from Luffy-kun's crew.
He did it!
This time... Luffy-san...
really beat Hody!
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
The Straw Hat pirates...
defeated the New Fishman Pirates!
Hey...
The N-Noah!
The Noah is almost on top of us!
Run!
The island's gonna be crushed!
If we hang around for too long,
the Neptune Army's gonna trap us in the plaza!
Hurry!  Those insane commanders are gone!
This is terrible!  How is the evacuation proceeding?!
Very few citizens have made it to safety.
Most of them are still on the island!
Are you alright?
Is it too late?!
Didn't it work... Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat!
Even though the rebel threat has been defeated...
How tragic.
No, there's still hope!
He still...
isn't giving up!
Straw Hat Luffy-san...
is doing all he can...
to destroy...
the Noah!
Destroying...
The Noah?
That enormous ship?!
Seriously?!  That's just too reckless!
Have some guts, all of you.
I agree.  Let's watch and wait.
Luffy-san!
Luffy-sama!
If he can destroy the Noah before it crashes...
then the island will be saved.
But if he can't make it...
Fishman Island will be destroyed!
Show us what you can do, Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Luffy!
Luffy-kun!
What are you doing?!
I... won't run!
Don't be ridiculous!  Can't you see the Noah?!
I know!  I know, but...
hearing what Straw Hat is doing...
reminded me...
of when I was a kid, twenty years ago!
Of that one human this whole country is indebted to!
This is one great catch!
Wait!
No!
Who are you?!  Don't you value your own life?!
Huh?!
Hey, you're kidding, right?!
Why would he...
side with the fishmen?!
Neptune helped me out once, long ago.
We exchanged the drink of friendship!
S-Spare our lives!
We'll never kidnap fishmen or mermaids again!
Don't cause any trouble in my friend's country!
You snot-nosed brats!
I'm making this island...
my turf!
You mean Whitebeard?  You trust these guys
as much as you trusted that great pirate?!
You know... I actually hate humans...
and this is the fishmen's country... yet he was...
We made the decision with Jinbe when we entered the plaza.
We won't let anyone harm Fishman Island!
You can leave it all to us, Bro-hoshi!
We're friends, ain't we?
He said something like that,
and is putting his life on the line!
Straw Hat!
You have to do it, Straw Hat!
That's right, Straw Hat!  We're cheering for you!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
You're human, yet you're fighting for us!
We're not gonna run away!
Hang in there, Big Brother Straw Hat!
Fishman Island is in your hands now, Straw Hat!
Go, Straw Hat!
We believe in you!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-chan!
Stop, Noah!
Stop!
Halfway there...
Luffy-sama!
Your wounds are opening!
Stay away!
Watch from over there!
Right now, I gotta put everything I got
into destroying this thing!
Stop right there, ship!
Straw Hat!
Luffy!  Do it!
Smash it!
Super!
Father, I'm so sorry.
We must destroy the Noah.  There's no other way.
Straw Hat!
It's the ship of promise...
but we have no other choice. Our lives are more important.
Forgive us.  It looks like
we won't be able to keep our promise -jamon...
Joyboy.
Just a little more!
Please...
Stop!
Who's there?!
Luffy-sama, please stop!
Luffy-sama!  I beg of you, stop!
Get out of my way, Weak-hoshi!
If I don't destroy it, the island's gonna...
It's alright!
Of course it's not!  Everyone's still on the island!
The Noah has already...
stopped!
Sea Kings?  Why?
Luffy-sama yelled at me again!
Hey, this is no time to worry about that!
I don't understand it either.
But...
the Noah has been stopped.
What is this?!
What's going on?  The Sea Kings stopped the ship!
Luffy-sama!  Your wounds have opened!
You're covered in blood!
W-Well... whatever.
As long as... the ship stopped.
I'm just glad... everyone's... safe.
Luffy-sama!
It's alright.
My, what a remarkable human.
What a strong human.
Even if we'd been late,
the island might have still been saved...
but the Noah would have been completely destroyed.
I'm so glad we made it.
Good thing Princess Shirahoshi called us here.
I couldn't do anything... I was so sad.
That's not true.  You were touched
by the Straw Hat child's strong emotions...
and you made a wish.
An impassioned wish...
that you could help him save the island.
Our power is your power.
You summoned us to help him.
A-Attention everyone.
T-This is unbelievable.
It'd take too long to explain it all...
but it's the undeniable truth.
The Noah has stopped!
It wasn't completely destroyed either!
Fishman Island... has been saved!
Straw Hat did it!
Straw Hat!
We're saved!
Alright!
Straw Hat!
What a relief!
He did it!  Alright!
Fishman Island is saved.
However, after fighting so hard to save it,
Luffy is severely wounded and in great danger.
The citizens of Fishman Island,
captives of their past, are hesitant to help him.
When it seems like Luffy's life is about to end, a single man's actions will change history!
Next time, on One Piece:
To the Future!
The Path that Continues Toward the Sun!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!