It's not like we've seen
kono sekai no hate nante
the end of the world with our own eyes.
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
umi kara umi o mata ni kakete
in search of the greatest treasure of all...
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Everybody's laughing at us,
sonna no yumemonogatari da to
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
The beating of our hearts is our only compass.
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Editing
JulesMFinWinnfield
Just keep pretending that you know everything!
shitta kaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are nothing but guidelines.
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and your tears'll dry up someday...
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Raise your head, hoist the anchor!
kao o agero ikari o agero
...once the storm in your heart's passed by.
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm and clutch victory!
kaji tore saa kachitore
Once the winds of tomorrow start to blow...
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro ni wa
The sky is clear, so unfurl the sails and open your heart!
harebare ho o hare mune o hare
...I wanna meet somebody!
dareka ni aitaku narun da
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't pretend you can't see it.
mite minu furi suruna yo
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
It's not like we've seen
kono sekai no hate nante
the end of the world with our own eyes.
kono me de mita wake janai
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
dakara ikou ze amanojakku senchou
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
deki ya shinai koto tte nani
We haven't even started yet!
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I wanna know it all!  Now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima yes we can!
Yes, we can!  You can!  This moment...
yes we can! you can! kono shunkan
We can!  I can!  With this feeling of freedom...
we can! I can! kono kaikan
Now...  Now, oh yes, we can!
ima ima oh yes we can!
Honorable Chairman
Mao Sockdong
Yes, we can!
yes we can!
All pirates who seek One Piece strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the
Gomu Gomu Fruit and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Luffy and his friends departed Dress Rosa,
and were en route to their next destination, Zou.
Out of the blue, they were attacked by battle boats,
and Luffy was taken to an uncharted island,
Silver Mine, along with Bartolomeo.
Straw Hat, you'll be soon joining them.
This is where your voyage ends.
I'm a blast furnace man with the power of the Guzu Guzu Fruit.
My body is a white-hot blast furnace.
I can smelt ore and produce all kinds of things.
I'll turn you into a sublime silver statue,
befitting of a man worth five hundred million!
Their lives endangered by the leader of the Silver Pirate Alliance, Bill,
Fighting Desire, Bill's follower and Bartolomeo's childhood friend, Luffy's party falls into a mine shaft.
There, they learn the truth about Bill.
Shambles!
They defeated Bill's right-hand man, Peseta, with help from Zoro and the others,
and managed to return above ground,
only to confront Bill again.
What'd ya say?
Don't tell me yer the one that sank our boats that day...
That's right.
It was me.
It was me who sank you.
It was me who saved you.
I put on a hell of a show, didn't I?
And guess what?
Being the simple-minded fool that you were,
you took the bait hook, line, and sinker, and bought into my dream, becoming my loyal dog.
That's all there is to it.
You damned, dirty...
I ain't gonna let this go...
How dare ya...
take advantage o' our feelings?!
Your tears make me sick.
Desperate Situation
Luffy's Battle at Fever Pitch
Pathetic!  Oh, so pathetic!
Man, pirates are a hopeless bunch.
You guys really do believe in immature crap like dreams!
You're no better than kids.
But you were still pretty handy!
All I had to do was dangle a dream in front of you,
and that's all it took to hypnotize scum like you into serving me!
You bunch of goons unwittingly
worked your butts off around the clock,
all to bring me treasures and bounties that I'm going to use to live it up in the best way possible!
So then, what brought you here, Desire?
You said you wanted to "settle things", right?
Surely you don't think you can actually defeat me, do you?
What?!  You underestimate me!
Alrighty, then.  Bring it on!
Hey, what's wrong?  Huh?  Bring it on!
Well, if you're going to be that way,
I'll just smelt you first!
Straw Hat!
Man, you grind my gears.
Wait, he's-
Desire!
Let Luffy-senpai handle 'im.
Such pure eyes...
They make me want to throw up!
I'll turn you into mincemeat!
Attaboy!
He's so strong...
You ain't bringin' me down.
So this the strength of a man with a bounty of 500 million.
Bill!
Is that Desire?!
Why's she with Straw Hat and that other guy?
Y'all gotta listen to me!  Y'all been had by Bill-
Desire betrayed us!
She's joined sides with Straw Hat,
and wants to destroy the Silver Pirate Alliance!
She already took out Avelon and Peseta!
What'd you say?!
Then that means the Straw Hats attacked us because...
Desire masterminded it.
What're ya on about?!
Guys, don't let 'im fool yas!
That ain't gonna work, Desire.
I saw 'em with mah own eyes!  All our pals, abandoned by Bill,
slavin' away under this right here ground!
Come now, come now!  You're all part of my crew,
and you know I wouldn't do such a thing!
Down with the traitor!
Kill Straw Hat and that other guy!
How dare 'e say that an' feel no shame...
Well, saw that coming.
Let's roll!
They're all so naïve...
They'll die, as my shields.
Straw Hat, just 'member they's been hoodwinked!
Go easy on 'em!
There you are, Guzu Guzu.
No way!
Luffy-senpai!
Well, guess we'd better head back to the crew!
Okay!
H-He's somethin' else...
Quite pathetic of you to be defeated
by such a lowly pirate.
Was that as far as your greed took you?
I suppose this means the Monster of the New World
will be quite disappointed with you.
Should he cast you aside, it will mean your end.
The Monster of the New World...
The King of Greed that easily brought
my pirate crew to its knees with the power of money.
Seeing the face of those giving in to me...
Now that's entertainment.
If he...
...discards me...
Not yet!  It's not over yet!
Aren't you eating too much?
I suppose you know what you're doing.
Well then, let us see what you are capable of.
It's gettin' kinda hot!
Yeah, it is.
Still wanna fight?!
Huh?
What's goin' on?
The ground's...
There's a ton of 'em!
When will it end?!
One-Sword Style: 360-Pound Cannon!
Zoro!  Kin'emon!
Where's Straw Hatter?
We did meet with him!  However...
They said they wanted to handle everything on their own.
If we sit tight, they'll come.
Huh?!
How can he be so easygoing?
I'm just relieved to hear that they're fine.
What the... everything's melting!
What's up with that?
Is it even human?
It's Bill.
B-Bill?
I thought he was a blast furnace human!
He's s'posed ta be a Paramecia-type Devil Fruit user, ain't he?!
But that's more like Logia!
You won't get away!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
It's hotter 'n hell!
At this rate, th' whole island's gonna melt!
That's probably what 'e wants.
He wants t' smelt everythin' down, including us!
Eh?!
We'd better scram!
You're not going anywhere!
Barrier!
Behind us!
He's cuttin' off our way out!
I'll smelt everyone that's useless to me!
It's comin' in from the side, too!
Desire, you alright?!
L-Luffy-senpai!
Aw, crap!
Leggo my hand, Bartolomeo!
Ain't you gotta go help your hero Straw Hat become Pirate King?
Shaddup about that!  I ain't lettin' go!
You's mah pal!
Even if I was that rotten,
I wouldn' throw away a pal!
"Pal"?
Wait a sec, ya did toss me out once!
Huh, I did?
This is where you all die!
Oh man, that was too close!
Thanks!
Don't mention it!
I'll make up for not getting to you sooner by backing you up with everything I've got!
Go, go, Luffy-senpai!
Shaddap!
Hen-comb!
Can ya do somethin' about this hot stuff?
I'll handle it for you, of course!
Handle this if you can!
Bari-ability!
Big Hand!
That take care o' it?
Nope, not yet.
You worthless pirate scum...
I know something that none of you do.
Childish things like dreams...
won't help you...
...survive the New World!
Who cares about being the best?!
Or being Pirate King?!
I'm going to shatter those dreams!
Shut the hell up!
Gomu Gomu no...
Grizzly...
Magnum!
He did it!
Ah can't believe Ah fought next ta Luffy-senpai!
Mah wildest dreams came true!
Hey, look!
Why ain't things changed back?
All that molten metal Bill produced is made from real ore!
So it won't simply go away, even if you take him down!
Then how're we gonna get outta here?!
Like Ah'm s'posed ta know!
Hey, ain't that...
Hurry up!
Come on!
Alright, don't rush.
You're okay now!
You're lifesavers!
Hey!  Let us come aboard, too!
Get on already!
We gotta leave while we still can!
But Sis and the others aren't here yet!
We can't wait any longer!  Set sail!
Sis!
Th-Th-Th-That isn't a good sign, is it?!
Shouldn't we go help them?
Don't worry!
The Vivre Card's moving.  That means he's still okay.
This is nowhere near enough to take Luffy out.
Oh my, the island is sinking.
That's really not good!
Luffy-san and our captain are Devil Fruit users!
There they are!
Hey!
We's back!
Welcome back, you two!
Told ya!
This feels great!
Sis!
Hey, you gals!
Oh!  Glad they're okay!
Yous guys really saved our hides back there.
Dern tootin'!  Don't let 'chaselves be fooled by a bad guy 'gain, hear?
Oh, mah bad!
Oh, and...
If you ain't got nowhere else ta go,
"Make Luffy-senpai Pirate King" Group
Barto Club
Ah'll even letchas in the Barto Club.
We can hang out together like we used ta!
Come hang with us!
Bartolomeo...
Ah'll pass.  Ah'm not really a fan o' Straw Hat's.
Had enough o' ridin' in the back seat, 'sides.
From here on out, me 'n the gals're gonna be queens of the sea on our own strength!
That's our new dream!
Darn straight!
Don' push yer luck!
You ain't got no chance 'gainst Luffy-senpai!
I ain't gonna know 'til I try!
Yer gonna regret sayin' that!
Any idjit could tell ya don't!
You two are so funny!
Well, let's get goin'!
Huh?!
Wait!
Later, jerks.
Alright, we better get goin' too!
Aye, aye, Sis!
Take care!
See yas!
Alright, louts!  Set sail for Zou!
Aye, aye!
So that's Gran Tesoro...
This is where the Monster of the New World,
a man with power to rival that of the Celestial Dragons, lives.
The ore deposits at Silver Mine sank along with Bill, Tesoro-sama.
That so?  Well, no matter.
I've already had my fun with Bill.
The real entertainment begins now.
Dense fog and turbulent currents keep people away from the legendary island, Zou.
In a mysterious, millenium-old country where its native inhabitants, the Mink Tribe, reign supreme,
the curtain rises on Luffy's exciting new adventure!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Curtain Rises on a New Adventure
Arrival at the Phantom Island, Zou!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Curtain Rises on a New Adventure
Arrival at the Phantom Island, Zou!