It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew,
and then he broke into Navy HQ to save his brother Ace from imminent execution...
but his efforts were in vain.
The curtain was closed on the war.
Ace... died, didn't he?!
Yes, he's dead.
Ace!
The Great War of Marineford scarred the hearts of many people.
Ten years earlier, in East Blue...
The small Windmill Village.
The people in this village live in peace, but behind it...
lies a place where no one dares to set foot, Mt. Corvo.
Only the strong can survive there.
The weak only find death in this place.
Like I said, Granddad...
I'm gonna be the Pirate King...
What do you mean, "Pirate King"?!
L-Let go of me, dammit!
Not only did you eat that Devil Fruit, but now you're spouting nonsense as well!
Luffy, both you and Ace..
are destined to become great marines!
Dammit... I'm made of rubber, why does this hurt?!
Please let go, Granddad!
Leaving you in that peaceful Windmill Village was a mistake!
Of all things, the Pirate King?!
Yeah!
You imbecile!
Becoming friends with that damn Red Hair Shanks is completely unacceptable!
I'm gonna become...
as strong as Shanks is!
Hey!
What's this place?
So annoying!
Who's the reckless daredevil?!
It's me.
G-Garp-san!
You seem to be doing well.
You've gotta be kidding me!  Seriously, I wish you'd just leave me alone for a change!
That Ace is already ten years old, you know!
Is he?  Has it really been that long?
How's he doing?
It's nothing to laugh at!
If he gets any wilder, we won't be able to control him at all!
Just take him with you!
Anyway...
Don't just change the subject like that!
Sheesh, that kid's so distracting!
Take care of him too.
Now, come on, Luffy.  Say hello.
Heya.
Who's that kid?
He's my grandson.
What?!
We've gotta take care of another one?!
Garp's... I mean...
Garp-san's grandson?!
Not happening!
Well, you have to make a decision.
Do you want to spend your life behind bars...
or will you raise him?
I've turned a blind eye so far, but you've committed as many crimes as there are stars in the sky.
No way!
Well, true, I don't wanna go to prison...
But sometimes prison actually seems tempting...
Our hands are full with just Ace!
And now you want us to take your grandson too?!
I'm sure that kid's just as much of a monster, isn't he?
What a crappy-looking mountain hut!
You want to die, you brat?!
He's not listening!
Boss!
Are you alright?
What was that?
It's spit!  Nasty!
Who's there?!
Hey! You!
Apologize! That's gross!
Oh!  Ace!
You're back, Ace!
Hey!  Apologize!
Luffy.  That's Ace.
He's three years older than you.
Starting today, you'll be living with these people.
You just decided that by yourself?!
Try to get along!
You think this is settled?!
What?!
We'll take care of him!
Then my business here is done.
I'll come to visit when I have time.
Ummm... What about child support?
Put it on my tab.
This ain't no bar, y'know...
Huh?!
You're always welcome here!
Hey, Boss!  What are we gonna do with another one to take care of?
Well, first let's have something to eat!  Go cook something up!
Apologize!
Wait!
I'm entrusting you with this hat.
Where'd he go?
Who the hell are you?!
Let go of me!
If you don't wanna die, then fork over your cash!
I don't have any money!
Then call your parents and make 'em bring some cash!
I've only got Granddad...
Then call your Gramps here!
What's your Gramps's name?
Garp-san.
This kid is...
He's gonna live with us from now on.
Why did you take him?!
This isn't a nursery school, you know!
Boss, you're totally gutless!
Shut it, you scumbags!
It's time for dinner!
Hey, give me that!
It's my meat!
I want some meat too!
Didn't you eat already?!
It wasn't enough!
I won't lose to this kid!
Don't be greedy!
It's survival of the fittest.
His hand stretched!
A dog?
It's your turn to do the dishes!
Another bowl!
Pops, I want another bowl!
I'm a woman!
And don't you realize where you've been left?!
No.
Then I'll tell you.
This is the hideout of the mountain bandits who rule Mt. Corvo, the Dadan Family!
Mountain bandits?
I hate those guys!
Shut it, you damn brat!
It's already a pain in the ass raising you!
If you don't want to be here, that's fine by us!
Just go somewhere and die like an animal!
Now, now, Boss...
I'm still hungry...
I want some of that meat...
I'll have you know, this is all buffalo meat that Ace brought us.
He shares it with us so he gets to sit at our table.
The life of a mountain bandit is harsh.
Starting tomorrow, we'll work you half to death!
Cleaning.
Laundry.
Shoe polishing and weapon polishing!
Theft, looting, swindling and killing!
And listen... you're not gonna say a single word to Garp about the stuff we make you do!
One bowl of rice and one glass of water a day!
That's all I'm giving you.
Anything else, you'll have to get for yourself.
You'll have to raise yourself to be strong.
Alright.
You're fine with it?!
You should be crying by now!
Granddad threw me into the jungle once.
Earthworms, frogs, snakes, mushrooms...
If this is a forest, then there's plenty of stuff to eat!
Besides, I'm gonna be a pirate someday!
So I've gotta deal with at least this much!
Boss!
Are you alright?
What are you doing?!
And... pull!
Where's he going?
And where are you going?!
Wait... did you say "pirate"?!
Dammit, he's not listening at all!
Hey!
You see?!  He's way too stubborn!
That's why I don't want to raise Garp's grandkid!
Calm down, Boss.
Hey!
Wait up!
I'm Luffy!  I'm not angry that you spat on me anymore!
Why are you all laughing?!
He just spilled some booze on me.  It's nothing to get all worked up about.
It's nothing to get worked up about!  Let's be friends!
Are you going somewhere?
A dead end?!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Hey!  Ace has returned!
Food!
Ace, you came back alone?
What about... Luffy?
Wasn't he with you?
Hell if I know.
Where is he, and what's he up to?
Maybe he's dead?
If he is, Garp's gonna kill us.
Boss won't be too happy, either...
Pull yourself together, Boss!
What'd you say?
Listen to me, won't it look bad that he went missing the first day he got here?!
Leave me alone!  If he died, he's dead, nothing we can do about it!
Garp-san is gonna kill us.
Why do we have to look after Garp-san's grandson in the first place?
This isn't a kindergarten, dammit!
He should look after his own grandson!
So why didn't you tell him that?
What was that?!
If Gold Roger had a child?
He'd be beheaded, no doubt about it!
His last words should be something like this:
"I'm so sorry I was born!  I'm just garbage!"
Besides, I've had enough of that Ace, too!
In my opinion, it'd be best if he just went somewhere and died.  Then we could tell Garp it was an accident!
This is what they mean by "A devil's child has a devil's luck".
He is the child of a devil, too.
Just think about what'd happen if the government found out!
What do you think would happen to us?
Now, now, Boss...
Don't you think you've had too much to drink?
One week later...
Mmmm... Shut up already...
Be quiet...
Boss!  Boss Dadan!
Who is...
Who's there?
It's you!
That Luffy came back!
This kid...
He's still alive?!
You little...
Now, now, Boss...
Where the hell did you go?!
Now, now... Where were you, and what were you doing?
I was being chased around by wolves at the bottom of the valley.
The bottom of the valley?!  Why'd you go down there?!
Well, in any case, good thing he's safe.
The hell it is!  This just means that the troublemaker has returned!
Go to sleep for now!  We're putting you to work tomorrow!
That was fast!
Heya!
You going out somewhere again today, Ace?
Take me with you!  Let's be friends!
Wait!
Boss!  He's chasing after Ace again!
Hey!  You're supposed to be doing chores!
Don't wanna!
The damn kid won't listen to me at all!
Now, now, Boss...
Get your ass in gear and bring him back!
Right...
Hey!
Ace!
Ace!  Let's be friends!
Day eight...
Ace!
Wait!
Boss...
Work, you little brat!
There's no point in talking to him...
Get him back here!
Right...
I won't lose sight of you today!
I can do that too!
Let's be friends!
Ten days pass...
Luffy!
He left ages ago...
Go look for him!
Right...
He kept chasing, but he could never catch up.
Even so, day after day...
Ace!
One month...
Two months...
Ace!
On rainy days...
And windy days...
Ace!
Luffy kept desperately chasing after Ace.
Luffy went chasing after Ace's butt again?
I can't believe he hasn't learned yet, after all the trouble he's gotten into.
I wish he wouldn't make me worry so much!
You're worried?
Of course not!  Don't be ridiculous!
I got hit by a beehive...
Who are you?
Ace!
Hey!
He followed me all the way here... What a persistent guy...
Not good!
Damn!  I lost him again.
Ace sure is good!
Ace, is that you?
The king of Mt. Corvo!  That kid doesn't stand a chance on his own!
Why aren't you running?!
You'll be eaten!
M-My legs won't... listen to me!
He's...
Luffy's relentless pursuit had lasted more than three months...
I'm out of the forest!
What is this place?
Smoke rises from the piles of discarded trash.
The village where outcasts gather, the Gray Terminal.
There, Ace steals from the outlaws, gathering funds for when he becomes a pirate...
together with another companion...
Next time, on One Piece:
Sabo Appears!
The Boy from the Gray Terminal
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!