All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After the Straw Hat crew departed Punk Hazard,
they were attacked by Breed, a mysterious man who could subjugate sea creatures
who kidnapped Caesar as the crew was heading for Dress Rosa.
In order to retrieve Caesar, Luffy, Law and Chopper infiltrated the enemy ship.
There they happily reunited with a Kung-Fu Dugong from Alabasta, who idolized Luffy as his master.
Pull your arm way back, and strike!
Lower your hips!
Due to the effects of Breed's Peto Peto Fruit,
the sea creatures couldn't rebel.
Now, Chopper, Luffy and Law have all been caught by his mysterious ability.
Peto Peto!
Oh no!
Any living creature is at my beck and call!
I can draw out every last bit of strength they possess!
It's time you learned how terrifying that power can be!
Luffy Dies at Sea!?
The Pirate Alliance Crumbles
Dammit, it won't come off!
Luffy, get out of the way!
My body won't listen!
Dammit!
Look out!
Stop!
Chopper stopped!
You were merely bait.
From the start, I was after you guys.
What did you say?!
Stop!
Huh?  My body won't move!
Room!
Stop!
You guys will be my slaves for the rest of your lives.
I have nothing to fear
as long as you two are under my control.
Straw Hat.  Trafalgar.
Sit!
Hand!
Dammit!
This is my power, the ability of the Peto Peto Fruit.
One of the Seven Warlords and a
400 million bounty head are nothing before my power.
I normally make animals into my pets,
but you stinking humans are my slaves!
How cute!
I didn't realize it earlier because you were in that weird transformed state,
but you're so cute, little blue-nosed raccoon dog-kun!
You're an all new type of pet.
Let's go dress you up right now.
Stop it!
There, there.
Hey, what the hell are you doing to Chopper!
Shut up!  You guys are going to the cells!
Put some Sea Stone handcuffs on them.
Soon.
Soon I will be able to create the kingdom I desire!
Hey Peto, let me outta here!
Give Chopper back dammit!
You...
As I thought, this cage is made of...
Sea Stone.
Well, aren't you guys just pathetic.
Caesar.
Hey, open this cage!
Shut up!
Everyone's trying to order me around!
Did you fall for his ability as well?
Yeah, I've got both a collar and a leash.
It's as if I'm a pet!
I'm a genius scientist!
He said he has the Peto Peto Fruit ability.
Once he gives an order, we are forced to obey it.
Caesar, is he working with Doflamingo?
Huh?!
Are you an idiot?
Do you think I would I still be tied up if he was?
As far as I know,
that guy isn't one of Doflamingo's subordinates.
Rambling on about
making a kingdom and what not.
What kingdom?
As if I'd know!
Dammit!
How humiliating,
for me to be ordered around by that arrogant bastard!
Don't screw with me, damn you!
Caesar, lie down!
Lie down, Caesar!  I know you can hear me!
Dammit, I'll never forgive him!
None of you will ever escape from me.
Now...
I'm all ready.
How should I use you guys?
Peto!
Give Chopper bac...
You stinking humans never learn.
No need to worry, Chappy is right here.
Chappy?
Chappy!
My name's not Chappy!
Chopper!
Chappy.
My name is Chopper!
What's with those clothes, Chopper?
Don't laugh, Luffy!
Because of the Rumble Ball, my body...
Did all that dressing up tire you out?
Stop it.
My oh my, aren't you in a bad mood.
Let go of me!
Luffy...
Don't push your luck.
I've been nice to you so far.
So submit to my demands!
Are you okay Chopper?
Yeah.
Get down on your knees, Chappy.
With more respect!
It's time to teach you a lesson.
Stop it!
I told you to stop it!
What are you doing to my crewmate?!
Crewmate...  Crewmate?  Crewmate?
Crewmate!  Crewmate!  Crewmate?!
Screw crewmates!
They can't be trusted.
They aren't worth anything.
Listen!  What I need
are submissive pawns that do everything I say.
Tools!
I have no use for people that disobey me.
Just shut up and do what I say!
Stinking humans don't obey me!
People like that aren't my crewmates.  I don't need them!
But animal pets are good!
They silently obey all of my commands!
Animals and pets are the best!
That's why I need you, Caesar.
In order to make this.
That's... a Smile!  Where did you get your hands on that?
I, too, have connections to the underworld.
Using this artificial Devil Fruit
that turns people into Zoan-type users...
I will force all humans to turn into animals.
That way all of the despicable stinking humans will disappear from this world.
Just what are you planning?!
A kingdom.
I'm going to make an kingdom of animals
where there isn't a single stinking human.
And then I'll use my Peto Peto ability to subjugate all the animals!
I'll turn all of them into submissive pets!
That's the kingdom of my dreams.
Suit yourself.
But I'll never obey anyone.
Huh, what are on about?
Do you still not understand
the power of the Peto Peto Fruit?!
That doesn't matter!
You stupid stinking human!
You stinking humans
just need to shut up and listen to my orders.
Don't resist me!
I'm a pirate!
I don't take orders from anyone.
Pirates are free!
Pirates are free?
I hate humans like you the most.
Very well, I was gonna let you live as a slave.
But I guess all you stinking humans should die!
What is this place?
Show time.
I'll show you the power of the Peto Peto Fruit.
Now Trafalgar, this is an order.
Kill Straw Hat.
Traf!
Straw Hat, you kill Trafalgar!
Dammit!
Oh no!
This is crazy!
Now, kill each other.  No abilities.
Just punch each other to death like idiotic stinking humans!
Now, let the public death match begin!
Luffy, Law!
No way!
Traf... I can't... my body won't listen to me.
Dammit!
Good!  This show is great!
Dammit, my body won't stop!
Even though I don't want to fight you!
Stay away from me!
Kill each other, you stinking humans!
The leash.
Keep fighting!
Slowly... Stealthily... I'm outta here!
What an idiot.
Doesn't he understand
that he can't run away from me?
Well, I'll let him run around for a bit.
Right now, I wanna see this public death match.
Seal, look out!
Hey, don't get in the way!
Do you want to be whipped?!
Huh!
What do you want, you're annoying me!
You little!
Don't tell me that you're rebelling against me?
You little shit!
Damn you!  Damn you!  Damn you!
You little...
Stop it!
Dugong!
Do you want to save these guys so much?
Then I guess I'll stop.
Straw Hat, Trafalgar, stop!
I stopped.
In exchange...
you kill them!
It'll be much more fun seeing you kill them, seeing how you love them so much!
Kill them both, Dugong!
Now go!
That's just too cruel!
I'll be okay, Seal.
Now do you know what happens if you defy me?
Now throw them into the ocean!
Seal, didn't I tell you to lower your hips
and pull your arms back?
You really have gotten stronger.
Just when it seems that Luffy and Law's luck
has run out, leaving them in a desperate situation,
an unimaginable miracle occurs!
Next time, on One Piece:
Great Reversal!
Luffy's Anger Filled Fist Explodes
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Great Reversal!
Luffy's Anger Filled Fist Explodes