Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
To defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and invaded Dress Rosa.
Luffy joined a battle tournament to win the Mera Mera Fruit...
and made it through the preliminary round.
Now he's heading toward the palace to rescue Law from Doflamingo.
Leave the destruction of the factory to us!
Everyone, be careful.
Got it.
Both Traf's life...
...and Rebecca's wishes...
They're both in his hands.
We're heading to the palace.
We're gonna send Doflamingo flying!
In the Colosseum, the final round is underway.
Meanwhile, the Tontattans are trying to carry out Operation SOP, but...
Cyborg Franky has been brought down!
U... Usopp... You can do it.
Hurry and create some panic!
Don't worry, young master.
The enemy isn't even conscious anymore.
Usoland!
You can have this poisoned grape back.
The tatababasco...
That was our only hope!
You eat it...
and die.
The Legend Reborn!
Kyros' All-Out Attack
As soon as Sugar faints...
all the toys in the country will become big folk again.
All his evil deeds exposed, the true nature of the pirate Doflamingo will become clear.
What move will Doflamingo make?
What move will the Navy make?
What will the people of the country think, and what actions will they take?
Will they be overcome with rage and start rioting?
Will they give up and surrender to Doflamingo?
Or will they...
join us in our fight?
Su-
Sugar fainted!
I'm back to normal!
I don't believe it!
What's going on?  Where are these people coming from?!
The toys are...
It keeps getting bigger!
I'm back!
What is that?!
Bastard...
How dare you exploit me like that?!
Brother, no violence-!
Oh.  I stopped the wrong person.
You piece of shit!
Flapper?
Leo!
Leo!  I'm so glad!
Finally...
Operation SOP has succeeded!
Sugar!  Come on, wake up!
Sugar!
Hey!  Hey!
This is terrible!
What's that commotion about?
What?
What is going on here?
What?!
It turned into a weird old man!
What's happening to me?!
I'm back to normal!
Wait!
S-Sugar is... Doffy, I'm so sorry!
Quiet down, Trébol!
What about Sugar?
S-She's...
been knocked...
unconscious!
What?  What's going on?
Sugar has been knocked out?!
Hey...
Are you kidding me?!
All the workers we've gathered over the past ten years...
are reverting to humans!
The Hobby Hobby curse is being lifted!
The Tontattans' plan was successful!
See?  I told you Usopp could do it!
Young master, the Colosseum...
I'm back to normal!
Who are you?!
I remember!
What on earth is going on here?!
Um, I mean...
What could be happening?!  The toys...
The toys are turning into humans!
No, some of them aren't even human!
Don't tell me Sugar has been...
Our ten years of work...
Sugar has been defeated by somebody -in!
That little brat is pathetic.
But...
I hope she's not hurt.
You say such cold things, but you're really worried about her!
So hard-boiled!
Royal palace, please respond!
Everyone's calling in with emergencies!
Urgent report from the southern district, Sebio!
The toys assigned to work at the port have turned into pirates!
This is the eastern district, Carta!
The toys have become former Dress Rosa soldiers!
Government workers!
Marines!
Officials from foreign countries!
Giant beasts!
Reporting from the Primula District!
They're real!
Young master!
I'm human again!
I'm so happy!
Hang in there, Usopp!
Usoland!
Thanks to you, we were able to become human again.
We did it...
Operation SOP is a success!
Everyone's so happy to be human again.
What's wrong, Onepoco?
Mommy, Onepoco's acting strange.
Onepoco!
One... poco?
No, you're...
I'm back!
Dear!
Papa!  You're not Onepoco!
That's right, I'm your papa!
Papa!
How could we have forgotten you all this time?
It was a curse.  I was afraid I'd spend my whole life as a toy!
Daddy, lift me up!
Of course!
Up you go!
Damn, he's hiding again!
Where'd you go, stone man?!
Usopp... Gnomes...
It looks like Operation Sugar Oversurprise Panic...
was a super success!
Hang in there, Usopp!
Usoland!
I... I can't...
Usoland!  Please wake up!
Don't die!  You can't die!
Usoland is dead!
Everyone!
Um...
I'm... alive...
Usolan... d?
The hero lives!
Usopp!
Usoland, we can't thank you enough!
It all... went just as planned.
So cool!
Now... my crew will handle the rest.
The battle... has only just begun.
Alright!
Help!
Run!
You!
Who are you?
I'm Onepoco, the toy you kept pushing around!
Carry the damn box, Onepoco!
That was you?!
You're gonna pay for...
...ordering me around like a slave!
I'll never forgive you for this!
Royal palace, please send reinforcements!
The pirates are-
Hey!
We're not done rioting just yet!
Men, slaughter Doflamingo's underlings!
Hey, what's wrong?!  Answer me!  Hey!
How dare you be so rough with me?!
You bastard!
Esta...
I just remembered...
What?
I have a boyfriend!
What?!
You betrayed me!
I'm sorry!  I didn't remember!
I've been forgotten for ten years!  I'm gonna kill Doflamingo!
Take down Doflamingo!
Doflamingo tricked us all!
What are they talking about?  He's a great king.
You don't know what he's really like.
He's the devil himself!
Kill Doflamingo!
Come out, Doflamingo!
We'll teach him how much we've suffered these ten years!
What's going on here, Isshou-san?
Seems the tide has turned.
This country was covered by a much deeper darkness than I thought.
Huh?  Darkness?
It's time to paint the ground...
...with the blood of Doflamingo's men!
I'm so beautiful!
We're gonna reclaim the country!
Bring down Doflamingo!
Those wretches!
Soldier-san is valiant...
and he will always watch over you.
I couldn't remember him...
King Riku, it's me, Kyros!
Kyros?
That's right!
I'm sorry.  I've never heard that name before.
But now I remember it all!
Who's that?!
Kyros!
I'd forgotten all about him.
What are you talking about?
Huh?  Where's the tin soldier?
That's him.
Huh?  But that's a human!
All the toys used to be human.  They'd been erased from our memories!
Now that Sugar has been defeated, our memories have returned!
He is the former captain of the Riku Royal Army...
Kyros!
The mightiest warrior in the history of the Colosseum!
Isn't he the guy on that statue?
Yes, that's him.  And he's also...
Rebecca's father!
Huh?  But she said she'd never met him!
All these years while he'd been forgotten,
he had no way of telling her who he really was!
He's been watching over his beloved daughter for a decade!
He's stayed by her side every single day as a toy soldier!
Who are you?!
It's you!
Kyros?!
Yes!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting for ten years!
I'm here to save you!
I've come to restore the true Dress Rosa!
Kyros has taken down Doflamingo.
As an unprecedented shock runs through the royal palace,
the Colosseum battle approaches its intense climax.
The battle for the Mera Mera Fruit finally reaches its conclusion!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Fire Fist Explodes!
The Power of the Mera Mera Fruit Reborn
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Fire Fist Explodes!
The Power of the Mera Mera Fruit Reborn