Look, there you are, my love, waiting in front of me.
Our long journey has just begun
Courage, love, friendship
and a little bit of playfulness,
these are the things will hold on to forever
We are all fragments of the Earth
coming together and little by little,
taking form
And the wind will keep on blowing
(Yeah)
Feel the wind, you got to feel the wind
Let's look to the wind to dry our tears
It's such an adventure, to meet someone
We won't stop
Look, there you are, my love, waiting in front of me
Every time you shed your tears, you get stronger
Every time you shed your tears, the memories
grow, and grow, and grow
(Yeah)
Feel the wind, you got to feet the wind
Let's look to the wind to dry our tears
It's such an adventure, to meet someone
We won't stop
Look, there you are, my love, waiting in front of me.
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind
by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate Gum-Gum fruit.
also takes to the sea to
becomd the next King of Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is
less and less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy and others had been captured by Largo,
captain of the Amigo Pirates, with his Net-Net power.
Even if you are a rubberman,
I will not let you get away with it, senor!
But Boss, the big beetle, tried to
sacrifice himself to save the island...
Wait!
Can't you hear what I'm saying!
Boss, after shedding his skin, then
burned down the nets which held Luffy and the others.
Oh no! It was too soon to shed his skin as I thought!
Crying or screaming won't help anymore!
We got your guardian angel as you see!
It's not over yet!
We won't let his last breath...
...be wasted.
Thank you, Giant beetle!
Now, it's showtime!
"A Special Presentation related to the Movie!
Luffy vs. Largo - The Battle is on!"
What can three burned men and
some weak sea idiots with pathetic weapons do...
...at this last moment?!
It's obvious! We want the Giant Beetle!
Boss!
Give him back!
You guys...
Go ahead, make my day!
Zoro! Cut that net!
Okay.
How stupid are you?
You know that your sword is too dull to cut my net.
We'll see about that!
Lion Strike!
No way!
We gotta fight, too!
Wait a minute!
Second Gear!
Sanji! Shoot me over there!
Alright!
Get ready, Net Man!
Why should I?
Armee de L' Air Assault Gum Shoot!
Jet Bullet!
Get the rest!
Alright!
Big Bro got taken down?
No, he was just off-guard!
He can't have been beaten by that kid!
To be recognized by Big Boss Shiki...
Did you get hurt, maybe a bit?
Now I remember!
That straw hat!
You have a 300 million berry price on your head...
You're Monkey D. Luffy, aren't you?
Yes, I am!
It's hard for me to take a young man's life
but the sweet sound of your death cry will be worth 300 million to me.
Mucho Burning Net!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Lance!
Mucho Sticky Net!
The jungle is a poor place to fight!
I need to get out of here!
Bastard! He's running away!
Of course! That's why they call it "weak sea!"
People from the East Blue are quick at running away!
No, A smart lady, from the East Blue figured that...
...two of us are enough to beat you all.
Hey! Why are we running?!
We're all ready to kick their butt!
Ouch! Don't be stupid!
You can't confront them!
He's right!
You can only do what you are capable of at times like these...
...even if that means using your brain!
You! Hurry up!
Don't tell me what to do, Pirate!
Do you want them to have
the beetle and the island?!
If not, you have to do as I say!
Are you sure...
Are you sure that I'll get Boss back
if I go along with you?!
Yes!
Are you ready now?!
Yeah!
We're all in agreement?!
You two are enough for us?
What a big mouth!
The only thing they've got going for them is their numbers.
Do you want me to protect you?
Are you kidding me?
You just watch your own ass!
Guys! Let's...
...Get them!
--W-What happened?!
Don't mess with us!
Fool! Aw!
Get out of here!
What are they doing?!
Take that!
Surprised?
The caves here are all connected to
different parts of the island.
It was a waste to just use them as an escape route
for when an enemy comes!
Alright, get down everybody!
Thunder Bolt..
...Tempo!
Oh no!
Let's get them all at once!
What's going on here?!
Stop it!
Sure Kill Egg Star!
Augh! It stinks!
Nice!
They're great!
You think you can make a fool out of me?!
You can't get away with it!
What the hell?!
I'll kill you all!
Oh no!
Boss!
Screw you!
Out of bullets?!
What have you done?!
As a requiem for my brother,
I will take your life!
Here on the beach, with an expansive view,
you'll find it hard to elude me, I'm sure!
Oh yeah? But I'm sure you can't beat me!
How stupid you are!
Bring it on, senor!
Oh? What's going on there?!
-It's Luffy!
...Seems like he's fighting.
Jet Pistol!
No shock! Net Body!
W-What's that?!
Sorry! your attack won't hurt me anymore!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
It's not working! How long are you going to do that?!
Until you get blown away!
Luffy's attack isn't working!
He must be a Devil Fruit eater!
That's not good.
Alright, let's finish it up.
This is for my brother!
A requiem of a death cry!
Mucho Mucho...
...Full Net Body!
-Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
Now, you're captured
You will never break this net!
What now?!
It is a submarine, isn't it?
It's being used as a pirate ship?!
Looks like it.
Now, I have a prize worth 300 million berries!
Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
W-What are you...?!
Stop it!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
Buy DVD or BD, it's worth every Penny.
www.FUNiSUB.co.cc
Oh no!
Augh! Luffy!
I got it!
I'm coming to save you, Luffy-san!
What?
Oh, wait - I seem to have forgotten I can't swim!
I thought I'd die here!
Even though I'm already dead!
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
Ow, ow, ouch! What do you think you're doing?!
You bastard! A few minutes ago,
you could barely breathe fire!
I can't take it! Let's fight right now!
No! Wait until I get down!
Ah no!
Ow, ow, ow... You bastard!
-Those two...
--Ow, nice one!
Are they gonna fight forever?
Dunno.
You haven't won yet!
Dad...
There you are.
Can I join?
Why are you here?
I heard there was an orange plantation so...
What a view!
My dad used to love this place.
And so did I.
Look, Yoko!
This is my favorite place in the whole world!
Yeah! I love this place, too!
I realty really love it!
Yeah? You really love it?
Burn everything up!
Take all the treasure and food!
Kill all who resist!
Dad! Dad!
Yoko!
Hurry and escape from this island!
No I won't! Because I love this island!
I love the view from the orange plantation!
You said that you love it, too!
You're right.
You save...
...t-this island from now on.
Dad!
Together with the island...
...live strongly!
I was like you.
I really hated pirates.
What?
Then, why did you become one?
Well... I m not sure why.
Nami!
You're one of us now!
Uh-huh!
But Luffy is not the kind of pirate that you think he is.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Let's make it clear which one of us is stronger!
Shut up! I don't care!
I just wanna fight him!
Is that it?!
Yeah, I think I see what you mean.
Yeah?
Uh-huh.
He's too stupid naive to be a pirate.
I agree.
It's quiet. Did they finish fighting?
Oh yeah,
I wonder how Boss did.
What do you say? Do you give up?
He says "No, I won!"
What?!
Alright, that's it!
It's time to go back to the sea!
What're you talking about, Nami?!
We're not through yet!
It seems like it only takes a half day
to record the magnetic wave of this island.
So we better go now before it resets.
Nami-sama!
Luffy!
Thank you for saving our island!
No problem!
Giant Beetle! I'll be back someday so,
let's continue where we left off!
Promise me!
I thought that they were specialists in trapping.
But I m afraid we've lost touch with the Amigo Pirates,
It seems as though it was impossible for them
to defeat the monster that you created.
However, one escapee doesn't affect
the execution of my plan at all.
Those monsters will help me to conquer the world!
Let's declare war against the whole world!
Shiki the Golden Lion's supreme plan will begin!
Ji ha ha ha...