Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
The crew received a distress call and landed on Punk Hazard,
a bizarre island that is split
between burning and frozen sides.
Sink, Devil Fruit users!
Cut the crap.  Let us into the laboratory!
I'm the only one here.
If Straw Hat shows up, you can have his head.
But if that's all you want here, then you should leave!
I'm out!
One!
Two!
Three!
Super!
The Straw Hats... and children?!
We got out of the building!  We can go home!
And you!
Of all the atrocious fiends to run into... it's Smoker!
And with him is always a cutie-swaaan!
This isn't good!  We've run into the Navy!
We can't go this way!  We'll have to find another exit!
Hurry back inside!
What's the Navy doing here?!
How should I know?!  Anyway, run!
Quickly kids!  Through to the other side!
There's gotta be a back door!
Soldiers!  We will capture the Straw Hats!
No way!
A Huge Jam
Luffy Sinks in the Icy Lake
The Lake at the Center of Punk Hazard Island
- Luffy's Group -
Fire!
Aim directly below their boat!
W-We've gotta retreat!
What are you talking about, Usopp?!
Forward!
You don't understand the situation at all, do you?!
Those guys are trying to sink us into the lake!
You cannot escape from me, Brownbeard-sama!
Huh?  Who?
Don't pretend that you don't know me!
I'm a former pirate
whose bounty was 80,060,000 beli!
Brownbeard-sama!
Brownbeard-sama!  -sama!  -sama!  -sama!  -sama!
We've never heard of you!
Those ignorant bastards!
Take my attack of rage!
Dammit!  They...
We're falling!
Oh no!
Alright!  We did it!
That's Boss for ya!
He capsized their boat!
Have you learned your lesson?
Now you can struggle all you like,
until you sink to the ocean floor!
Aaaah!  It's so cold!
More than a few minutes here and we'll become icicles!
Dammit!
My powuh'th fadin'...
Y-You had plenty of time to fight back, Luffy!
But you kept on saying such dumb things.
So... you should be more careful what...
Sowwy... It'th awright...
I dun' wanna make'em my friendth anymo'...
Alright, finish them off!
Ready!
Hey, Usopp!
Take both of them for me!
I'm gonna slice'em up!
H-Hurry... I'm almost...
I'll finish this quickly!
Hey!  What's wrong, Zoro?!
Sharks!  Why are there sharks in the lake?!
You fool!  This is technically the ocean!
This hole was ground zero of the fight
between Aokiji and Akainu.
Cracks tore right through the island,
so sea water flowed in and made this lake!
Of course there are ocean creatures here!
Zoro!
Sharks!  Scary!  Sharks!
Zoro got eaten by sharks!
Aim carefully!  They can't do anything now!
They're everywhere!  We're doomed!
Blast them to smithereens!
Why?!  I never imagined my life would end like this!
This is the end!
Fire!
What?!  What happened?!
Brook!
Most frigid of winds,
cuts colder than the arctic.
Feel the underworld.
Damn you, you filth!
Ah, I did not have time to warn you.
I froze your gunbarrels...
so if you shoot, they will explode in your faces!
Who are you, skeleton-mask?!
You are unworthy to hear my name.
It's Brook.
You still told it to me?
I returned from the underworld,
and dedicated my second life
to my captain with the straw hat!
I am known as the Soul King!
When did he pull that trick with our guns?!
We won't let you get away with this, you damn-
"Won't let you get away with this?"
That's my line!
Damn you!
How dare you?!
I will not lose my crewmates a second time!
Only ice!
Damn he's fast!  He's too strong!
I didn't think they had other allies!
But even if you fight all you want, it's useless!
They're already shark bait!
See?  Just look for yourself!
The sharks have all been killed!
Hey!  Where did they go?!
Here!
You came at a perfect time, Brook.
I'm glad you're alright!
As it happens, I was chased here by a strange fellow...
You've really done it now,
you half-man half-beast freaks!
Do you really think my training was so weak...
that I'd die to something as trivial as sharks?!
But... the human body... can't train against the cold...
Freezing... I'm turning into ice!
I told you... you guys...
that trying to cross the frozen lands...
in these clothes...
But look... We're in luck.
We should be thankful... that we met them.
Boss!  We won't let them take another step!
Wait!  There's something familiar about these guys!
That one will do...
I'm going with the fourth guy from the right!
I've decided...  I'll take the one next to him!
I'll take that one...
The one that girl at the far left is wearing...
What are they saying?
Those clothes look so warm!
Alright, go!
Get one for me, too!
Are they... coming for our coats?!
How crude!  What are they, highwaymen?
Now I remember!  It's that hat!
That's one of the rookies
from the Worst Generation two years ago!
That's right... He's Fire-Fist's little brother!
The pirate worth four hundred million, Straw Hat Luffy!
F-Four hundred million?!
What?!  What is that?!
Nooooo!
Gimme...
that coat!
It's better for your health if you don't resist!
I'll go a little easier on you!
Oh, everyone!
You're in much better shape
than I thought you would be!
Help me!
Laboratory ・ The Main Entrance
Look, Smo-san!
This is why I didn't want to mess with that guy!
What are we going to do now?!
Hurry!
This way, children!
We've gotta find the back door!
Wait!
Go back!
It was that man!  It was he who cut me down!
What?  Really?!
So does he have your body?
No... he most likely does not, however...
Then this can wait until later!
Please, wait!  He might know something!
Our first priority is to find a backdoor!
We're not going back to meet the Navy!
I don't see any doors that look promising!
Where is the backdoor?!
Alright! Super-let me take care of it!
Ooh!  Do you have a sensor or something installed?
No I do not!
Then don't take the lead!
The samurai was with them.
Hurry!
I can't let the Straw Hats escape, either.
What's this?!
It's like some sort of thin film or something.
What was that?  It felt weird...
I guess that's not important right now!
Now hurry and run, damn kids!
Huh?  Did I drop my cigarette?
Follow me!
What's this?
Sheesh, what are you doing now, Sanji-kun?!
I'm particularly super this week!  Finding a backdoor will be easy!
Guys?
Is there something wrong with you?
Huh?  Like what?
Come to think of it, my chest feels light...
What's happened?!
I don't believe it!
My chest is so heavy!
Huh?  I've turned into a human!
Did I just... turn into a raccoon dog without...
E-Everyone, calm down!
I know!  Let's do a roll call!
Chopper!
Yeah!
Franky!
Present!
Sanji-kun!
What?
N-Nami-san?
It's Nami... right?
Yeah.
What is going on here?!
Law, you...
What is your goal?
Give us back our ship!
Sure.
Seriously?!
Although, I can't let you have it the way it is.
It's falling!
Run!
Pull back, Vice-Admiral!
His power is just too damn creepy!
We can't fight this guy!
I can't allow a single one of you to escape.
He attached it to the bedrock of the island?!
He reshaped the ship into some weird object!
Dammit!  Without the ship, we can't get back to base!
The Warlords report to the Government!
Attacking us is against the rules, you know!
Trafalgar!
I'll report this to HQ!
You'll be stripped of your position!
No need to worry.
What's this?!  Cut it out!
Huh?  Snail Phones?
What?  It's gone!
No way... Mine too?!
Those are ours!
He took all our Snail Phones!
I cannot let you report anything you've seen
on this island, not to the Government or HQ!
Do you think we're just going
to let you act like the pirate you've always been?!
Smokey!
Even if you are a surgery-man who ate
the Ope Ope Fruit, and can operate on everything!
Don't get in the way of his attacks, men!
He cut me!
Huh?  I'm alive...
You're in my way!  Get out of the circle!
Circle?!
As long as you're inside the circle that Law created,
you're like patients strapped to his operating table!
This is his operating room.
He can freely control and operate on
anything within this space.
He is the Surgeon of Death!
Trafalgar!
If that's what you're trying to do...
Stop it, Tashigi!
Your Haki is no match for him!
Captain-chan!
Tashigi has been cut down, and the thugs from the Navy's G-5 unit face annihilation...
but then Smoker stands up to Law.
A one-on-one fight
between a Warlord and a Navy Vice-Admiral begins.
Their battle, so fierce
that it destroys the entire surrounding area...
takes an unexpected turn!
Next time, on One Piece:
Clash!
Law VS Vice-Admiral Smoker
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Clash!
Law VS Vice-Admiral Smoker