All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
The crew has landed on Punk Hazard,
an island split between fire and ice.
There they learned about the plans of Caesar Clown,
the master of this island.
Now then children, time to get off.
This is your home.
Don't just wander off again.
My head hurts!  Master, please give us some candy...
You'll get the candy soon, of course.
So relax and savor it.
The delicious, delicious candy.
Luffy and the others were running from the Land of Death.
Together with their ally,
Trafalgar Law of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
they put in motion their plan to kidnap Caesar,
save the children and escape from the island.
Protect your Friends!
Mocha Runs for her Life
Mocha!  Give us the candy!
Lady!
Now let's go!
Let go of me!  What are you doing?!
Stay still.  I'm giving you a sedative.
Huh?  Where am I?
This won't stop us!
Oh no!  We have to chase after the kids!
Alright.
Give us the candy!
Wait!
Not again!
This isn't going to work forever.
How long do I have to hold them off?!
Candy!
Lady!
Candy.
Candy!
Mocha, are you alright?
Chopper-chan!
Run now, while you can!
Okay.
Mocha, wait!
We have to hold the children here.
We won't let them get to Mocha!
Please, Mocha!  Hang in there!
Biscuits Room
W-Where am I?
W-W-W-What are you doing?!
How embarrassing!  No!  Please, put me down!
Shut your mouth!  This isn't the time.
Look!
The killer gas is leaking into the Biscuits Room?
This is bad.  It's only a matter of time
until Building B is completely flooded with gas!
I know, so shut up!  Stop causing me trouble!
What now?!
This isn't the way to the exit!
What?!  Why didn't you say so sooner?!
Please put me down before we catch up to my men.
Why are you always so prideful?
Do you want me to drop you right now?!
What now?!
Isn't this the legendary named sword, Shuusui?!
Don't touch it!
Just shut up and let me carry you, you sword geek!
What is this place?
I don't know which way to go anymore!
Candy!
No!
Mocha?
Gimme the candy!
No!
Candy!  Candy!
Konbu, Biyo, stop it!  Please listen to me!
Candy!
Gimme candy!
Mocha!
Oh no!  Some of the children cut her off!
Stop it, everyone!
This is terrible!  If they get the candy,
they'll fall right back into their addiction!
We have to get those kids away from Mocha!
Outta my way!
Let's go!
Gimme the candy!
No!
Gimme!
No!  You can't have it!
No fair, hogging it all for yourself!
If we eat it, we won't be able to go home!
Don't you care that you'll never see
your mom and dad again?!
Shut up!  Just give us the candy!
I wanna go home!
I want all of us to live and go home!
Mocha ate all of it!
Mocha!
How could she be so stupid?
Give it back, Mocha!
You gotta be kidding me!
Don't hog it all, you idiot!
Mocha!
Don't do it!  Spit it all out!
Mocha, can you hear me?!
Mocha!
I told you what that drug was, didn't I?!
Hey...
Why can't we eat the candy?
Well you see...
that candy is a lethal poison!
What?
Chopper-chan.
They're all... my friends!
I promise!
Don't!
Once we grow up...
When we're all grown up, we should go out to sea.
The sea?
You mean become fishermen?
Don't be stupid, I mean we should go on an adventure.
Let's go find stuff like islands made of gold!
Sounds fun!
Once we've recovered and we go back to our islands,
we'll all be apart.
If we go out to sea when we grow up,
we can meet up again.
Oh, I see.  Great!  I don't want to leave my friends.
So when are we gonna go?
Hmmm, how about...
When we turn twenty!
That's so far off.
That'll just make it more exciting, right?
I see!
Then let's promise!
I promise!
So, Master is a bad guy?
Yeah.  He's as bad as they come.
But he's always so nice to us.
The candy he gives us every day is so tasty!
It's all part of his trap.
No way, but...
You're... his test subjects.
T-Test subjects?
Mocha, open the door!
We're going to the Biscuits Room!
You were never really sick!
T-That's impo-
Your big bodies are proof.
Turning humans into giants as a tool of war...
is something scientists all around the world have been trying to do for centuries.
In other words, their experiments have failed
over and over for centuries.  Nobody has succeeded.
There's no easy way to say this...
This experiment will also fail.
Caesar knows this.  All he cares about
is gathering data for his next experiment.
So... what's gonna happen to us?
You'll die.  None of you will make it home.
That delicious candy is a lethal poison.
It causes your body to break down
without you even realizing it!
And yet, if you eat one you'll want another.
The more you eat,
the harder it'll be to escape from Caesar's grip!
When you saw the children on the other side of
this door, you could see how terrifying it is, right?
I've given you a sedative, but the side effects of the candy and the experiments...
will most likely...
claim your life long before you grow up.
Mocha!
We won't grow up?
We... won't ever get to see our moms and dads again?
That's right.  Not unless we get you out of here now.
We never thought that we could die.
We wanted him to help us
because we wanted to go home!
We were afraid he might break his promise and keep us for another year because of the unknown disease!
But...
We didn't think we were gonna die!
We thought we were going to grow up!
This isn't what they promised us!
We only ate the candy because they gave it to us!
Nobody thought they were going to die!
I know!  You've done nothing wrong!
That's why we're gonna get Caesar, no matter what!
I can't forgive him!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry... that we didn't find you sooner!
Chopper-chan.
Chopper-chan, we...
don't want to die!
I won't let you die!
I swear I'll save you!
Caesar is a strong, evil, terrifying man...
but, you know...
our captain is much stronger!
He'll be the king of these seas someday!
Luffy will definitely beat Caesar!
So listen up... Mocha, right?
We can't let the other kids have the candy, ever again.
I'm going to stay here
and do my best to give them the sedative.
So Mocha, will you go to the Biscuits Room
and protect the candy there?
Yeah!
I understand!  I'll never let them eat the candy again!
We're all going to go home together!
Exactly!
Mocha!
Mocha just coughed up blood!
Why'd the delicious candy make her do that?
What's wrong with Mocha?
Hey... There's something wrong with her.
I can't believe this!
The children have stopped.
See?  This is because you were so selfish!
Mocha!
Mocha, hang in there!
Why?
This is what the candy does to you!
Mocha wanted to save you!
Even if it meant... sacrificing herself!
Chopper,
this might be our only chance to calm them down!
But I have to treat Mocha first!
There's no time.
The kids are standing still!
Go!
No violence, alright guys?!
Yeah!
Fight numbers with numbers!
Hold them down!
Alright!
Sanji-kun?!
The Navy?!
Sanji!
Bro!
Does kicking them in the balls count as violence?
It's a little over the line.
Roger that!
Medical team, up front!
Yes, Sir!
Chopper, let these guys help you!
They can handle an injection or two, at least!
Right!
Alright, you're gonna hafta calm down now!
I'm counting on you guys!
Heave, ho!
Forward!
I'm pretty sure the examination room is around here somewhere.
Carry her there!
She doesn't have long.
You know that, right, Racoon Dog?
I know!
Then we won't waste time talking!  Let's go!
Yeah!
Mocha...
Dammit, this is my fault!
Chopper-chan...
Mocha, are you alright?  Does it hurt?!
Chopper-chan, I...
I didn't give them the candy!
Mocha, you...
Yeah!  You protected your friends!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Thanks to you, everyone can go home!
Mocha, I promise I'll save you too!
I swear...
you will grow up!
Thanks!
What?!
Building C - Dust Box
Why'd the Dust Box suddenly...
W-Who's there?
Straw Hat Luffy!  What's he doing here?
Shoot him!
Where is Caesar?
Huh?  Uh...
I dunno!  I don't-
Where is Caesar?!
H-He's right down this corridor, in Building R!
I see.
I got it.
Brownbeard tries to save his men
by telling them who Caesar really is.
But Caesar twists his words to conceal the truth.
Seeing Caesar laughing triumphantly, Luffy's rage explodes!
Next time, on One Piece:
Brownbeard's Despair!
Luffy's Enraged Attack
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Brownbeard's Despair!
Luffy's Enraged Attack