It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew,
and made his way through the Great Prison, Impel Down,
in order to rescue his brother, Ace.
WHAT?!  You know about the war between the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates, right?!
Uh, what?
Navy HQ?
Now that we're through the Gates of Justice,
the only possible destinations are Enies Lobby and Navy HQ.
We're currently traveling the Government's exclusive route, the Tarai Current.
The enormous vortex that connects the Government's three main facilities.
NOBODY TOLD US ABOUT THIS!
Buggy!  Buggy!
Be silent, you flashy fools!
You're letting your emotions run away with you.
If you're real men, won't you come with me and fulfill your dreams?
Today...
I will take Whitebeard's head, and with it, the whole world!
I'll follow you!
Who needs to live in peace anyway?!
Indeed!  Let's go, men!
Let's go to Navy HQ!
Looks like they've come to an agreement.
Just do whatever vyou want.
I know you're worried about Ace-san...
but right now, you should rest for a while.
We're about to plunge right into a war that will change the world.
If Impel Down was the world's mightiest prison,
then Navy HQ is the world's mightiest stronghold.
We now go back in time a little.
This is a small Sky Island, Weatheria.
It is a country inhabited by scientists researching the weather.
Hey!  Hey, hey, hey, young lady!
Hey!  Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, young lady!
Hey!  Hey!
Yes, I can hear you!  What is it?
Hmm?  Hey, wait!  What's this?!
So, how is it?  How do you like my cloud candy?
It's a little experiment of mine.
It's really hard to make it taste like cotton candy, how did it turn out?
Please tell me what you think.
Are you trying to kill me?!
W-W-Wait a second, young lady!  You shouldn't be so violent!
Sheesh!
It's sweet...  It really does taste like cotton candy!
I know, right?
This sure is one strange island.
But anyway, this island is flying towards the Sabaody Archipelago, right?
Indeed.  It's a special service to get the blood pumping.
But it's been quite a while since I asked, so I was wondering, when are we going to get there?
Hm?  When, you ask?
What?!  How can you not know?!
Weatheria's movements are decided by the wind.
It'd probably go faster if a typhoon started blowing, though.
How far did we go yesterday?
About 200 meters, I think.
Sheesh...  If this wasn't a Sky Island I'd have left ages ago.
But you know, even if we go down now, Sabaody Archipelago is far, far away from here.
You'll get there someday if you stay here.
Hey, I don't have time to just sit around here and wait for that long, you know.
Then shall we go down?
My research funding is about to run out anyway.
Go down...?
Down to the ground below us.
We can get down there?!
My research costs a lot of money, after all.
Sometimes I go down to the ground and use my weather research to make money.
W-What is this?
Young lady!
Over here!
A ship?
What's with this ship?  It's flying?!
Here we go!
There's an island that'll do nicely!
This island...
This is awful...
You're going to solve...  this island's problems?
That's right.
As far as I understand, you seem to be in dire need of rain.
I can make it rain here by using my weather research!
What did you say?!
My services are on a special discount right now.
How does one hundred million beli sound?
One hundred million?!
I'm sorry, but we do not have that much money in this village.
Maybe it was a bit too expensive?
It's way too expensive!  There's no way they'd be able to pay!
Really?
Then one hundred beli will do.
So cheap!
That's too cheap!  You've got no business sense at all!
Oh, don't mind that.
Anyway, are you sure about this?  You seem so confident...
Please have some faith in my weather research.
Well, here I go.
Are these...
soap bubbles?
There's something inside them...
Young lady.  Use this and summon the wind.
This is...
Should I untie all the knots?
That's right!
T-This is unbelievable!
It's raining!
It's a great success.
They're all happy.
Indeed.  My weather science is quite handy, isn't it?
Well, then, I suppose this is where we say goodbye, young lady.
I've asked the chief here to help you,
so he should provide you with what you need for your journey.
I'm not going.
What?
I've decided not to go back down yet.
I've grown a little interested in your weather research.
What?
Think you can teach me some more of it while we're headed for the Sabaody Archipelago?
Well, of course!
Really?  Thanks!
We'll gladly welcome anyone who loves the weather!
Guess one cloud stayed behind...
Excellent.  I'll start with a lecture on these soap bubbles with the rain clouds inside them...
Well, this isn't good.
Why, you...!
What are you doing?!
Uh, sacrifices are necessary for the sake of progress!
Sacrifice, you say?!
L-L-Let me down!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
TL Note: Karakuri = Mechanics
We now go to Karakuri Island.
The kingdom where geniuses are born, Bulgemore.
It's super calming.
He was so much more fun before.
What are we gonna do to get old Franky back to normal?
Even if we try to perform surgery on him again, the cola shipments are late,
so if he can't retain his old pervertedness...  I mean, wild nature, he won't go back to normal.
Wild nature, huh?
So cold...
What am I doing out here?
Oh, what luck!  A muffler out here!
Huh?
What is the meaning of this?
"Keep out.  This is the forest of exiled Mecha Animals."
This is the "Surprise Awakening in the Jungle" Master Plan!
Reclaim your wild nature by struggling to survive in this harsh environment, old guy!
Don't try this at home, kids.
Oh, be reasonable.  Please calm down, ladies and gentlemen.
You seem to be rather tense, but now is not the time for breakfast, is it?
You must eat at the right time,
otherwise it will affect your health.
Oh, I see.  So it really is breakfast time now, is it?
Well, this is not good.
Delicious!  A cup of morning tea after waking up is just the best.
Would you like some as well?
It is good to be alive.
Looks like it didn't work.
Help!
Good morning, boys.
Old guy!
Please, call me "Mister Frank", not "Old guy".
Violence is not...
You might be at a somewhat naughty age, but...
If we just talk about this...
I'm sure we can...
Come to an...
Understanding...
Stop it.  Violence...  Will not...  Solve...  Anything...
Mister Frank!
Come on!  You're not gonna get through to him!
Calm down...
Listen to what I have to...
Listen...
Li...
SUPER!!!
Just who the hell do you think I am?!
I'm the great Franky-sama!
Alright!  Old guy, you're back to normal!
Transformation complete!
What's wrong?
Now that I've calmed down a little, the steam has disappeared.
TL note: Taihen = Terrible, Hentai = Pervert
What?!  This is perverted...  I mean, terrible!
Oh, I know!  There's a place that might have something!
Where are we going?
To Doctor Vegapunk's house!
If we go there, we might find a machine that makes cola!
Doctor Vegapunk?
He's a genius whose scientific knowledge was incomparable, even here in the future kingdom of Bulgemore!
The Mecha Animals we ran into earlier were all cyborgs made by Doctor Vegapunk!
He was a bit of an oddball and he abandoned all his cyborgs to leave the island...
but he was apparently an amazing man.
Grampa told me that there are lots of dangerous creations in here, and that I should never come to this place...
Let's do it.
What the hell is this?!
Sanji is being chased by a large crowd of gender-ambiguous people.
He runs, and runs, and runs, before eventually running into...
a mysterious queen, wearing a frilly one-piece dress.
Elsewhere, an enormous round creature is chasing after Chopper!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew's Whereabouts
Giant Bird Chicks and a Pink Showdown
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!