Translations, DeSiBoY
Timing,        Dino08
SockPain
Typesetting, DeSi
Editing, rumble
Encoding, jaga01
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
Attack AFX, narutossss
QCing, DeSiBoY
Before arriving at their next destination,
Luffy and crew stopped at Spa Island to enjoy a vacation
and met the sisters, Sayo and Lina.
This is a Sea Raccoon, named Munki.
Big sis Sayo!
So this is where you were, #100.
Straw Hat, it's been a while, right?
TL Note: Gum Gum Bazooka!
That notebook. That was Foxy's target, right?
This notebook has directions on how to create a gem written inside.
Everyone, please save us...
Foxy arrived with the intention of stealing the notebook entrusted to the girls by their father.
It contains the secret behind creating a gem.
Luffy and crew managed to defeat them, but...
Sayo was taken hostage by the true enemy, Doran.
Collapse!    The Spa Island
Great Treasure Contest!
Big sis Sayo!
Damn it!
This ship is filled with traps.
Boss, get it together!
That was pathetic, Foxy the Silver Fox.
To escape via a trap of mine.
Well, whatever.
Now all we have to do is wait for them to discover the secret behind the gems.
We really can't understand much from this alone, after all.
You already searched all over this ship, right?
There was no big X anywhere?
Yeah.
What should I do? This memo must be fake after all.
Yet, big sis has been...
Luffy!
Huh?
Save big sis Sayo.
Sure.
Heh? You will?
Really?
I really want to see that gem.
Huh? Even though this gem could be a fake?
But, what do we do, Luffy?
That's right.
Shall we destroy this ship?
EH?!!
HUH?
How did it come to that?!
Hey, hey, is that alright?
What about Sayo?
If we destroy it, we will find her, right?
And the hint about the gem?
Destroying it would make searching easier, right?
Let's hurry up and start this.
Zoro?
I mean, just thinking about whether something is or isn't on this island is pointless, right?
You all are seriously lacking in delicacy.
Nami-san, more than anything else, I can't stand listening to anything that artichoke mustache fool told us.
It really doesn't matter if this ship sinks, does it?
Ah, even Robin is in on it!
So, nobody is going to stop this?
It's Captain's orders after all.
Oh, so you do understand!
Franky!
I'll let you take care of Sunny Go.
I thought so.
Super!
Ah, we rarely come to such a resort.
Alright, destroy it!
TL Note: 108 Pound Cannon
TL Note: Gum Gum Whip!
TL Note: Tabasco Star!
TL Note: Carving Hoof Sakura
TL Note: Three-Verse Humming: Arrow-Notch Slice
Everyone is strong!
Return Sayo!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Like such bullets would be effective against me!
Huh? What?
He deflected the bullets.
Ouch!
You bastards, you sure did it now!
Hey! Hurry up and return Sayo!
You bastards!
WHAT IS THAT?!
A cannon?!
It wasn't a chimney?
Big sis!
Lina!
Damn! A hostage situation?
You think you can go all out and do as you please?
Don't mess around!
How much do you think this Spa Island cost?
That shitty bastard!
Sayo!
Bis sis!
Big sis Sayo!
I am going to send this little girl flying!
Stop it!
Initially, I wanted to have you solve the mystery of that notebook
but, forget that.
I'll just take the notebook.
Only after that, will I return her.
I will give you the notebook, so return big sis Sayo!
Don't!
You can't hand it over!
Big sis Sayo...
Lina, solve the secret of the notebook, and complete father's research.
No! Why?
Believe in our father, Lina!
Don't hand over his research to these guys!
You know that father tried to accomplish his dream, for the sake of us and the villagers.
H-Heh?
I beg of you. Don't lose our father's dream, for my sake.
That's a lie. Father was merely a selfish researcher!
Lina...
But... But...
Wasn't it always like that?
It's done! It's done!
Do you think father will enjoy this birthday cake?
Yeah.
He didn't come home!
He must have discovered something interesting.
I'm going to bed!
Yeah.
Cake.
I see.
So they made cake for my sake.
Father?
Did I wake you?
What is this?
30 year old cast-off bug skin.
It should be useful for my research.
They must have gone through metamorphosis 30 years ago tonight.
Is that so?
Ah! But, last night...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ahh, cake!
That sure is a tasty looking cake!
Ah!
Hah, that cake...!
Well, I made it yesterday,
but it may have gone bad. It's summer after all.
Doctor. Doctor!
He already examined you and left!
I don't know that person!
He doesn't understand anything about us!
He isn't thinking about us!
Hey, hey. This isn't the time for you siblings to be fighting.
Leave them be.
It's their problem.
Lina, you are wrong.
Listen.
Father was...
I feel bad about the cake.
Father...
She must have been looking forward to the birthday party.
Yeah.
Within the 30 year old cast-off, there is an ingredient necessary for gem creation.
If I hadn't taken this opportunity, I would have had to wait another 30 years.
I couldn't avoid going.
Yeah.
You aren't angry?
Yes.
I see.
But Lina must definitely be angry.
You are just like your mother, but Lina is more like me.
When she gets angry, she doesn't let it go easily.
When the gem is made, let us all eat a large cake, this big.
Yeah.
The size should surprise Lina as well.
Nuki is saying that it is all true.
Eh?
Also, the reason your father left home was to protect
you two from villains who were targeting his research.
No way.
This is...
There isn't one here.
You won't easily find a four-leaf clover.
But, big sis found three.
That is because your sister believed that she will definitely find them.
Believes?
That's right.
Research and four-leaf clover hunts are the same.
If you believe, never give up, and work hard, you will always succeed.
Really?
Alright! Then I will find a five-leaf clover!
Oh! Five-leaf?
That is amazing.
I found it!
Hmm?
I found it! A five-leaf clover!
W-Whoa! This is...
Lina!
It's true! I really believed I would find it.
That's right, Lina! It's amazing!
Yay!
Alright, Lina! I will do my best as well!
That's right. I forgot.
I believe it will come true.
It is father's dream, so it will definitely come true!
Lina!
I decided against it!
I won't hand over the notebook!
W-What?!
Here we go!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat with us at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Don't screw with me!
Successive
TL Note: Tabasco Star!
Nami, get on.
Yeah.
Sayo!
Hurry and untie her.
What is this?
A lock?!
From where did you climb up here?
Idiot! What are you going to do?
Wait!
TL Note: Three-Bladed Style
TL Note: Giant Metal Slash!
EH?!
They sure are doing a good job.
No, you do some work too damn it!
You bastard!
What?
That bastard!
He released all of the ship's ballasts at once.
Alright.
You bastards!
Let's go, Lina!
Yeah!
TL Note: Bone Balloon!
Boss!
What exactly is...?
Heading out first!
That idiot! Leave us a damn escape route!
Luffy, you are amazing!
Ah, I forgot that I become tiny when I use this.
Heh?
Geez. Think about what will happen after, will you?
A large X!
Yay!
Serves you right!
The X mark, and it is so large!
Yeah. That underwater volcano is what father had drawn on the map.
Doran built that ship on top of the treasure he was searching for.
For him to not have realized that the key to the secret was under his feet makes him the biggest idiot.
Aah!
Amazing!
That is a... round rainbow!
This is the first time I've seen a round rainbow.
Me too.
A mystery rainbow!
Cool!
W-Wait a second.
Could that be the treasure?
Eh?
Now that I think about it, the Round Rainbow is called, "The Gem of the Seas".
No way!
T-This is...
There is no way this is the treasure, right?
Don't look down on us!
That is...
I'll let you guys have the entire treasure!
Don't mess with us!
Huh? That rainbow is strange.
The order of the colors is the opposite of a normal one.
The order of colors?
What is wrong?
It might be that...
-A few days later-
Could that be...
Oh?
Hah?
It's the monster raccoon from that one time.
No, it's sea raccoon.
Hmm?
A letter?
Ah! It looks like Sayo's instincts from that time were right on the mark.
Big brother Luffy and everyone else, are you doing well?
After we left you, we immediately returned home and tried what Big sis thought of.
According to my father's formulas, we made 7 varieties of chemical,
and by mixing them using the same order as a Round Rainbow...
Yay!
They said that they made the gem!
Yay, yay, yay!
Sayo, Lina.
Oh! Is this it?
Amazing!
They all say, "Thank you!"
Let me get a better look, Luffy.
-Huh? Let's see here.
Me too! Me too!
Hey, hey! It isn't a toy you know!
Huh?
Huh? What is that?
Ah! It is candy rain! Ouch.
It's good.
Ah, I dropped the gem.
Where?
I don't know.
Search for it!
Hurry, and search for it!
You all, SEARCH FOR IT!
YES!
Why are you so excited, Brook?
After having gotten to know each of you so well, I decided.
I shall work hard to become a 'true' friend to you all.
True friend?
That isn't something that happens by putting in hard work.
No way!
Next time on One Piece:
Brook's Hard Struggle
The Difficult Path to Becoming a True Crewmate?
I will become Pirate King!
Brook's Hard Struggle
The Difficult Path to Becoming a True Crewmate?