Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew find themselves drawn into these events,
and things have escalated into an all-out war.
And now, due to Hody's ruthless scheme,
an unprecedented crisis looms over Fishman Island.
Everything will be over soon.
Shirahoshi, Fishman Island, and your companions...
A weakling like you can't protect any of them!
You're wrong.
I'll protect them all!
That's what the last two years were for!
You say you'll protect them all?
Don't make me laugh!
You sure have a big mouth, Straw Hat.
Damn that Hody.  He's even willing to attack Decken.
Run away, Shirahoshi!
Draw the Noah away from the island as far as possible!
It's too late.
Too late?  What's he talking about?
Wait... Didn't he just take out Decken?!
If Decken dies or loses consciousness inside the Noah...
...then his ability will stop working right above Fishman Island.
The Noah... will fall...
right onto the island!
What're ya doin'?
Dat hurt!
Can it!  I'm gonna fillet that giant body of yours!
Even Cap'n Decken...
never kicked me for no reason like this!
Manjuu: A rotund Japanese pastry
You damn Manjuu-bastard.
How dare you...
knock Nami-san over
with the shockwave from your fall!
Payback time!
This is payback...
for the shockwave that hit Nami-san!
Oh, crap!
Beware of the shockwave, Nami-san!
Another shockwave?  Give me a break!
Don't let your guard down!  Watch out!
She made something fly out of her staff earlier!
What now?!
Is she a witch?!
How rude!  I'm not a witch!
Call me an enchantress instead!
Granted, it's not really magic.  Just calculated science.
C-Clouds?!
Thundercloud Rod
Hot!
Help us!
Stay away!  I'll turn into a fried squid -hi!
Was it that woman's fault -hi?!
Hey, Ikaros.
The man in the black suit
became concerned when he thought she was hurt.
She is most likely the Straw Hat Pirates' weak point.
What?!
I'll go hold her still.
When I do, finish her off with your spears!
Roger that -muhi!
Just leave me alone now,
unless you want to be roasted!
What?!  My legs won't move!
I'm gonna make you into fried squid -hi!
W-W-Wait a second!
Why won't my feet move?!  Somebody!
Nami-san!  Oh, that's right!
Take this!  My Fried Squid Spear!
May I see your panti-
No way!
Is this a friend of yours?
He's gonna be dried up!
Become a fried squid!
Pardon?
What's happening -hi?
My spears should drain the water from your body,
and dry you up -hi!
Hey, Dried Squid Spears!  Why?!
What's wrong?!
Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!
Why?!
Umm...
I dried out a long time ago.
There's no way that could possibly be true!
It's quite a long story, but if you really want to know
how I turned into a dried-up skeleton...
There's no way that could possibly be true!
Oh, but it is.  It all happened fifty years ago...
Help!
Hey!  Aren't there any worthy opponents around?
Are you alright?
Who are you -hi?!
It's me!
That doesn't help -hi!
What?!  You don't recognize this super robot?!
Hmm?  Now that I look at you,
I see that you're one of the commanders!
You must have backbone, right?!
I may be a squid, but I'm also a fishman!
I do have a backbone!
What?  You're a squid, yet you have a backbone?
Sympathy!
He didn't mean it literally.
Hey, skeleton.  Step to the side real quick.
What?  Why is that?
Your feet!  Your feet!
What about my feet?
You're standing on him!  Standing right on him!
Huh?!  Who's this guy?!
He's the reason why I couldn't move?!
Um... Who might you be?
How do you like it?!
What?
The power of my headbutt to the bottom of your foot!
My attack will slowly begin to take effect.
What?!
He refuses to admit that he got stepped on!
My apologies for stepping on your face!
Don't say that!
My attack's name is...
Chou Ashiura Zutsuki!
Super Sole Headbutt!
He gave it a name!
Where'd you go, you damn coral-head?!
I'll chew you to pieces!
There's no way I can lose underground!  I move wherever I want!
Daruma-san!
Don't fill the ground with too many holes!
We're gonna get stuck!
Alright!
Chopper!  Are you done?
Come out over here!
Fool!  He's let his guard down -dogon!
I'll flatten him!
Hey, Chopper!
Can he hear me?
Be squashed and die -zugan!
Usopp, duck!
Horn Cannon: Eleven
Nice going, Chopper!  Did you connect the tunnels?
Yeah, it's done!
Alright!  Here we go!
Skull Bomb-Grass
How'd you like that taste of my strength?!
We fought against enemies who dug holes back in Alabasta!
Our experience won this fight!
Yeah!
Damn you, coral-monster!
Was that you?!
I'll show you my terrifying power!
When it comes to power, I've got an ace up my sleeve!
I'll chew that nose to pieces!
Why don't you try?!  Back me up, Chopper!
H-Hey, I need backup!
Chopper?
Now, it's time for the counterattack!
Dammit... Now I'm angry!
I won't forgive ya now, even if ya apologize!
I'm gonna crush ya!
Great!  This is what I'd expect from a master swordsman!
You're a worthy opponent!
Help me.
Are you alright?
I'll treat your wounds right away.
Darling!  Stay awake!
Daddy!
Hurry and treat their wounds!  Quickly!
Damn Hody.
He even attacked defenseless citizens!
Is the princess... alright?
I don't know.
But I'm sure...
she's still fighting for us!
Madame Shyarly.
What will happen to Fishman Island?
Will it really be destroyed?!
The pirate with the straw hat will save the island, right?
He must!  Right, Madame Shyarly?
Let's pray.
We can't do anything but pray
that Her Highness and the others...
stay safe!
Pray for Fishman Island to be saved!
I have to take it away.  Far away!
You sure are desperate.
Away from the island...
Noah!
Shirahoshi!
If the Noah falls, it's all over!
Oh no!  She can't hear us!
You mustn't swim straight up!
To the side!  Move to the side!
So they've caught on?!
Shirahoshi!
Brother!
Ryuuboshi!
Don't interfere with my plan!
Brother!  Hang in there!
If Decken's power doesn't stop working here, then what was the point of killing him?
So that's it!
If we don't move, then the ship will crash down onto Fishman Island and everyone there!
After Weak-hoshi worked so hard to draw it away from the island!
Bro-hoshi!  Let's go to Weak-hoshi!
Right!
Shirahoshi!
Weak-hoshi!
I won't let you go!
Fishman Island will be crushed, along with all of its people!
Straw Hat, all your companions are sure to die as well!
Are you alright?!
Shirahoshi!
Swim to the side!
Weak-hoshi!
Damn mermaid!
How insolent!
Shirahoshi heard us!
She's swimming to the side!
You shouldn't have done that!
I won't let you!
Wait!
Let me go!
I ain't letting go!
Damn it...
Noah!  Come this way!
I'm losing my grip...
Noah!  Follow me!
Let's go!
Right!
Damn Decken!  Just die already!
Damn it.
That bastard, Hody.  I won't let him get away with this!
Noah!  I'm right here!
The ship... It's starting to move to the side!
Great!  Keep going, Weak-hoshi!
Shirahoshi!
Go!
My left hand's target...
Hody, it's you!
Remember that!
Until you die...
I will always be hunting you, body and soul!
Noah!
Shirahoshi!  Just a little further!
If it moves too far, all of this was pointless!
All the way to the ends of hell!
I won't let you go!
Hody!
Just a little further, Weak-hoshi!
Decken!
I swear... I will kill you!
I'll break through by force!
Never!
My axe, your target is Hody!
I will protect everyone!
The Noah... is falling!
Just in time!
Fishman Island...
is still in danger!
It can't be!
Victory is mine!
Noah has started falling again,
and Luffy attempts to stop it to save Fishman Island...
but his fierce battle against Hody continues in the deep sea, where he's at a disadvantage,
and he is driven back.
And then, as the air on the Noah's deck is lost...
Luffy is trapped in a hopeless crisis!
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy Defeated?!
Hody's Revenge
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!