Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Two years have passed since the great war at Marineford.
Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates have all been training on their own,
and now they return to the Sabaody Archipelago in order to move on to the next stage: The New World.
Sunny!
We've kept you waiting for two years.
I'm glad you're still in one piece!
Who's this pretty woman over here?!
If it isn't my crewmate, the super archaeologist...
Robin!
You haven't changed, Franky.
Of course I've changed, you idiot!
Behold all the manly romance
that has been integrated into my body!
Have a look at my first and probably final
model change!
I have...
transcended human knowledge!
Yes.  I doubt anyone would
even consider you human anymore.
Hey, hey!  Are you saying I'm a perversion of nature?
You're far too kind!
So this is what a coating looks like?
It's like jelly!
Indeed!  That Rayleigh knows what he's doing!
Now the ship can travel the depths of the sea.
What an amazing technique!
I met Rayleigh and Shakki earlier.
At the bar, right?
What number were you?
I was the eighth.
Luffy is the only one who hasn't showed up.
I see.  It's almost time to set sail again.
I've finished the maintenance.
Installed new weapons too!
I look forward to seeing them.
Anyway, where are the others?
Usopp and Sanji were here earlier.
Usopp went off to buy fuel,
and Sanji is stocking up on food.
I see.  By the way, on the way here...
I came across this.
Have you heard anything about this?
What do they mean by "Soul King"?
Oh, about Brook?
Yeah, I knew.
His TDs are selling like crazy, after all.
He is shining brightly.
He came out of the dark, misty oceans
and climbed all the way onto a brilliantly shining stage.
It's possible...
that he'll never come back and be a pirate.
Soul King, mysterious...
He's nothing but bones!
A skeleton with an afro,
the girls can't resist the contrast!
If you want to make out with her...
Got milk!  Got milk!
Calcium is more important than protein!
Captain?!
Captain Luffy?!
Damn it...
Luffy!
I missed all of you so much!
Hey...
Luffy!
Franky!
Nami!
Sogeking?!
Amazing!
You've all changed over the past two years, huh?
I'm sure you've gotten stronger!
It's the Straw Hats.
Why are they just sitting in the middle of the street?
Well, you see...
Try to avoid eye contact.
We wouldn't stand a chance against those guys.
Damn it all...
What happened, exactly?
I don't know!
Shivers ran all through my body.
What kind of trick did he use?!
Oh, right!  We ran into some trouble ourselves.
The thing is, Cocoa got...
Uh, I mean, Nico Robin got...
What was that, Zoro?!  Nico Robin got kidnapped?!
We're so sorry.  We were right there, and yet...
Yeah, yeah!  It's true!  It's terrible, Luffy!
It might be slave traders!
Like what happened to Caimie last time!
Who took her?!
Well, we don't have any leads on that...
Captain!
I think someone had a grudge with the real Nico Robin
and they mistook Cocoa for her.
That's possible.
We got an almost perfect lookalike.
Guess that backfired on us.
Hey!  Why are you being so secretive?!
Well, whatever.  Just leave her.  It was her fate.
Huh?  Uh, aye, Captain!
What?!
Hey, Luffy!  Robin just got kidnapped, you know!
Okay, what's with this creature?!
Are you playing a joke on me?!
Even if you are, you shouldn't say things like that!
How can he talk?  Is he a stuffed animal?
Take it back, Luffy!
Oh, shut it!
More importantly, contact the one hundred pirates
who have joined us on this island.
They will gather at Grove 46!
The guy with the long nose,
the woman with the long orange hair,
and the kid with the cloak and enormous backpack...
Find all three,
and make them regret crossing Straw Hat Luffy!
Roger that!
Remember not to kill them
until we've brought them here.
This'll be a perfect way to show
the terror of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Alright, let's go!
Wait a second, you guys!
Have the past two years
changed your hearts so much?!
Luffy!
I-I'm so sad...
I'm starting to cry!
Again, what the hell is this creature?!
What about Robin?!
Are you all just gonna let this happen?!
What?  How can you talk?
Toys these days sure are well made!
Damn it... I misjudged you guys!
I'll go rescue her, even if I have to do it alone!
Wait for me, Robin!
What was that?  A fight amongst the crew?
There's no doubt about it.
Most of the crew, including Straw Hat Luffy,
have changed considerably over the past two years.
But there's no mistaking that strange pet of theirs!
They are...
the Straw Hat Pirates!  They're still alive!
This is Grove 47.
We have confirmed the presence of the Straw Hat Pirates!
The new companions Straw Hat has been gathering...
are going to meet at Grove 46!
Great work.  Message received!
Go there immediately,
and move the civilians to safety!
Yes, Sir!
The pirates are assembling in Grove 46!
Our enemy is the Straw Hat Crew!
We're going into the lawless area!
Prepare for battle!
Barricade the entrances from Groves 40, 42 and 44!
Reinforcements from G1 are on their way!
S-Sentoumaru-san!
I'll be going on ahead!
I'm taking PX-5 and PX-7 with me.
What?!  The Pacifista are being dispatched?!
Of course!
Are you taking the Straw Hats seriously enough?
It's been two years since the war.  They've gotten even stronger!
They're on an entirely different level from
the regular rookies that come to these islands!
We never figured out the meaning
behind Lord Kuma's actions two years ago.
But his eccentric actions,
even after he lost his personality,
led me to believe there would come a day
when the Straw Hats would regroup on this island.
Let's go!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Oh, it's moving!  It must be this way.
This is what happens when you oppose me!
Damn it...
Run away!
There sure are a lot of pirates around.
Maybe I should put it on after all?
I'm telling you to drop the price a little!
I-I can't do that, valued customer!
Half price for this mountain of clothes?!
That's just...
Hey, Nami!
You can buy as many clothes as you want
on Fishman Island, right?
We should be getting fuel now!
No way!
Right!  I'll buy these too, so give me a 90% discount!
Noooooo!
Hey, hey... I see that your haggling skills
have powered up these past two years as well.
Hey, Moss-Head!  Don't fall behind.
It'd be a real pain if you got lost again.
Huh?  Look who's talking, Bearded Swirly-Brows!
The hell was that?!
Smells nice.
This looks delicious.
Welcome!
Feel free to taste one.
So dazzling!  There's a lady right in front of me!
Damn... Where'd he go?
If I'm gonna go fishing I'll need a fishing rod.
Ah!  There's a fishing goods store right over there.
He's gone... Damn that guy!
Robin!
Where'd they take you?
Damn it!
Damn!  Damn!  Damn!
What happened to everyone?!
Luffy... Zoro... Nami... Sanji... Franky...
They all used to care about their crewmates so much.
How can they just ignore it when Robin is kidnapped?!
It's awful!
What's the point of all my hard work
for the past two years?!
Who was I trying to help?!
Hey, Chopper!
Hey!
Over here!
It really is you, Chopper!
Usopp!
Look at you!  You've grown so big!
I bet you're really comfortable to ride now!
Have you been doing well?
Yeah!
You're right!  He's so much softer than before!
Long time no see, Chopper!
Huh?!
Nami?!
Yes?
Oh, I forgot!
I'm happy to see you again,
but we don't have time for this!
Robin's in trouble!
What?  So, they were fake?
That's why there are two Namis?
Unbelievable!
Robin has been running from the Government
for twenty years!
Do you really think they could just
stuff her in a bag and carry her off?
It's unthinkable.
I see!  She did seem a bit different from usual...
She didn't have her familiar scent either.
That means... Man, I'm really annoyed now!
What's with those guys?!  Pretending to be us!
I won't forgive them!  How dare they imitate us?!
It's almost as if we're really...
It's like we're famous!  You jerks!
What are you so happy about?
Well, considering how well-known our captain is,
I'm not surprised that impostors have showed up.
I need to work on my signature!
I've already figured mine out!
We're not famous, we're infamous!  Get it?
Hey, Chopper!
Chopper!
Seriously... We'd finally managed to get
the real Straw Hats' pet!
Ouch!  My side hurts!
What?!
That weird creature was
a survivor from the real Straw Hat Pirates?!
Why didn't you say so sooner?!  Bring him back here, now!
That's impossible!  Where are we supposed to look?!
We've completely lost sight of him... The Sabaody Archipelago is huge!
Ouch!  My side hurts!
I'm too tired!  Let's walk!  Let's just walk...
Hancock was right,
I'm better off wearing the mustache.
She said not to cause a commotion.
Hey, isn't that the kid with the cloak and
huge backpack that the Captain was talking about?
Kid?  Isn't that just a jolly old man?
Huh?  You guys...
H-Hey, Bro!  Come over here for a sec.
I-If you just come along quietly, we won't hurt you.
But the Captain is really angry.
You're not going to live long either way.
What?  Are you too scared to speak?
I knew it!  You're Sanji, aren't you?
And you're Zoro, right?  It's been a long time, huh?
H-Hey, it's been a long time... hasn't it?
Y-Yeah!  Anyway, let's go!
Sure!  Are the others already there?
Sorry I kept you waiting!
I don't think he understands, do you?
Who cares?  We just have to take him to the Captain!
I want to go to the shoreline.  I wanna go fishing.
No way, you damn bastard!
Why not?!  Why should I listen to you?!
It's not like I want to be with you, either!
It's a total pain!
You're just gonna loiter around the island again,
aren't you?  You blind Moss-Head!
We're all meeting up soon,
so just shut up and follow me back to the ship!
Sheesh.
You're sure talking big to the first one to get here,
number seven.
Why are you ranking us by the order we got here?!
Don't let it go to your head just because,
by some miracle, you managed to get here first!
So sorry about that, number seven.
That's it, I'm gonna kill you!
Using these legs, which I've trained for two years in hell!
Bring it on!  I'll cut you in half!
Grove 46 here.
The place is crawling with rookies
that have been accepted into the Straw Hat Crew!
I can identify four captains!
Albion the Gashed, wanted for 92 million beli.
Lip Service Doughty, with an 88 million beli bounty.
A-And the Super Rookies...
The captain of the Caribou Pirates,
wanted for 210 million beli...
Wet-Hair Caribou!
And his brother from the same crew,
wanted for 190 million beli...
Blood-Splatter Coribou!
The Straw Hat Pirates meet up at the Sunny,
one by one.
However, the marines have mobilized
because of the Fake Straw Hats' actions...
and they break into Brook's concert.
Amidst the confusion, Brook starts singing his final song as the Soul King.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Big Shots Gather
The Terror of the Fake Straw Hats
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!