Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
It's time.
Finally, the curtain of the Great Age of Pirates...
is about to fall.
Z-sensei.
After bidding farewell to Fishman Island,
the Straw Hats have finally arrived in the New World.
W-What's going on here?!
The Navy?!  Seriously?!
They're over there!  And there too!
They've got us totally surrounded!  All 360 degrees!
They must have known what route we were taking.  I'd expect nothing less from the Navy.
There's no way we can escape
when we're surrounded like this.
How can you discuss this so calmly?!
This weather...
They're coming closer!
What're we gonna do, Luffy?!
Huh?  Now that you mention it, where is Luffy?
Full speed ahead!
We're gonna push straight forward, men!
Against so many enemies?!  You...
There's no time to sweat the small stuff!
Usopp!  Prepare the cannons!
Chopper, fill the cola tanks!
Fine, we'll just have to play the hand we have!
Leave the front to me!
We'll take care of the sides.
I've got the back!
Bring it!
We're ready!
Hold up, Usopp!
There's no need.
Why?!
Huh?
The warships are all disappearing, one by one!
The rain's stopped too!
Thought so.
What's going on?
Those were mirages,
they're known to occur in this region of the sea.
Mirages?!
What a relief.
We can't let our guard down yet!
If my guess...
i-is right...
What is this?!
Enormous raindrops!
What is with this weather?!
These are the waters of Mobedumule!
Momemomejuban?
Mobedumule!
Or as they're also called, the Temperamental Waters.
Weather phenomenons
unlike anything anyone has ever seen or heard...
come one after another, as if by the ocean's whim!
It's freezing?!
So these are some risky waters, huh?
They'll hit us!
360 Pound Cannon/Phoenix of 360 Earthly Desires
Damn...
Right!
Cotton candy?
Now it's an avalanche from the sky!
Nice, Robin!
It's started raining like crazy again!
I hope it's normal rain this t-
What is it now?!
Don't tell me...
The sea is parting!
So anything is possible?!
We're starting to fall!
At this rate, we'll wind up back in the deep sea!
No, we'll probably crash into a boulder
before we get there, and then drown to death.
Don't say such terrible things!
These waters are amazing!
Why're you just calmly admiring it?!
How do we get out?!
I'll punch it.
I'll cut it.
I'll kick it.
Alright!
No, it's not alright!  What are we gonna do?!
Leave this to the Sunny!
Alright!
Awesome!
We're saved!
And now it's scorching heat.
Hot.
That was close.
But that was quite impressive, Nami-san.
You know so much, even about the New World's climate.
I made sure I learned as much as possible
about the New World during the past two years!
When it's this hot, you just gotta have a beer.
Butterfly!
I'm starving!
Me too!
Oh, that's right!
We still have that deep sea fish we caught!
Sorry, but we lost most of the deep sea fish
during the weather earlier.
Whaat?!
Well, I did manage to salvage a little of it.
I'll cook up something, so just wait a second.
Alright, first off I'll whip up some carpaccio...
and some deep sea bouillabaisse.
Now, what should the main dish be?
Hey, it's ready!
Come get it!
Yay!
Looks delicious.
Food!  Food!
Let's dig in!
You can start with that.  It's deep sea fish carpaccio.
I don't see it!
Isn't it right there on the big plate?
There's a plate here, but no carpaccio!
There's no way that it's...
not there?!
Boo!  Boo!
You already ate it, didn't you?!
It wasn't us!
Then who?!
What if...
it's another weather phenomenon of Mobedumule?!
Yummy!
Something's in here!
The soup's gone!
What?!
What's that?  Something's coming out!
A bug?
A monster bug!
Is that the thief?!
No, how could it be?
Huh?
What?!  The strawberries disappeared?!
What?!  Now the corn disappeared?!
Seriously?!
Damn it, you're not getting away with this!
Luffy, it ran outside!
I've got a feeling this might be even worse...
The fridge is empty too!
Where'd it go?!  I lost sight of it.
What's going on?
There's a monster bug!
What?
The food-thief's getting away!
Thief?  How rude!
I only ate the stuff that was lyin' 'round back there!
Huh?  Me?
That's what a thief is!
What are you doing, Luffy-san?!
It got away!
What got where?
H-Huh?  Where'd it go?
It got everything in the fridge!
Including the booze!
What?!
Where'd you go?!
You're...
human?!
You've got some nerve, eating my food!
There she goes!
Huh?
Damn!
Hey, I'm counting on you, Franky!
Leave it to me!
I ain't gonna get captured here!
Hold it!
She threw Franky into the air?!  She's amazing!
Looks like we better get serious.
Since it's come to this...
Let's do it!
S-She's...
Huge!
Amazing!
You are wonderful...
Mega-Missy!
Run away!
Now, come to me!
Not good!
We're gonna get impaled!
Hope ya don't hold this against me!
I'll take you on!
Alright, I'm comin'!
What?!
Alright!  He's lifting her up!
What's this?!
Modoshi: Reversal
W-What?  She can't swim?
Missy!  I'm coming to save you!
Maybe she's a Devil Fruit user?
Daddy, I'm sorry... It's over.
What's this, all of a sudden?
Daddy... Daddy!
I'm gonna save you, no matter what!
Wait for me, Daddy!
Daddy!
What a relief.
She's awake!
Missy, are you alright?
Hey, you!
Luffy!
You're not gonna use violence
against a lady again, are you?!
You can shrink and then grow again.  That's so cool!
I... I'm actually a giant...
but then I ate the Mini Mini Fruit.
A giant?!
Yeah... that's right.
Now this here's my regular size, but I can go down to
five millimeters or go back up to my giant size.
In all, I can go between the three different sizes.
You're pretty interesting!
Really?
Yeah, and you're strong too!
I mean, you were so small
and yet you threw Franky into the air!
Even if I'm small, I'm still as strong as a giant.
It's easy!
See?
Awesome!
Looks like he's completely forgotten that she ate our food.
Sheesh, getting all chummy.
Can you do anything else?
Sure can, I've got another special trick!
I sneak into an enemy's body in my mini-size...
then grow big again,
and blow the enemy to smithereens.
Nooooo!
Then I could be turned into a giant!
What do ya mean by that?
Luffy is a rubber man.
He wouldn't be blown to pieces, he'd just stretch.
Really?
Look at that!  You ain't lyin'!
By the way, Missy, what's your name?
I'm Lily Enstomach.  Folks call me Lily the Glutton.
I can eat tons!
So, Lily... Why are you on our ship?
Ya wanna know why?
I was out here waitin' fer someone,
when y'all just appeared outta nowhere!
But why would you wait for someone out here?
Who were you waiting for?!
My Daddy.
Hey!  I ain't got time to be messin' 'round here!
Lily-chan, what's wrong?!
Calm down!  The balance between
your head and your body is all messed up!
My bottle was shattered!  What should I do?!
I finally got all the way out here
by sneakin' onto Navy ships and warships!
Now I'll never get to my Daddy!
W-Wait, you're searching for your dad?!
What kind of dad is he?!
Daddy's only
the greatest pirate chef in all of the New World!
Pirate chef?  Lily-chan, what's your dad's name?
He's Panz Fry!
I've heard of him!
Is he really that famous?
He's a master of volcano cooking!
Volcano cooking?
What's that?  Is it tasty?
Well of course!  Just thinkin' about tastin' it...
My favorite meal, sea monster churrasco!
Ghost herbs that only grow round volcanoes!
Salt crystals that formed
hundreds of millions of years ago in the lava gaps!
He lets the meat of three sea monsters
absorb the salt...
before putting it right into a volcano to flash fry!
Sounds delicious!
And that ain't everything!  The most delicious of all is...
Is what?!
A super large fryin' pan filled to the brim with
every kind of food from both the sea and mountains...
cooked on top of a volcano!
It's called the Thousand Man Paella!
All you need is a single bite...
and you'll think that you're lost in a dream!
It's like runnin' through
the prettiest field of flowers in Heaven!
I wanna eat it!  I wanna go to Heaven!
Heaven food!
Wait!  This ain't the time!
You were the one who started it.
I've also heard rumors about Panz Fry.
He's a pirate who steals food
from the Government, the Navy and other pirates...
and gives it to starving people, bringing them great joy.
So he's...
a hero?!
Hero?  That's so embarrassin'.
Wait!  I ain't got time to be embarrassed!
Whatever.  Just explain.
Ah, right.
I was always with Daddy
when he was travelin' 'round as a pirate...
but he suddenly disappeared two weeks ago.
I reckoned that the Navy got him.
So I went to several different islands to gather information...
and found out from a newspaper
that Daddy's being taken to Impel Down!
Impel Down?!
Why would they take him there?!  Isn't he a hero?!
Daddy has a bounty of 320 million beli.
He's worth over 300 million?!  Seriously?!
When he was out and stealin' food
from the Government and the Navy...
his bounty kept growing and he didn't even know it.
I finally made it out here
after a whole mess of trouble...
but my ship was torn apart by these crazy storms,
and I had no idea what to do.
What a kindhearted soul!
She cares so much for her dad!
But still, Impel Down of all places?
That place is rough.  I almost died there!
I'm not going to Impel Down.
What about your dad?!
Well, when I snuck aboard a warship, I overheard...
We are planning to transport Panz Fry
through the waters of Mobedumule.
...that the ship holdin' Daddy
will be comin' through here soon!
Meaning, the Navy is headed this way?!
If we bump into them, we'll be in serious trouble!
Yeah.  But I'm gonna save Daddy, no matter what!
Before they can take him to Impel Down, I must...
take Daddy back, right here!
Lily-chan.
I thank y'all for everything.
I won't cause any more trouble.
If ya can spare me an empty bottle, I'll be off.
Y'all better get away from here as soon as...
Lily.
About that...
Let me help you!
I want to try that Heaven food that only your dad can make!
Plus, your dad's a hero!
I wanna meet the hero too!
But...
That's how it is.  Don't worry about it, Lily-chan.
There's no getting around it.
If I didn't help you with this,
I'd be disgracing the name of perverts!
So we'll be facing the Navy
immediately after entering the New World?
This is getting exciting!
This must be some sort of destiny.
Will y'all really...
Sure, leave it to us!
Luffy...
Everyone!
Once we get him back,
let me eat plenty of that heavenly volcano cooking!
Yeah, of course!
I'll let ya eat 'til yer stomach bursts!
Shuzo-san, please reply!
Shuzo-san!
What is it?
The captain isn't here right now.
Whatever business you have, I can pass it on to him.
All ships were supposed to assemble today.
Why haven't you arrived yet?
Hey, what is it?  Respond!
Tell us where...
I know you're there.
A-Ain-san...
You're there, right, Shuzo?
I am heading your way, right now.
Currently, I am entering the waters of Mobedumule.
That's quite a detour you're taking.
You don't seem to understand how important our plan is.
I understand perfectly.
Then why-
I received word...
that a convoy ship carrying the great pirate Panz Fry
will pass through the waters of Mobedumule!
We can't just overlook this and
let him be taken to Impel Down, can we?
All the pirates in the New World...
must be slaughtered!
That's the Neo Navy's objective, is it not?!
We cannot risk the chance that
your selfish actions will tip off the Navy to our plan.
Come to the rendezvous immediately!
You needn't worry.
There will be no evidence
after I send the Navy's ships to the bottom of the sea!
Nothing can stop me from carrying out this plan,
and proving that I'm worthy
of being his right hand man!  Not you!
You know what will happen if you fail, right?
Of course.
Insolent little girl!
Attention all hands!
It's time to show the Navy
the true terror of our Neo-Navy!
Prepare to ascend!
Yes, Sir!
Hey, what's the weather doing now?!
More mirages?
It's probably just mist.
This really cuts down our visibility.
It might be hard to spot your dad now.
Yeah.
Hey, Lily, look at that!
It's the Navy!
That's Daddy!
That guy?
Well then...
Men!
Time to go get Lily's dad back!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Z's Ambition" Arc
The Strongest Unknown Army Arrives!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!