Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
To defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and invaded Dress Rosa.
Luffy joined a battle tournament to win the Mera Mera Fruit,
and completed the preliminary round.
Now he's heading toward the palace to rescue Law from Doflamingo.
We're heading to the palace.
And...
We're gonna send Doflamingo flying!
At the Colosseum,
the battle tournament finals have begun.
Wave Motion...
Dragon's Claw!
Meanwhile, in the underground trade port,
The Tontattan's SOP plan has begun.
With this fake grape made from tatababasco, we'll knock Sugar unconscious.
You may be able to hit a fly, but not me.
I'm too fast.
Wait, Leo!
Robiland?
I knew you could do it, Captain.
Alright, now we control the lift.
I guess you do have some fight in you.
We made it past the rock man!
He just doesn't give up.
We're trapped!
Luffy, take her and go on ahead.
Leave this guy to me.
You go take down Doflamingo.
Defeat Sugar
The Gnome Army Attacks!
I'll take out this rock bastard!
Alright, I'm counting on you.
I'm your opponent!
He's blocking the path!
He's behind us too!
I said I would deal with you!
Three-Sword Style...
Oni Giri!
Gomu Gomu no...
Stamp!
Let's go!
Alright!
Black Rope: Grand Dragon Twister!
Silence won't shield you.
One-Sword Style...
Draw...
Death Lion's Song!
Captain!
You thought your puny strength would get you into the castle?
G, for Get Real!
I will go, whatever the cost!
And then...
I will kill Doflamingo!
Royal Palace, First Floor
Captain!
This is bad!  If this goes on, we can forget about taking down Doflamingo!
We won't be able to rescue our brothers and sisters at the factory either!
The Underground Trade Port
We haven't gotten any new workers this past year.
I know.
Shining Flower
"Elegant Sunflower"
They haven't shown themselves in the palace either.
Who's slacking off?!
Artificial Devil Fruit
Smile Factory
I-I wasn't slacking!
They must have noticed that five hundred of their people have gone missing.
Yet they never see the bad in people.  The Tontattans sure are dense...
I mean, pure-hearted.
Then why aren't they showing themselves?
Who knows.
Well, if we can't get any new workers, we'll just
have to make the most of the five hundred we have.
Get moving!  Whip of Love!
Hey!
These Smiles aren't ripe yet!
Are you alright?
I thought you Tontattans could grow any plant.
W-Well yes, but the Smiles aren't natural...
No excuses!
Please let my brother take a break.
The food today was spoiled, so he...
You're complaining about the food too now?!
Don't you want to cure your ailing Princess Mansherry?
W-We do!
Then keep producing Smiles!
They're essential for the medicine that can cure her.
Less than ten percent of the crops you produce each season are usable.
Work harder and make the process more effective!
Could you let us see Princess Mansherry?
No.
Why?
Well...
If you catch her disease...
...it'd make us all cry!
You Tontattans are our invaluable partners!
S-Sanshita-san!
We'll do everything we can!
Please look after our princess!
Of course!
How can they believe such a blatant lie?
W-What are you doing, Robiland?!
I'm sorry.  But if you'd just charged in like that, you would have been killed.
I looked at that fly's corpse.
This is...
He hit it perfectly between the eyes, despite its size.
Trébol's dynamic visual acuity is exceptional.
It's far too dangerous to go after Sugar while he's still guarding her.
So what are you going to do, Robiland?
First off, we have to separate Sugar and Trébol.
That's easier said than done.
Usoland, please lead us!
Legendary hero Usoland!
L-Leave it to me...
Hey, what's with this crate?!
It's a swarm of pink bees!
I have news, Trébol-sama!
There's a commotion in port four from Captain Eves' crew.
They're demanding to talk to a commander about the deal.
They must be really brave
if they're not scared of Joker's name.
Hey, did the guard change?
The usual guard is out for lunch right now!
This is an emergency!
Several of our people have been injured!
Please help us!
Injured?  I hate that.
Hey, hey!
Trébol-sama!  You're outside?
Strengthen the security on the four doors to the Commanders' Tower.
Yes, Sir!
And inform me right away if something happens.
Uh... Yes, Sir!
Trébol-sama!
We appreciate your hard work!
Hey, hey!
Where is it?  Where's the fight?
Port four.
What?  You won't fight, Usoland?
It would be easy for me to handle this, but...
Doing nothing can't harm me.
...by watching over you, I will give you confidence!
Confidence?
I see.
So that's it.
Don't worry!  If anything goes wrong, I'll save you!
That's so reassuring.
We'll follow you till the end!
Legendary hero Usoland!
S-Sure...
Who's there?
Here I go!
He did it!
Now, as soon as she eats that mega-spicy tatababasco...
She didn't take it!
This time, for sure!
You idiot!  Don't scream!
If Operation Sugar Oversurprise Panic fails...
...everything else we've planned will go down the drain too!
Now that it's come to this...
Give up, Sugar!
What are they doing?!
We've come to retrieve our comrades being held in the factory!
And we'll knock you unconscious!
Unconscious?
I don't know anything about your comrades.
What?!
Really?
Really.
Okay then.
It's not okay!  Don't let her trick you!
T-That was close!  Give back our comrades!
Who told you all this?  You're clearly too thick to realize that you're being tricked.
I had been wondering why the Tontattans
haven't been seen in the palace for the past year.
So it was because someone has been deceiving you.
Silence!
Hold her down and force her mouth open!
How insulting.  You think I'm weak.
Little Black Bears!
Time to make the contract.
Oh no!  She turned us into toys!
Obey my orders until you die.
Have we all been forgotten?!
What?
A bunch of toys showed up out of nowhere.
What were we just doing?
Slaughter all the intruders in the Commanders' Tower!
I can't resist her orders!
Slaughter all of them... Even me?!
Don't!  I don't want to fight!
Those must be Sugar's subordinates!
I can't believe she had more backup aside from Trébol!
Leo!  It's me, Flapper!
Take down the enemy soldiers!
No!  No!  No!
Nooo!
Trébol, come back!  It's a trap!
Trébol!
A trap?
Hey, you!
Look at that, Trébol-sama!
The pirates are causing a commotion.  We can't deal with them!
Hey, hey, you!
What's the problem?
Trébol-sama!
Hey, what's up?
Well, it's not really a problem...
Just, a bunch of bees that were in the cargo.
There's no problem with the deal.
That woman!
Hey, hey, wait, wait!
You!
Hey, who are you?  Hey!
She disappeared!  Hey!  Hey!
But wait... That face...
Was she one of the Straw Hats?!
How'd she get here?
Trébol!
Why are they after Sugar?
Get back here!  You've been tricked!
Die, you imbecile!
Now I'm mad!
Beta Beta Chain!
Sticky Stick...
Huh?  What's that?!
Meteor!
Being faced with Trébol's furious, terrifying attacks,
Leo and the others suffer a devastating blow.
The Riku Royal Army's last hope is the toy soldier.
His true identity as a former Dress Rosan legend is revealed at last!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Last Light
Our Captain's Secret!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The Last Light
Our Captain's Secret!