Impel Down, the great prison where the world's worst criminals are kept...
In this grand and impenetrable prison, the largest in all the world,
one man, attempting to save his
condemned brother, Fire Fist Ace,
has managed to break in.
He is Straw Hat Luffy.
Yet...
20 years before this incident,
There was one man who escaped this prison,
which had taken such pride in being inescapable.
You're kidding me.
He cut off his own legs?!
That legendary man was...
Captain of the Flying Pirates...
the Golden Lion, Shiki!
This story takes place some weeks prior to the Golden Lion, Shiki and Luffy's meeting.
Captain! Corto-san!
Huh? What is it?
It's finally come!
A message from Boss Shiki!
Really?
It finally came, huh?
Get me the Snail Phone!
Yes, right away!
I did it, Bro!
Now, as soon as we're in Shiki's crew,
we'll finally get a chance to make a name for ourselves!
Bro?
Why're you crying?
Amore, my beloved little brother, Corto.
I am most saddened.
If this Señor Shiki's plan is fulfilled,
the world shall be consumed by grief.
When I think of hearing those thousands and thousands of voices raised in despair...
It makes me sad, oh, so very sad.
I've got the Snail Phone.
Right! Get him on the line!
Are you the captain of the Amigo Pirates, Sir Largo?
Nah, I'm Corto, the vice-captain.
I'll hear you out.
Is that so?
Then I'm calling to let you know that we've decided to welcome Sir Largo to Big Boss Shiki's assembly...
as our 51st pirate captain.
That's no surprise!
However, there are some conditions you'll need to satisfy in order to attend.
And we must ask that you complete them beforehand.
Conditions?
Nothing so far.
This is not working.
Boy, am I hungry!
I don't know how you can say that after eating so much.
We've had feasts and banquets every night lately.
Our stomachs have expanded, and we have to eat much more to get full again.
Ah, you're right. My bones are growing fatter these days.
That's your imagination.
How's it going? Catch anything yet?
Nope. Not even a nibble.
We're almost out of food.
If you don't catch anything, you won't eat anything.
What?!
Don't you "What?!" me!
I told you it was a bad idea to feast again before the next island!
And yet, you lot went on...
Banquet! Banquet!
Were we really like that?
I don't know...
Damn it, you guys!
I've got one! I've got one!
Here it comes!
Way to go, Brook!
This is a huge one!
Right! Let's have another banquet today!
Haul it in even if it kills you, guys!
Hang in there! You've almost got it!
Things sure got livelier all of a sudden...
Here it comes!
Wha-?!
No way!
What is that?
A...
A beetle just...
ate...
our fish!
Awesome!
That's...
a pirate ship!
Another one showed up!
Boss! Get them!
He's coming!
He's huge!
I wanna ride that thing!
What're you saying, Luffy?!
Hey, Usopp! We're gonna catch 'im!
Got it!
Wait! How'd you get ready so fast?!
I won't let you destroy the ship!
Franky's attack didn't work?!
Seriously?
Leave it to me!
Now, come here, giant beetle!
They sent Boss flying?!
That beetle just breathed fire!
Does that bastard plan on burning the Sunny?!
Luffy! Are you alright?
Not only is that beetle huge, but he breathes fire...
That's just too awesome!
He looks fine to me...
I've decided!
I'm gonna make him a member of our crew!
Hey! Wait a second, Luffy!
Now, giant beetle! Join my...
Gotcha!
You're kidding, right?
What's he doing?
He's coming this way! Oh, yeah, he is!
He's coming a bit-
WAIT A MINUTE! HE'S AIMING FOR US!
Help... Help...
HELP ME!!!
Hey, Usopp!
Sheesh, what a moron!
He flew off...
What are they doing?
There's an island over there...?
Think that's where the beetle lives?
Boss!
Be careful, Boss!
We're gonna crash!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
You finally stopped, huh, giant beetle?
Now, be a good boy and join my crew!
I won't take no for an answer!
There's no way Boss...
would ever...
become a pirate!
Ouch!
What's going on?
Who'd have thought there'd be an island out here?
And anyway...
What the hell's going on here?
Yoko! What's going on?
These guys're pirates!
PIRATES?!
PLEASE, SPARE US!
Quit that already!
Could it be...?
Aren't you the Straw Hat Pirates?
Yeah, we are...
Now that you mention it, that's Straw Hat!
And this guy's the Pirate Hunter Zoro!
And isn't that Black Leg Sanji?!
Then that must be...
Uh, oh.
Who are you?
Hey!
Let go of me!
He tried to steal Boss!
I'll bite him to death!
Yoko! Stop it!
Shut up! I told you to let go of me!
What's with these guys?
That hurt...
Hey you! You the owner of that beetle?
"Owner"? Don't be ridiculous!
Boss is my comrade!
Comrade?
Oh, you already had companions, huh?
And there's no way you'd let me have him in my crew?
Of course not!
I wouldn't let you have him, even if I died!
That so? Well, guess there's no helping it then.
Ready, and...
Hey! What are you doing?
Boss!
Sorry I hurt you.
You think you defeated him already?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Boss!
Hey...
Stay away!
A wound like this is nothing to Boss.
As long as he just gets some sleep in the dirt, he'll be fine by tomorrow.
That's awesome!
That's not all.
Tomorrow just happens to be his molting day.
And then, he'll be even bigger and stronger!
You mean beetles keep shedding even after they're full grown?
Boss is different.
He sheds his skin once every month.
That's how he got so big.
So, you're gonna get even stronger?
That's right! He's amazing, right?
Yeah, he's awesome!
Right! Let's have another fight tomorrow!
Let's decide once and for all who's stronger!
That's ridiculous...
Right! Then it's a promise, man to man!
That youngster is just as amusing as the rumors said!
Boss...
Over here!
This sure is an impressive cave!
What IS all this?
This is our escape route.
Escape route?
This cave is a giant maze.
It means we've got a safe hiding place if pirates show up.
We're the fastest in the world when it comes to running and groveling!
The fastest in the world?
That's how we survive here in the Grand Line.
We don't have a military, and since it's a remote island, the Navy always has us on a backburner.
Speaking of the Navy...
Wasn't that girl earlier wearing a Navy coat?
What is the history behind that?
She wears it in memory of her father.
He was a great man.
He couldn't stand by as the island was constantly attacked by passing pirates,
so he stayed on this island, far from other Marines, in order to protect us.
"In memory of..." So I assume...
It happened about five years ago.
He was fighting alone against some pirates, and that's when he died.
Three years later, Boss arrived out of nowhere.
He warmed up to Yoko right away, and remains the island's Guardian Angel to this day.
Perhaps Boss' strength reminds her of her father's.
You sure we can enter your city?
We're pirates, you know.
You people are a special case.
Here, you can see it now.
Oh, a windmill! It's huge!
We're so high up!
And here I thought this was just a huge rock, but the other side is full of life, huh?
Anyway, how do I say this...
The buildings are each of completely different style.
What a strange place.
Figured it out yet?
The island was uninhabited when we first arrived, but that was only the beginning.
Oddly enough, all of us had come here from the same sea,
and we built this city to reflect our hometowns.
Welcome, Straw Hat-masters!
This is the village of those who came from East Blue, Kansorn Island!
Also known as Little East Blue!
Who'd have thought we'd meet the famous rookies from East Blue!
Zoro-san! You're from Frost Moon village, right?
We've got the Dojo from that village! Please have a look!
Dojo?
Sanji-san, you came from Baratie, didn't you?
Please have a taste of food from our town's Baratie!
It's really good!
You've got a Baratie here?
What? You don't have anyone from Syrup village?
Hm, I think Luigia-san was from there.
Luigia?
Yeah. He lives in the biggest mansion in town.
Mansion?
There was only one mansion in Syrup village, and that was Kaya's...
They're all so cheerful...
All pirates are the same!
I wonder if Luffy and the others are alright?
No need to worry, Chopper.
They'll probably contact us soon enough.
You think so?
Anyway, shouldn't we prepare the bug cage?
Yeah...if that thing joins our crew, we'll need it.
See?
I-It's me! Nami, you there?
Usopp? Yeah, I'm here.
What's up? Did you catch the beetle?
Nah, that's not-
SHADDAP! Be quiet for a sec, will ya?!
I got it already!
Well, think you could come over here for a bit?
There's a village on the other side of the island.
They really wanna meet you!
What do you mean "You"?! Call her "Nami-sama"!
What the hell?
Anyway, just get over here! Please!
Huh?! Wait just minute, Usopp!
He hung up...
Why is it only you?
Who knows...
Well, I guess I'll just go have a look.
I'll leave the rest to you guys!
Sure! We'll handle it!
She's gone...
So, that's the island?
The island is surrounded by large rocks and many underwater reefs
making it difficult for any ships to reach it.
Well, this ship won't have to worry about any reefs.
Now, let the hunt begin!
Our prey is the giant beetle who ran away from Shiki's hideout!
Let's go, men!
AYE, AYE SIR!
Next time, on One Piece:
Movie Special Episode
Little East Blue is Targeted