Wait, PX-1.
This guy...
...He's the real one!
If you were to go on a vacation, where would you like to go?
Hey, Zoro!
If you don't hurry up and run...
Zoro... san...?
What just happened...?
Zoro...
...vanished!
Z...
Zoro...
DAMN YOU!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ZORO?!
HE WAS...
HE WAS JUST...
...RIGHT HERE!
Zoro...?
Z-Zoro?
Zoro?
Zoro!
ZORO!!!
Stop it, Chopper!
Don't be reckless!
Zoro... Where did you go?!
He doesn't have any self-control...
Regardless, that Kuma boy...
What is that bastard doing here?
Bartholomew Kuma...
This is why you can't trust pirates!
They're surrounded over there, too?
Zoro just vanished!
Does this mean that the real one showed up at last?
There's no mistake...
I've seen that ability before...
Back at Thriller Bark, he used that...
...to get rid of a girl...
...and she never came back!
This is really bad!
Hey! What'd he do to Zoro?!
Where'd he disappear off to?!
I have no obligation to answer.
I'm the most tight-lipped man in the world.
They say that anyone who gets blasted off by his pads...
is sent flying through the sky for three days and three nights...
though I'm not sure whether it's true or not.
Nobody except the person who was sent flying knows where to, though...
but it definitely won't be on this island...
or anywhere else where you might meet them anytime soon.
They might end up on the edge of some distant sea.
What?!
Say something, you damned freak?!
Where'd you send Zoro?!
So, he finally showed up...
The real Warlord...
There are three of them who look the same...
What's going on?!
Th... The real Warlord...
Don't come any closer!
Damn it... Stop!
Stop it!
I've got 8000 subordinates, you know!
Hey! Can't you hear me?! Don't come any closer!
Look out, Usopp! Behind you!
Behi...?!
Usopp-san!
Stay out of this.
He even got rid of his own comrade?!
Even PX-1?!
What're you doing with your allies, Bear?!
Run, the three of you!!
Luffy!
Just run away, everyone!
We'll think things over once we're safe!
GO!!!
Hey, let's go!
But... Zoro...
Like he said, we'll think about that later!
Let's go!
Let's go! The beam only grazed me!
I'll carry you on my shoulder, so let's hurry!
Be careful, you two!
Brook!
BROOK!
I shall protect you!
Even if it costs me my life!!
...Though I am already d...
BROOK!!!
He did it again!
Damn it... What am I doing?!
Two of my comrades just vanished before my eyes!
Damn it!
Sanji!
Get going, Usopp!
Don't be ridiculous! We're leaving together, Sanji!
Why, you...!
Stop it, Sanji!!
Damn pad-bastard!!
SANJI!
D-Don't come any closer!
Don't come any closer!
Don't come any closer...
TL Note: Flame Star
Damn!
Usopp!
Run!
RUN!!
Usopp!!
Sanji?
Damn it to hell!
STOP IT, SANJI!!
Even Sanji...
What's going on...?
What are we gonna do?
No way...
Everyone's...
The situation over there seems pretty hopeless...
I'd like to help them out, but I'm getting too old...
You're holding off a navy admiral on your own,
and you're still trying to do more?
You're making me look bad here, so just cut it out already!
You are the "Dark King", Rayleigh, are you not?
Kuma?
Luffy?
You really expect me to believe what you just said?
Decide that for yourself.
I am already endangering my own position.
Just what're you planning to do, Kuma?
As long as it doesn't directly affect the World Government...
we have no obligation to get along with the navy.
I will not answer that question.
You bastard!
Luffy!
Let's go!
Get out of our way!
What?!
Wait!
You can't, Luffy!
Luffy!
NOOO!!!
Luffy! Help!
NAMI!!!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Luffy! Help!
Luffy!
Chopper...
CHOPPER!!!
Stop it...
Stop it!
PLEASE, STOP THIS!!!
Luffy!
ROBIN!!!
Luffy!!
What...
What's...
...wrong with me?!
Anyway, you!
Join my crew!
I am glad to be alive!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
Well, get on, Franky!
On my ship!
There's no choice. I'll give you a hand!
I, Franky, accept the position as your shipwright!
Why are you trying to save me?!
I just want to die!
I still haven't heard you say it!
SAY THAT YOU WANT TO LIVE!
I WANNA LIVE!
I'm gonna keep fighting, even though I don't have any friends!
As long as that Doctor's flag is there...
You do have friends!
I'm your friend!
I'm gonna stay here, but...
If you ever feel like it...
then feel free to come visit us...
SHUT UP!
LET'S GO!!
What do you want?
You don't know anything...
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you to get off this island, didn't I?!
Luffy...
Help...
NAMI!!!
YOU'RE ONE OF US!!!
Wait.
We've both got stupid dreams...
I'll be your ship's cook.
THANKS FOR TAKING SO DAMN GOOD CARE OF ME ALL THIS TIME!
What're you talking about? Get onboard, already.
We're friends, aren't we?
Gomu Gomu no
Bullet
You idiot...
Did you really think...
that you could defeat me?!
Please...
LET ME BE A PART OF YOUR CREW AGAIN!
IDIOT!
HURRY UP AND TAKE MY HAND!
A wound in the back is a disgrace to a swordsman.
I'LL NEVER...
LOSE AGAIN!
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT...
...PIRATE KING?!
Zoro...
Usopp...
Sanji...
Nami...
Chopper...
Robin...
Franky...
Brook...
Everyone...
I couldn't even...
...save a single one of my friends!
So, you're gonna send him off and be done with it?
I hope you have a good explanation for this.
This is a huge problem, you know?
We will never...
...meet again.
Farewell.
Grand Line...
Sabaody Archipelago...
Grove 12...
On this day...
...the pirate crew, led by captain Monkey D. Luffy...
...the Straw Hat Pirates...
...was completely and utterly defeated.
Next time, we'll be having one of our rare period drama specials!
This time, we'll be holding the once in a hundred years,
Great Miko ritual, with the Goshinpo on the line.
We have to make an appearance as well!
Goshinpo eh? Sounds yummy.
You're gonna eat it?!
Next time, on One Piece:
Special Historical Arc
Boss Luffy Appears Again
I'm gonna be a detective!