Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
In response to an emergency call for help they received,
Luffy and the others head for the opposite side of the island.
Nami's group had been captured and trapped in a mysterious facility on Punk Hazard Island...
I came to this island to rescue my son!
I will kill all who get in my way!
There they are!
Fire!  Don't let them get away!
Stop right there!  I'll take you on!
Who are they?!
Who are you?
Gigantic... children?
C-Children?!
What's going on here?!
Save the Children!
The Crew's Battle Begins
The Frozen Lands
-The Mysterious Facility-
Biscuits Room
-Sanji's Side-
Who are these kids?
Perhaps this is some sort of nursery?
They're absolutely huge.  Are they giants?
Did we drop anchor at an island of giants?
But there are some smaller kids too...
Then, maybe this facility
doesn't discriminate between races?
I don't see any adults, though.
Hey, who are you?
I don't know them...
Ah, could you be the frozen people?
You made it out?!
Frozen?
What's she talking about?
This island is getting more and more mysterious.
That's...
You're a robot!
W-What?!
It's a robot!
So cool!
I love robots!
They're the best!
What do you mean, best?
Sanji-kun?!
Robot!  Robot!  Robot!
Oh my, you...
like armored me that much?!
Hey, what did she mean by frozen people?
Oh, look!  It's a stuffed animal!
What?
A stuffed raccoon dog!
I'm a reindeer!
So cute!
Help me!
I want one!
Franky is ridiculously popular with these kids!
Swirly eyebrows!
Can it, you damn brat!
You're right!  How weird!
Cut it out!
Stag beetle robot!
I can change my hairstyle at will!
Like it?  Like it?  Like it?
Hands come out!
I can even...
pick my nose!
Super!
Hey!  Will somebody listen to me?!
Sheesh.
I say, all of you!
Do any of you know of a child named Momonosuke?!
He is a young man, he is!
Scary!
The head spoke!
Run!
Hey, you guys!  Can you tell us-
Wait!
Shut up, idiot!  We can't ask them anything!
You're just scaring them whenever you speak!
The door to the Biscuits Room is open!
Here they come!
Anyway, let's just get to the far side of the room!
It must be the pirates from before.
Don't let them escape!
What kind of facility is this?!
Please tell me!
I seek a child named Momonosuke!
Stop talking!
A woman raised her hand against me!
This is a shame for a warrior, it is!
I want to slice open my belly!
Go ahead!  You're getting on my nerves,
you chauvinist pig!
Damn escapees!
You're not getting out of here!
Wait!
Calm down.  Guns and explosives are forbidden here.
We can't use anything stronger than gas bullets.
If we hit the children, we'll answer to the Master!
Hey...
Are you really planning to cross this lake, Luffy?!
The Burning Lands
-Luffy's Side-
Yup.
And just how are you planning to cross this lake?!
Parts of it are on fire.  Others are frozen!
Then the water temperature might be fine.
And I am quite sweaty...
Shall we swim across?
Don't be absurd!
Me and Robin can't swim, you know.
You want to ride us across, don't you?!
Why should I have to...
Stop staring at me!
Even Zoro wouldn't be that considera-
Wait, you're actually ready to do it?!
Well, whatever I think...
If we don't cross the lake,
we'll be taking a huge detour.
Guess there's no choice.  I'll handle it!
Alright, let's do this!
Fan Grass
What's this grass?
It's a boat!  That's amazing, Usopp!
And this fan grass will serve as oars!
You have all sorts of seeds, I see.
How wonderful.
The Boyn Islands were a treasure trove
of strange plants, after all!
Whenever I entered a dangerous area,
I managed to snag some convenient plants!
I survived on that island for two whole years,
so you could say that there's nothing I can't han-
Get aboard, Usopp!
You'll get left behind.
Hey!  I was the one who made that!
Alright!
Cast off!
To the land of shaved ice!
Row, damn you!
The wind is so strong!
And it's a headwind, at that!
Of course.
The extreme temperature difference
on the island causes the wind to blow.
The water's boiling out here.
If we'd tried to swim, it would've been a disaster.
We're not really making much progress.
You have to row, dammit!
You won't get away.
Wait, you bastards!
Look out!
It's the centaur from before!
Hey!  Did you decide to join my crew after all?
Did you just invite him again?!
Will you stop asking every freak we meet to join us?!
A horn?
Boss!
Boss?
That reminds me,
didn't the Snail Phone say...
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
The intruders are heading your way!  Please take care of them!
Something just appeared on the shore.
Is that his boss?
So the emergency transmission was from him?
In that case,
it would be silly for him to try to attack us!
One of them is carrying a sword.
Is that the...
samurai who cut down our comrades?
Alright, children, out of the way.
Out of the way!
That's dangerous!
Hey, Robot-san.
You aren't fom this island, are you?
Of course not.  But, boy... I am a cybor-
Do you have a ship?
Of course we do!  Our Sunny is the world's-
Save us!
What does he mean?
Please, save us!
What do you mean, save you?
This isn't a nursery?!
Lady!
Please, help us!
Please!
Nami-san, don't stop!
Take us out of here!
Please!
Nami-san, hurry!
We're not sick any more!
We're all fine!
Sick?  What kind of disease?
Damn kids!
Listen up, children!
You see, those people are all really scary people!
You mustn't get too close to them!
Really?  They didn't seem that way.
They were deceiving you!
So the stag beetle robot is a bad guy?
That's right.
Raccoon Dog-chan too?
Yes.
And the guy with the swirly eyebrows?
Yeah, listen to us...
We will protect you, alright?
We will protect all of you sickly children.
We will...
make them fall asleep using the smoke gun.
Please... Wait...
I...
I wanna go home!
Wait!
Those damn brats!
Please, wait!
Let us out of here!
Please, Lady!  Help us!
Now, wait up, children!
Sorry... we're being chased, so...
What's going on?!
Hey, let's take them with us!
Idiot!  We don't even know where to go ourselves!
What good would come
from bringing all those kids along?!
But what...
is this sadness?!
Then...
come save us later!
I know, even though
I haven't gone outside the building!
This island is empty, isn't it?!
There's no town here and no people!
That's why nobody's come to help us!
I wanna see Mommy and Daddy!
Lady!  Please come back!
Come back to save us!
Hurry up, Nami-san!
Let's help these children!
What are you saying, Nami-san?!  There's no reason to do that!
They even said they were sick!  This might be a hospital!
We only just met them,
and we don't know what's going on here!
It's not like we're a charity that rescues children!
You think I don't know that?
But when children are crying for me to save them...
how can I turn my back on them?!
Lady!
Quickly, they're getting away!
Those kids are in the way!
Who cares?!  Kill the children too!
But Master will...
It's still better than letting them get away!
I won't make it in time!
Sanji-kun!
Swirly bro!
Awesome!
That man...
is incredibly skilled!
Damn it!
Raccoon Dog-chan!
A rocket punch!
T-They're...
not running away anymore!
When Nami-san is kind... (only ever to children)...
she is truly wonderful!
I'm falling for her all over again!
Chopper.  You go on ahead with Nami-san.
Sure, leave it to me!
Hey, kids!  Follow the beautiful lady and the Kung Fu raccoon dog!
I'll hold back the pursuers!
But don't get the wrong idea!
I'm only responding
to the longing in Nami-san's heart to save you.
If anything,
I hate you for stealing Nami-san's affection!
Swirly bro, thanks!
Shut it, you damn brat!  Get lost!
Come on, let's go!
Follow us!
Right!
Damn!  The children!
You don't have to help me out, Franky.
Armored Franky can't disappoint his fans, can he?
We will be your opponents.
Now, bring it!
Snow!  Snow!  Snow!
Playing in the snow is so much fun!
Near the mysterious facility
-Brook's Side-
Killing time is the best!
Robin-san told me to wait here...
but Luffy-san and the others sure are taking their time!
Ta-daah!  Snowmen!
Let's rearrange the eyes and nose, like this.
It looks like me!
Hmm?
W-W-Wait!
Who are you?  Why are you?
Just what...
Whaaaat?!
J-Just a torso?!
To save the children, Nami and Chopper
frantically press on inside the mysterious facility.
As Sanji and Franky fight for their lives,
Brook is at the mercy of the powerful torso samurai,
and at last, a duel begins between the two!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Duel of Swordsmanship
Brook VS Mysterious Torso-Samurai
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A Duel of Swordsmanship
Brook VS Mysterious Torso-Samurai