It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has come to Marineford...
to save his brother Ace, who is about to be executed.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates have been advancing on the execution platform.
Now, they've made it past the defensive walls,
and broke into the plaza.
During the Navy's fierce counterattack,
Luffy gained the support of Whitebeard's entire force,
and now desperately runs toward Ace.
Men!
Old Man...
As of this moment...
lend Straw Hat Luffy...
all of your strength!
The path...
is open!
Here I come, Ace!
Grandpa!  Please move!
There's no way I'll step aside!
I am a Vice Admiral from Navy HQ!
I was fighting pirates long before you were born!
Gramps!
If you want to get past me, then it'll be over my dead body!
Straw Hat Luffy!
That is...
the path you chose!
Please, Grandpa!
Let me past!
Luffy!
C-Coby!
Pull yourself together, Coby!
Damn that Straw Hat bastard!
How dare he do this to Coby so heartlessly!
He will not be forgiven!
Must...
become stronger...
He's alive!  Thank God!
Where's Luffy-san?
That Straw Hat bastard...
and Vice Admiral Garp!
Are those two really gonna fight?
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat is almost at the execution platform... this is bad!
At this range, we can't miss!
Our target is Straw Hat Luffy!
Insolent fools!
Back away!
Pirate Empress!  Just whose side are you on anyway?!
Luffy, first and foremost.
But what if a stray bullet were to hit Vice Admiral Garp?!
What are you saying?
Vice Admiral Garp... don't you know who that man is?
He is my grandfather!
Grandfather?!
Vice Admiral Garp is?!
Obviously he will be, once I marry Luffy!
What's...
obvious?
Do something, Straw-Hat-boy!
If vyou don't act fast, the bridge will fall!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-kun!
Luffy...
Straw Hat Luffy!
I've told you already!
If you want to get past me, then it'll be over my dead body!!
Bastard!
Grandpa!
Why do I have to fight these guys?
Training.
Training?
But I'm hungry... and tired of getting hit!
Don't be soft!
One day you're going to become the world's strongest marine!
I'm not gonna be a marine... I'm gonna be a pirate!
What?  Don't be stupid!
Ouch!  Grandpa's fist hurts most!
Take this!
And that!
Gomu Gomu no-
Stupid kid.
There's something I need to tell you Grandpa.
Yeah, what is it?
I'm not going to be some pirate!
So you finally came to your senses!
Yeah, I'm not going to be just any pirate...
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
This is that Red Hair's influence!
Get out of the way, you!
I've gotta knock some sense into this kid's corrupted mind!
Grandpa!
I'll never let you become one of their kind!
Even after tiring yourself out and falling asleep...
your stomach is still as active as it always is.
You probably hate me for being such a strict granddad.
But Luffy... the reason why I put you through this harsh training,
and want you to become a marine,
is because I don't want you to go down the wrong path.
That is my wish.
Luffy, I have a treat for you today!
The Navy left us plenty of food.
You can eat as much of your favorite meat as you want!
Grandpa...
I can't do it, Grandpa!
Please move!
If you don't kill me, Ace will die!
Never!
It will happen, no matter how much you hate it!
I'm not holding back!
Luffy, I now regard you as...
my enemy!
Garp...
Dammit!  What's wrong with me?!  This isn't the time to...
The Old Man, my brother and my crew...
are falling, and yet...
I'm so happy...
my tears won't stop...
Even now that it's come to this... I want to live...
Vice Admiral Garp!
Gramps...
You play the parent after all, Garp.
Looks like he's gonna make it to the execution platform.
Didn't you say he was a reckless piece of trash?
I still think he's reckless.
How does he plan to release Ace?
Get lost, brat!
Your guard was down.
Old Man!
Finally...
Finally!
I finally made it!
Luffy!
You're one hell of a guy...
Ace!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Hold on a second.
Take this.
This is the key to your brother's handcuffs.
Here's the key.
Luffy...
You...
What the hell is that...
Look... Fleet Admiral Sengoku is using his ability!
This is the first time I've seen it!
Did you really think that I would let you get away?
Sengoku!
A giant Buddha?!
To think you had something so valuable, Straw Hat Luffy...
The key!
Aim!
Hold your positions and be ready to fire at any time!
This is bad!  The key...
Straw Hat Luffy...
You are also a renowned criminal worthy of the death penalty.
Now, as brothers, I will execute you myself!
What happened... I lost consciousness all of a sudden.
Straw Hat?
Three!  What are you doing here?
What is that?!
Hey, Three... protect Ace with a wall!
He became huge...
The execution platform is collapsing!
What just happened?!
Ace hasn't died yet!
We're falling!
I'll make a key!  Those shackles will be off in no time!
Gotcha!
Captain Buggy!  That's Brother Three!
What?!
What's he doing frolicking around in that cosplay?!
Didn't he escape a long time ago?
The dignity of Navy HQ is riding on Fire Fist Ace's execution proceeding smoothly.
It must succeed!
Was that... the executioners?
I see.
Straw Hat Luffy broke into the plaza, but Admiral Borsalino stopped him in his tracks.
Straw Hat!
You have to save your brother, no matter what!
Mister Two...
Very well, what do we do now?
We rescue Straw-chan!
Because he's my friend!
That's all the reason I need!
Your... friend?
Bon-chan... The Gates are closing.
We're... going.
Thank you!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan...
You have to save your brother, no matter what!
He didn't run away.
He remained loyal to Straw Hat right to the end!
Right, you lot hurry up with the preparations!
Yes sir!
Has the other one still not shown up?
What's taking him so long?!
He's taking a while to get ready because of the sudden change of orders...
Hey, hurry up!
Right, let's go!
If I were to tell you...
that I'm here to honor the will of my late brother...
would you laugh at me?
I would never laugh at that!
Fire!  Blast the execution platform and everything with it!
Save your brother, Straw Hat!
I'm on it!
This can't happen!
Straw-Hat-boy!
No way...
Ace!
Brother Three!
The three of them were hit!
The Seastone handcuffs make Fire Fist's body vulnerable!
He has to be dead!
Straw Hat too, without a doubt...
There's a tunnel of fire coming out of the smoke!
You never change, Luffy.
Never listening to a single word I say.
Always doing the the dumbest things.
Good work!
Thank God!
Ace!
U-Unbelievable!
Straw Hat... and Brother Three...
Ace!
Ace has been freed and the pirates' morale skyrockets.
And Whitebeard makes an important decision.
Next time, on One Piece:
Ace is Rescued!
Whitebeard's Final Captain's Orders!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!