Translations, Vegard Aune
Timing, Chilli-kun, G_I_A
Typesetting, DeSi
Editing, mithrandiryod
Encoding, SockPain
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
QCing, SockPain
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
While heading for their next destination, Fishman Island...
Luffy and the others met the mermaid, Caimie.
A group, called the Flying Fish Riders, had captured her friend, Hacchin, and to save him...
Luffy and the others changed course to the Flying Fish Riders' base.
Whether it's from the sea, or the sky, we're ready for'em!
We're gonna beat'em all!
YOU GUYS!
PREPARE FOR BATTLE!
YEAH!!!
Tragedy!
The Truth of the Unmasked Duval
Well, well...  Who's got the freshest fish here?
Hey, hey, hey!
Alright! Him!
I got him!
What?
My turn!
Uh, wait...
This is awesome!
Whoo! I'm flying!
Luffy's riding one of those things?!
Just leave him alone.
Take this!
Bombs!
Damn!
Nami-san! Robin-chwan! Are you alright?
That was close!
Geez... If they had hit a lady with that, I wouldn't have let them live.
Pull in the sail! It'll get in the way!
Everybody, dive!
Understood!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
You idiots!
We're in the middle of a fight, so what the heck do you think you're doing?!
I'b sowwy...
Oh, and why'd you two try to save him? You're Devil Fruit users too, right?!
I seem to have troubled you, too...
It's even worse when we have to save all three of you hammers!
Idiot, don't waste my time!
The Macro crew!
Now, let's get Caimie back while we have the chance!
Yeah!
Hey, Straw! Could you give us a hand, here?
Caimie! Pappagg!
You freed me from the ropes and the cage! Thanks, Roronoa! You're a nice guy, huh?
It was the captain's orders, idiot.
Hachi!
Hacchin!
You guys! You took advantage of the fact that I couldn't move and beat me as much as you wanted!
I haven't punched you yet, Hachi! I'll finish you off with my Fishman Karate!
Man, you've got terrible luck!
Stop flappin' your mouth like that, damn it! We've got much worse in store for you!
Now, come! I've developed a new style of Goldfish Fencing just for you!
The waters will be stained with blood!
Hacchin!
Takoyaki Punch!
We'll let you go for now!
Hacchin!
Caimie! Pappagg!
I'm so glad, Hacchin!
I'm so sorry, Caimie, Pappagg! I was going to save you!
Don't worry about it, Hachi!
Ah! Watch out!
Don't forget that this is our territory! After all, the ones who caught you in the first place...
were us, the Flying Fish Riders!
Roronoa!
Zoro-chin!
You need to watch yourselves...
Get Back. You can just leave this to us
Thanks for everything, Roronoa! I'm really sorry for what happened back then!
Back then?
I hurt you pretty badly with my Six-Sword Style...
You didn't even land a single blow, as far as I remember!
Oh, that's right.
We did it, Chopper! Now, take this!
Fire!
Bullseye! Did you see that, you damn fish?!
Usopp, you're amazing!
Anyone up for the Zero Fight?
The Zero Fight?
Interesting! But isn't that move life-threatening for us too?
I'm sure that you will be more than up to paying the medical fees?
I'll give you a million!
I'll do it, Head! I'll go! Move, move, move!
A really huge guy is coming! And he's swinging a massive club...
He isn't steering at all... Don't tell me that he is just going for a collision...
If that giant hits us at that speed, the ship won't hold...
Luffy! You take care of the fish.
Sure.
Interesting... With this size and speed, the impact will be like a small meteor!
He's not changing his course at all, just like Sanji said!
However, he's not the only one... who can deal some damage while in the air!
Gum Gum Balloon!
This'll be our dinner tonight!
That's so cool, you two!
Looking at it up close, it really is big.
Damn... This crew doesn't seem like it'll go down easily.
Usopp!
Now that I think about it, there are a lot of them flying around up there...
How many will we have to beat before it ends?
I wanna ride one, dammit! Don't think I've given up just because of what happened earlier!
Give it up! I won't save you again!
How can this be?
What's up, Brook?
To think that my first real action as a member of the Straw Hat Crew was to drown...
It would be a disgrace if I did not help you!
It is about time we reduced the number of those Flying Fish...
Please observe!
What an incredible jump!
What's with that skeleton mask guy?
We'll skewer you!
Lullaby Song!
Wow! They all fell asleep...
You too?!
Music is... Power!
Excuse me!
We fell asleep!
Damn him, what was that?!
He used some sort of dirty trick!
It is no trick!
It is music!
Wait!
He's pretty good, that Brook!
Looks fun... Here I come!
Wait, Luffy! Not again!
Alright, I caught you! I won't forgive you if you dive again!
Hey, you're asleep?!
Hey, hey! Wake up!
That guy! He went into the Head's room!
You saw it...?
You...!
It seems like you know me...
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com!
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net!
R-Roronoa!
Zoro-chin...
I have reached my limit! I have a muscle cramp!
Though I do not have any muscles to have a cramp in!
Brook, you're pretty enthusiastic, huh?
You took out quite a few of the Flying Fish.
I am glad to have been of help!
But please... let me rest for a while...
Zoro-san...
as I thought, your injuries...
from Thriller Bark still haven't healed...
I won't let these fish beat me! Don't worry about it!
You let down your guard, Roronoa!
Six-Sword Style...
Octopus-Arm Danger!
You saved me, huh?`
That's right! You guys were spacing out and all...
Hacchin! You were really cool!
Just what I'd expect from you, Hachi!
Really?
Die, fishman!
Right! Excuse me!
I thought I was gonna die! Thanks!
You are quite welcome!
I told you to watch yourself, didn't I?
Don't take them on one by one... Get in formation!
Note: Formation (Hentai)
Pervert?
Note: Pervert (Hentai)
You called?
Attack in flying formation!
Note: Flying Formation (Hentai hikou)
Delinquent pervert?
Note" Delinquent pervert (Hentai hikou)
You mean me?
It's not you!
They're here!
Here I am! Here!
Welcome!
A woman? It's a shame, but we were ordered to kill everyone!
Can you kill me?
What the-?!
Too bad. Mirage Tempo.
Beware of thunderclouds of despair!
Dos Mano... Clutch!
Split-Hoof Diamond!
Don't break formation!
I knew it, they're calling for me.
No, they're not!
Now!
Huh? They didn't mean me?
What?! Bullets don't affect him?!
Strong Hammer!
Amazing! They're all really strong, Pappagg!
To think they'd go this far...
We were just gonna grab Hachi and escape...
Take this!
Damn! Franky! We need to get the ship ashore!
They're at an advantage out here in the ocean!
That's probably why they reside out here, you know.
They're not gonna give us a chance to steer the ship!
Luffy!
Run! A huge guy is coming!
Is it the Iron Mask?!
The masked guy and a cow!
A cow?
That's Motobaro's voice! It's the Head!
Getting yourselves knocked down in droves...
What's that?! Something showed up!
You're not just bugs, y'know! Flying Fish Riders!
H-He crushed his own house...
I don't need this base any more, as long as I can kill the Straw Hats!
We're so sorry, Head! We'll draw them out to sea and finish them off right...
Move it!
I have no need for a fishman, mermaid, or glove! If you wanna run, then just get lost!
I'm a starfish!
I didn't enter the slave-trading market 'cause I wanted to!
You guys understand that, right?!
Of course, Head!
What a great day this is!
The man whom I wanted to kill so badly that I even saw him in my dreams, is right here.
I'm so grateful!
I guess there is a God, huh?
One day, I was suddenly thrown into the depths of Hell because of that man!
Hey, isn't he looking at us while he's talking?
Today, I'll kill ya right here, even if I die myself...
Pirate... Black Leg Sanji!
I really wanted to meet'cha!
Oh, crap! The Head's really pissed off!
Me? That guy wants to kill me?
Sanji, who's that guy?
It seems like he's got some sort of grudge against you...
Could it be something that happened at the restaurant? Try to remember!
If it's something from back then, I did plenty of things that people might be mad at me for...
Let him shoot you! You've deserved it!
Quit playin' dumb, Black Leg!
We're talkin' about somethin' recent here!
Crap! Those are harpoons!
But if it's something recent, then I'm even more confused!
W-What? There's something strange about these harpoons...
These're my scorpion venom harpoons!
If they hit'cha, ya'll be headed for the afterlife in three minutes!
Know the depths of my fury!
Nami-san, watch out!
Damn bastard, I can't remember at all! Who are you?!
I'm gonna kill ya and yer crew!
I saw what was underneath that mask.
Really? Who is he?
Don't be surprised. You've seen his face too!
Me, too?
That bastard...!
He knocked off Duval-sama's iron mask!
Very well... Take a close look at my scarred face!
What the-?!?!?!
No way!
He's...!
My...
Oh, my...
I wanna cry!
I've been waitin' for this day...
I decided to murder ya, and so I set out to sea!
But lookin' for ya would be a problem, y'know...
After all, yer wanted poster and yer true face didn't match!
Even if the marines or bounty hunters ran into ya, they just might' not notice ya!
Nah, there's no way that'd happen!
Those guys'd definitely find ya!
Head...!
They'd find ya, and then they'd say...
"I found you!"
"Black Leg Sanji!"
And then I told'em...
"I dunno anyone like that!"
"I ain't even a pirate!"
QUIT SCREWING WITH ME!
The Sunny's in trouble!
We're gonna die! We'll sink!
Calm down! This week, I'm exceptionally super!
I'll show you the Sunny's true power!
Awesome, Sunny!
Next time, on One Piece,
Explosion!
The Sunny's Super Secret Weapon Gaon Cannon.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Explosion!
The Sunny's Super Secret Weapon Gaon Cannon