Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
The crew received a distress call and landed on Punk Hazard,
a bizarre island that is split
between a burning side and a frozen one.
Both the Straw Hats and Smoker...
are nuisances who
could reveal this island to the Government.
We'll take both of them out in one stroke!
Send word to Joker!
Yes, Sir!
I could never even figure out
why you joined the Warlords!
What is your goal?!
There are things you can't see unless you move...
Smoker!
My heart...
I don't have to tell you anything.
Reunited After Two Years!
Luffy and Law
No!
Tashigi-chan, he's way too strong for you!
Please let go of me!
I didn't become a marine just to
let someone else protect me at times like this!
If you go back under that curtain,
you'll just get cut to pieces again!
Just leave this to Smokey!
The curtain's gone!
Alright, now!
Go, Crocotaur!
What could that be?
A ship?
Isn't that a warship?
Does that mean the Navy's here?
What?!  There wasn't anything here earlier!
What's going on?!  Did something happen to Master?
There's somebody over there!
Huh?  Isn't that...
Hey!  Hey!
Imagine meeting you!  It's me!
Thanks for everything you've done for me!
Straw-Hatter...
He's...
the guy we met in the Human Shop on Sabaody.
Trafalgar Law.  But now, he's...
Right, Trafal... Traf!
That guy helped me escape
during the Whitebeard war.
And he even treated my injuries!
He did?
That's right!
He saved my life, just like Jinbe!
Hey!
I never thought I'd meet you here!
Really, thanks a lot for before!
Huh?
Where's the talking bear and those guys?
Bring Straw-Hatter over here!
I'm gonna take him away from this place!
Let me take care of him for now!
I'm a doctor!
Where is Ace?!
What'll happen if we just let him be?
Well, to put it bluntly...
Like I said when we came to this island,
if his wounds reopen, he'll probably die.
Straw-Hatter will need complete rest
for another two weeks.
Understood.  Thanks for all you've done for us.
I'm impressed that you survived, Straw-Hatter.
But there is no need to feel indebted to me
for saving you back then.
I was just acting on a whim.
We are both pirates.  Don't forget that.
Guess you're right.
If we're both going for One Piece then that makes us enemies...
but I still owe a debt to a lot of people after what happened two years ago.
How lucky that I got to meet you
right after meeting Jinbe!
Really, thanks!
Hey!  There's a collapsed marine over there!
Isn't... that...
Hey... Please save me, Trafalgar!
Smoker-san!
Don't tell me...
Smoker-san?!
Smokey!
The Navy?!
W-What?  Isn't that...
Hey, this isn't good, Luffy!  The Navy's here!
R-Right!
Captain-chan, what's wrong?
Smokey, are you alright?!
Smoker-san!
I knew it, it's Old Smokey and his group!
That sure takes me back!
There's a hole... in his...
Smoker-san!
In order to become a Warlord...
he delivered the hearts
of one hundred pirates to Navy HQ!
He's completely deranged!
How could you?!
How could you?!  How could you?!
Hey now, stop that.
I can't stand... such crudeness.
Tashigi-chan!
Dammit!  He got her again!
Even Smo-san is down!
What did he just do?!
You never learn, do you?
Don't get so serious.
Tashigi-chan!
Luffy, hurry up!  We're in danger here!
Oh, right!
Hey, Traf!  I wanted to ask...
Go behind the laboratory.
You'll find what you're looking for there.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
We both have something we want back.
He must mean me, thank goodness.
This is dangerous!  I'm a former pirate as well!
Alright, Luffy!  We've gotta get away from the Navy!
I wonder if Smokie's group will be alright?
Were they defeated by Traf?
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Fire!
Stop it, this isn't the time!
Smo-san and Captain-chan are...
It's so cold!
What can we do?  The children won't last much longer!
Mountain Outside of the Laboratory's Backdoor
-Sanji's Group-
Alright, I'll cut off my fur and give it to them.
Stop it!  That's my body!
You say that, but there aren't
any other warm coats around here.
I wonder if there's a mountain hut nearby?
Oh, a camera, a mirror...
and a s-shower!  A mountain hut would have those!
I'm gonna tie you up!
Who's who?
Law is so scary!
I see that I have no other choice!
Put a leaf on each of your heads!
Huh?!  This isn't the time for nonsense!
The kids are about to collapse from the cold!
Besides, there isn't a single plant on this island!
So there aren't any leaves!
Then use rocks or something else, it matters not.
Make haste!
Fine... It seems like you got some sort of plan here.
I'll find rocks for the kids!
We've done it.  So, what's up with this?
If this is just some silly superstition to make the cold go away,
I'm gonna flatten you!
Alright!
Doron!
Whaaaaat?!
What's going on?!
We've got coats!  And shoes too!
How?!  What did he do?!
Gloves!
It's warm!
It's so warm!
The truth is, I consumed a rare kind of fruit,
and ever since, I have been able to use magic...
to change any object into a disguise!
I am not familiar with clothing from foreign lands, but will these do?
Though I must warn you that it's magic,
so the clothes will vanish if you remove them.
Yay, thank you!
Hmph, don't go overboard!
You've got Devil Fruit powers?
Pardon me?  Devil?
But you know...
If you could do this...
why didn't you do it right away?!
But... it's such a waste to conceal those breasts.
Idiot!
T-That itches...
That itches, it does!
You just can't bring yourself
to say that you're hurt or that it's cold, huh.
It's because I'm a warrior.
There they are!  Hey guys!
Heeeey!
Heeey!  Heeey!
What are they doing here?
Everyone, are you alright?
Oh, it's them!
It's Luffy's group!  Zoro!  Usopp!
Robin!  Brook!
I'm so glad you're here!
Why is that idiot cook so enthusiastic?
Is he trying to stay warm?
What's that?  It looks like a bunch of giant kids, but...
Huh?!  Hey!
What're you doing?!  Cut it out, Franky!
The Straw Hats' Shelter
We're here!  This place will do.
This equipment looks like the stuff in the laboratory.
But it's all in pieces.
Maybe there was some kind of big explosion.
Well, as long as they shields us from the blizzard,
it doesn't matter.
So, where do we start?
That's gonna leave a scar on my fragile body!
I'll take care of you right away!
Wait, Sanji-kun!  What are you doing with my body?!
I'm Chopper!
My lower half has returned to me, it has!
Legson... My hind-legs...
I told you, there's no such creature!
This is quite surreal.
What an odd fellow.
The skeleton...
Is talking!
Are you alright, Nami-Sanji?
I wonder...
I dreamed that I was in a river...
I floated down the river,
through valleys of giant boobs.
This isn't the time to have dreams like that!
Hey, do the tank thing!
Can you shoot another beam?
C'mon!
Shut up!
Who is he on the inside again?
Huh?  Are you sure?
You're having a hard time dealing with this, right?
Let's just calm down and talk this over, everyone.
Alright!  So, who turned into who?
First off, I'm Franky!
Don't come to me if you get hurt!
I'm Chopper!
If you get hurt, I'll treat your wounds!
I'm Nami.
I'd rather die than fire a beam!
And... We...
are Nami-san!
I've been waiting for this!
I think Nami is being too crude.
I won't do it again!
Please, don't hurt Nami-san any more!
Don't do it, Nami!  You'll kill yourself!
If you touch my body,
it'll cost you 200 thousand beli!
Peeping will cost you 100 thousand!
How will I survive?!
How long are you gonna keep laughing?!  Stop acting like this doesn't concern you!
So, to start at the beginning...
this is the samurai from the Wano Kingdom
that we've heard about.
The distress call that we received
was meant for the Crocotaur they called Boss.
It came from one of his subordinates.
This is because the samurai
was relentlessly attacking the centaurs.
However, I was only attempting to find and rescue
my missing son, Momonosuke.
I merely cut down those who stood in my way.
And behold!
All these children were imprisoned in that facility.
Momonosuke must be in there somewhere as well!
Yeah, we weren't the only children.
We hadn't even learned all of the new kids' names yet.
But the question now is,
what happened after they sent the distress call?
It was the man from earlier.
They referred to him
as one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
What?!
Traf... is one of the Seven Warlords now?!
Indeed.
He joined their ranks during the past two years.
Before I knew it, I had been cut into three parts...
My head was thrown inside the facility.
My torso was simply abandoned.
My legs seem to have been used as monster bait.
I was running around, relying on my senses,
when I must have become stuck to something.
It was the back of the dragon's head.
Come to think of it, you were talking about that "Damn Warlord" earlier, right?
What?  It was just a pair of legs, right?  How could he have talked?
That's a good question.
Ah, that...
was my farts.
It is a talent I have possessed for a long time, it is.
You were farting?  That's disgusting!
Indeed it...
Ah!  The place is starting to stink!
In any case, it is quite comical
how you're just legs and a head!
I, on the other hand,
encountered someone who was just a torso!
That obviously must be this guy's torso!
Oh, you're right!
Did you see it?!  Where?!
Where did you encounter my torso?!
U-Umm...
Tashigi... chan?
Y-Yes...
Whaat?!  Are you really Tashigi-chan?!
Did your minds get swapped?
What's going on?  How did this happen?
Ummm, are you alright...
without a heart... Tashigi-chan?
Yes, strangely enough.
She's acting really shy.
Does that mean...
T-This is just terrifying!
Tashigi-chan and Smokey are...
The ships that were hidden near the laboratory...
had "CC" written on them.
Huh?  Really, Vice-Admiral Smoker?
Yeah.  Had they been the same ships that were used here in the past,
they should have said "PH" for Punk Hazard.
If we assume that someone above Law
is pulling his strings, and that "CC" is their initials...
then I have a hunch who it might be.
If he is on this island...
then it would explain quite a lot.
Doctor Vegapunk's former associate...
the scientist...
Caesar Clown.
What do you think you were doing, Law?!
I should be the one who is complaining...
Caesar!
The ruler of Punk Hazard,
located in the tempestuous New World...
surprisingly turns out to be
someone who has people's respect and admiration.
As the Straw Hats are shocked by this revelation,
Smoker is about to uncover the identity of Master, who has been pulling strings from the shadows!
Next time, on One Piece:
The World's Worst
The Terrifying Scientist, Caesar
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
The World's Worst
The Terrifying Scientist, Caesar