Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle,
the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
Another eruption!
We can see it right there!
Who cares about the Log Pose?
Hey, what's this?
The Snail Phone is crying.
Hey, what's wrong?!  Does your stomach hurt?
You idiot, that's an emergency signal.
Someone's calling for help.
So, if I pick up the phone,
we can communicate with them?
Wait, Luffy!  Less than fifty percent of emergency signals are real!
Please, help me!
My companions keep getting cut down.
The samurai's gonna kill us all!
Samurai?
Hey, what's your name?!
Where are you?!
Somebody please save me, I don't care who.
I'm on...
Punk Hazard!
It's so hot.
No doubt about it.  This is the right place.
This is Punk Hazard?
Those probably weren't people's houses.
This must have been a government facility.
What's wrong, Luffy?
Is that...
W-What?!  D-Do these things really exist?!
No, they're fictional creatures!
How could they exist for real?!
But just look at it!
What else could you call it?
A-
Awesome!
It's so cool!
Th-
This is no time to be admiring it!
So cool!
I'm out of here!
Its roars are cool too!
Cool!  Cool!
Who goes there?
Stay away from me!
What the hell are you doing?!
Hey!
This thing just talked!
D-D-Don't be ridiculous!  You must have imagined it!
Really?
It's hard enough to believe
that this is actually a dragon!
Is it really a dragon?
Yes, as hard as it is to believe.
A lizard's body with giant wings...
No matter how you look at it,
it's exactly what the legends describe!
Don't tell me...
Not good!
I-I-I-
It breathed fire!
How could a creature like this possibly exist?!
Am I dreaming?!
How interesting!
Now it's my turn!
It wasn't effective?!
He sure is tough!
Behind you!
Luffy!
It's looking right at us!
Bring it on!
Don't provoke it!
It can hear you!
I can sense your presence!
So it's true.  The dragon definitely just said something!
Damn it!  How can it be so strong and tough?!
Bastard!
Luffy!
Yeah?
He spoke.
Told you so!
I heard it too!  Why?!
It's flying!
So cool!
Pffft!  Are you companions of that Warlord?!
Warlord?
What are you talking about?!
Here come the flames!
From directly above?!  We can't dodge that!
It's so hot...
Just you wait, Nami-swan!
I'll cook up a delicious desert in a flash!
Ah, I know!
We just need to change our point of view!
What do you think?
If this was a sauna, it would feel nice, right?
Cola is super-spouting out of my entire body!
This is so weird...  The island's sky
is split into two sections, just as I thought.
A burning hot sky and an arctic one.
What's going on?
I hope Luffy and the others haven't melted.
Huh?  What was that?!
What's wrong?!
I don't know... I'm feeling...
I'm spacing out...
Did I... push myself... too... hard?
Are these... symptoms of de-cola-ization?
Y-You guys!
H-Huh?  Me too?
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Hot!
It's so hot... and that dragon just spoke again!
He said "Warlord", right?
Does he have some grudge against the Seven Warlords?
Oh, crap!
Luffy.
Leave him to me.
This time, I will cut him in half!
Right, I got it!
In that case...
Hot!  Hot!  Hot!
I'll knock him down to the ground!
Even his body is hot!
Poooh- I must say, this is pleasantly cool!
Poooh- The flames are quite refreshing -pooh!
Ah... Stop that...
That tickles, it does!
Cease this!
I command you to cease this, I do -poooh!
I knew it!
Hey!  This is incredible!
There's a human sticking out of the dragon's back!
Huuuh?!  What's going on?!
So the one speaking earlier was...
You bastard!
Eat wings, why don't you!
Dumbass!
Zoro!  He's falling to you!
Usopp!
Alright!
Incredible!
This dragon looks delicious!
We can barbecue it on the island's flames!
Great idea!
Nami-swan!
This time, I thought I'd make us a cold shellfish crêpe!
Along with some champagne!
Huh?  Are you sleeping?
Mist?
No...
Damn it!  I've already inhaled a lot of it!
They've all been knocked out by the gas!
Is this a natural gas unique to the New World?
Or has someone boarded the ship?
I hope those four on the island...
have a Baby Snail Phone with them.
I have to... tell them...
Two humans.
One iron man.
And one pet.
Tie them all up!
Yes, Sir!
Pirates are ideal for our purposes.
Even if they go missing, nobody will care.
Let's take them straight to the Master.
Luffy and the others
saved somebody from the dragon...
but they are shocked
when they see his bizarre appearance.
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others
have been captured by someone...
and they are locked in a mysterious room.
There, they witness an unbelievable sight!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew is Astonished!
The Shocking Samurai Who is Only a Head!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!