Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But once there, they found themselves
in an all-out war against the New Fishman Pirates,
who plotted to overthrow Ryuuguu Kingdom.
After a long, fierce battle, Luffy finally defeated Hody,
and put an end to their schemes.
Alright, hoist the sails!
Time to set sail!
Please take me for another fun walk!
To the real forests above the sea!
Okay, sure!
The next time we meet, I'll take you there!
It's a promise!
Once we make it to the surface...
we'll be in the world's strongest sea!
Let's go!
You guys!
To the New World!
Having left Fishman Island, the ship is finally ascending toward the New World.
Things are going great!
It's going so well, it's almost scary!
I'm hungry, so let's get started already.
Wait until I finish this, Luffy!
Ah, this feels great.
What do you think of my Shower Tempo?
Want to join in?
Who, me?
I'm fine.  I washed myself two days ago.
I'm more interested in that cloud that looks like cotton candy.  It looks delicious!
It isn't edible.
Really?  You mean it isn't sweet cotton candy?
What?  There's something sweet and tasty
in the shower room?
It's true.  It really does look sweet and delicious!
Please, Nami-san!
Turn this way!
Chopper, don't get too close to that cloud.
Scary!  I don't want to eat that cloud after all!
This is so relaxing...
How I've missed Sunny's bath for the past two years!
Taking a bath and looking at the deep sea,
which looks like the night sky...
This is the life!
Will they be alright on deck without you?
I'll get out of the bath
before we enter the rising currents, so it'll be fine.
If any sea monsters appear,
I'm sure they can handle them.
Hurry, Usopp!
Now, wait just a minute!
We're up against giant fish!
A weak rope wouldn't be able to hold 'em!
This should do the trick.
It's done!
Oh my, you seem to be having fun.
I didn't think of it on the way down
because I was too excited about Fishman Island...
but if we catch a deep sea fish and pull it up to the surface...
Sanji can cook it up for us, right?
I hope it'll go well with cola!
Cooking, huh?  Great idea!
I'm looking forward to having a drink
to celebrate our entry into the New World.
So, which one should we go for?
I want one that looks delicious.
Perhaps we should fry that one and eat it with salt?
Fried fish with salt, huh?  Sounds great!
That one might be nice grilled in sweet soy sauce.
Grilled fish, huh?
Oh!  That looks good, too!
If we put mayonnaise on it, it'll definitely taste nice!
Huh?  Which one?
No, there's no way.
That one will taste nasty no matter how you cook it.
Really?  Well, any one will do.
Sanji can cook anything and make it tasty!
You want to eat that one after all?!
Wait, isn't it a bit too big?!
Quick!  Get it!
Sure-Kill Capture Star
Alright!
We caught ourselves a deep sea fish!
I wanna eat it soon!
Still, is that even a fish?
Maybe it's just some old guy?
Old guy?
It got turned into bait!
Hey hey hey!  Again?!
They just keep coming!
Hurry and reel it in, Usopp!
Huh?!  No way!
The ship's gonna capsize!
The fish just keep coming!
They're like matryoshka dolls!
Did something happen?  The ship's swaying.
And they're really noisy out on the deck.
I guess leaving them alone was a bad idea, after all.
One Sword Style
360 Pound Cannon/Phoenix of 360 Earthly Desires
Great job, Zoro!
What's all the fuss about?
Hey, Sanji!  Look at this!
I see, great idea!
Cooking a deep sea fish, huh?  I'd love to try it.
More importantly... Why are you cooked?
And you should be even more excited!
Because there are two more fish inside it!
Anyway, are we still moving up toward the surface?
I have a bad feeling, like we're sinking.
You're probably just imagining it.
W-What's that?
What could it be?
A giant sea snake!
Right!  Move us closer!  We're gonna eat that too!
We can't pull that with the ship!
Wait!  Could that be...
The Whitestrom?!
A giant white maelstrom, which appears underwater out of nowhere, just like a living dragon!
What?!
An underwater maelstrom?!
What is that?!  Isn't this, like, really bad?!
Sheesh, those guys are just...
What?!  This is bad!  Is that the Whitestrom?!
From what I've heard,
any ship that gets caught in this vortex...
reappears days later in an unbelievably distant sea,
with no trace of the crew!
That must mean that everyone dies!
This is really bad after all!  Let's get out of here!
The ship is carried to an unbelievably distant sea?
So... this is like one of those super cool warp zones?!
No, you moron!
Everyone!  Get us away from that vortex, quickly!
Hey!  Here comes the navigator!
We're getting out of here, you idiots!
What's with that fish?!
Oh, we caught it!
What are you doing?!
We can't move with that thing attached to the ship!
See?  The fish is getting sucked into the vortex!
Crap!  Get it out!
Aye!
No!  Cut it loose!
What?!  But what about our cooked deep sea fish?!
Which is more important, the fish or our lives?!
I only left you alone for ten minutes!
How could you get us into this much trouble?!
Franky!  Use the Coup de Burst!
No, it's super-too late!
Right?
Don't you "Right?" me!
We're getting sucked into the vortex!
This is quite the predicament!
This is awesome!
Nooo!  We're done for!
I don't wanna die!
Grab on to the ship!
This is so fun!
This is super-bad!
Even the Sunny can't withstand the forces inside this vortex!
This is all Luffy and those guys' fault!
My eyes are spinning!
Can't we escape this vortex somehow?!
There's no record of anyone successfully escaping
from the Whitestrom, because...
They all died, right?!
There's no way we'll reach the New World!
We're all headed straight for the afterlife!
We stopped!
Seems the Sunny is still in one piece.
We must have crashed into something and been thrown out of the vortex.
Whatever the case, we're safe!
Where are we?
What's this black wall?
It doesn't look like the Red Line.
Oh no!
What... is that?!
We're gonna get eaten!
It's a monster!
Nooo!
What is that?!
It's leaving.
A fin?  Can it be...
That wailing... Is it...
Amazing!  It's a school of whales!
Oh, that scar!
I'll come see you again!
And when I do, let's have another fight!
Laboon?!
Laboon!
We will definitely sail around the world
and come back here!
Wait for us!
Laboon!  You've grown this big?!
Don't be ridiculous!
Laboon is in the first half of the Grand Line!
He's so big, he couldn't even make it through
the hole in the Red Line!
Amazing!
It's like a miracle.
I never thought we'd see a pod of Island Whales.
That one has wounds on its head that look just like Laboon's.
Yeah!  The scars are exactly the same!
What a shock!  It really isn't Laboon?
We're going to deliver Binks' brew...
Laboon!  Stop!
Listen to me!
It's me!  I was part of the Rumbar Pirates!
It's me, Brook!
Come to your senses!
I told you, that's a different whale!
Laboon!
This is no time to be calmly admiring them!
Even if we're out of the maelstrom, we're still in danger!
First of all, we have to do a headcount to make sure nobody got thrown overboard in the vortex!
Nami-san!
Yes!
Robin-chan!
I'm here.
Okay.  We've gotta get out of here in a hurry!
If we collide with these gigantic whales, the ship will take major damage!
Count us too!
Sanji-kun!  It is my shame to admit that the other six crewmates have not yet received honorable deaths!
Nami-san, what are your orders?!
We can stay where we are.
That's right, we're doing just fine, you idiots!
Resume whale watching immediately!
What the hell?!
This enormous pod of whales
is creating its own ocean current.
Trying to resist it will just put us in more danger.
Make sure the sails are open!
Turn the ship in the same direction that the whales are moving!
Aye!
Yes... This is Laboon's homeland.
Are any of his relatives here?!
That's dangerous, Brook!
If anyone here is looking for a small whale
who got separated from the pod fifty years ago...
then don't worry!  He's doing fine,
in a sea on the opposite side of the world!
According to Luffy-san, he has grown big and strong!
Please, don't be concerned!
I'm sure Laboon...
Ride the ocean current!
Right!
We'll be alright now.
We're traveling with the whales.
That's nice, too.
Huh?  Brook?
We're going to deliver Binks's brew,
entrusting ourselves to the whims of the ocean breeze and waves.
Beyond the tides, even the evening sun is cheerful.
The song of birds, drawing circles in the sky.
Farewell to the port, to the old hometown.
Let's sing a song with a DON, a song for our departure!
The waves of gold and silver turn to splashes of water,
as we set off for the edge of the sea!
We're going to deliver Binks's brew.
We are pirates, crossing the seas.
The sea is our pillow and the ship is our mattress.
The skull is emblazoned on our sail and flag.
A storm is coming from the distant sky.
The waves are dancing, beat on the drums!
Hey!  You're letting us ride you!
We can let them carry us like this.
If you're caught by a treacherous wind, this could be the end,
We all seem to be riding the same rising current.
but the sun will always rise in the morning!
Beyond the surface lies
the final ocean of the Grand Line... the New World!
I can hardly wait!
Luffy?
I see it!
Finally!
Let's go, men!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
We're here!
In the New World!
We did it!
We finally made it here!
Uh, this is no time to celebrate!
The whales are...
When we see Laboon again,
we'll definitely tell him about you!
Stay well, Laboon's relatives!
Thanks for taking care of us!
Even so... I'd heard the rumors,
but this place is worse than I imagined!
This New World!
The weather's the worst!
Thunderclouds in the sky!
The wind blows fiercely!
The sea is raging!
The compass needles are out of control!
I can see the silhouettes of ships!
The pirates are causing a ruckus!
No, those are warships!
Suits me just fine!
The Navy?
Next time, on One Piece:
"Z's Ambition" Arc
Lili, the Tiny Giant!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!