The Released Swan!
Reunion! Bon Kurei
It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered,
and Luffy has broken into the world's largest prison, Impel Down
in order to free his brother Ace, who has been captured by the Navy.
Inside the prison, Luffy ran into Buggy,
as well as the former Baroque-Works agent Mister Three,
and the three of them made it to Level Three.
This is Level Three, the Famine Hell.
We have to escape while we're still able to sweat off the heat.
Then let's hurry down to Level Four!
YOU'RE GOING THERE?!
Soup Spaghetti!
The Sphinx woke up!
Firm Yakisoba!
Gomu Gomu no Gatling!
Meanwhile Hancock, who had helped Luffy sneak into the prison,
was about to reach the floor where Ace was being held.
Un! Deux! Trois!
Un! Deux! Kuraa!
What's with this singing?
Un! Deux! Trois!
Un! Deux! Kuraa!
Un! Deux! Ondoryaa!
TL Note: Okama = Cross dresser
Okama Way!
Oh, oh! Okama Way!
Yeah, yeah! Okama Way!
Spin, spin! Okama Way!
What's with this cheerful singing voice in the Famine Hell. Here, where standing up is a trial in itself?
Oh, oh! Okama Way!
If that's a prisoner, then we definitely shouldn't take him lightly.
Yeah, yeah! Okama Way!
Spin, spin! Okama Way!
This voice must be...
Oh, oh! Okama Way!
Hey, partner! This guy might be useful to us!
Spin, spin! Okama Way!
H-Hey! W-Wait a minute!
Oh, oh! Okama Way!
Yeah, yeah! Okama Way!
Spin, spin! Okama Way!
You're doing great!
I'm spinning around and around and around, like I'm caught up in the tides of time!
Over there!
No! I'm telling you, we shouldn't...
Guys! You can't be that tired now!
This heat is nothing!
I won't let myself be defeated by the heat!
Oh my, if it isn't Mister Three!
So, it's you after all?
WHAT?! MISTER THREE?!
Hey, you! What're you doing here?
If you're outside the cage, does that mean that you've been caught?!
Oh, no...I'm the one who's been caught...
I was so surprised that I had to do a double take with an "Okama Kenpo" called,
"Looking Back Twice On An Autumn Night's Dream!"
Hey...What's with this weird creature?
Leave it be. There's no profit in freeing him...
What're you saying?!
Just hurry up and get me out of here!
It's so hot here...
Still, if I keep going down these stairs...I'm sure I'll reach Ace!
He went downstairs?
Is that true?
You're not kidding around, are you?!
It's true.
Priceless, isn't it?
I see. Well, thanks for freeing me, Mister Three.
I owe you one!
Well, then...
WAIT FOR ME, MY DEAR FRIEND!
OKAMA WAY IS THE PATH TO HELL!
This is best for all of us.
Yeah, for sure...
With everyone on alert, how the hell did he slip though our defenses?
There was only one intruder, but even so,
if he does manage to free Ace,
it'll bring disgrace to Impel Down,
and the World Government will be the laughing stock of the whole world!
We will march into Impel Down...
and capture Straw Hat Luffy to restore the honor of Navy HQ!
Yessir!
Wait a second my dears...
W-Who are you?
I am Sadi-chan, and I love torture.
Not only do we have an intruder,
but for us to ask for help from the Navy...
This is...quite a sad day for Impel Down!
Using the -chan-suffix to refer to herself...Is she serious?
Silence!
Address me as "Sadi-chan"!
Oh, I just LOVE the sound of your screams!
You bitch!
Wait.
Are you saying we're not needed?
Indeed. This prison is a labyrinth in Hell.
Unless you know your way around this place, you'll be of no help at all.
You people just have to stay out here and strengthen our outer defenses.
Now we will raise the drawbridge, the only exit from here, and...
seal off Impel Down completely.
Do not worry.
There is no escape from...
...this underwater prison.
Very well. We will protect the outside.
Yes, that's like a good boy.
A koala?
What...You're kidding...?
A koala...
A koala?
A koala.
Impel Down has been completely sealed off.
A koala?
Hannyabal?
Magellan is here too...What's going on?
You've got a special visitor, Ace.
Who do you think has come?
Jinbei...
I'm pretty sure you've never met her,
so there's no way for you to know who she is,
but while few have seen her, her name is well-known!
The empress of the warrior clan, Kuja...
and one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
She is the strong, proud, and most beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Yay, yay, Hancock!
Hancock-sama!
Hey, beautiful! When I become Warden, will you marry me?!
Please!
That hurts! Now I really wanna become Warden!
Ah! I got it wrong! That really hurt!
What are you doing?!
Seriously?!
I did think she was one fine woman!
So, that's the Snake Princess of the Kuja-tribe?
Look over here!
Hancock-chan!
Look at that! What a hottie!
Hey Cutie! Come on over to my cage!
I'll treat you real nice!
She smells so nice!
I'd love to live on the Island of Women!
Nothing but women...I'm sure they're all naked, too!
What do you want with me?
Nothing. I merely wanted to see you with my own eyes.
The man who served as the trigger for the war I am about to partake in.
So I'm just some item on display, huh?
Boa Hancock! Are you ignoring us?!
Come over here!
The Empress who refused to listen, no matter what was said to her until now...
You really want to keep your position as a Warlord that badly?!
So, you are Jinbei...
Do not be so spiteful.
Lady! Hey, lady!
We're having a conversation here! Be quiet!
Shaddup, Magellan, go take a shit!
You can say that again!
Hey, Snake Princess! You sure the Island of Women isn't starving for some men?!
Hey! Give me the position of Warden!
Assistant Warden...
Hey! Hurry up and get your ass over here!
You just...
She's looking at us!
...keep taunting me with such coarse voices...
I'm just so scared!
That's just too much!
How much more perfect can she get?!
Hand over the lady, swamp ass!
This must be the most unrefined place on Earth.
These people disgust me.
Are you really gonna let the prisoners get away with calling you "swamp ass", Warden?
I guess you've gotten so rusty, you're not even fit to be the Warden any more?
She's too much!
Give me your job, swamp ass!
Still...
Hand her over! Hand over the lady, swamp ass!
Swamp ass! Give us Hancock!
It's true, I will not stand for this insolence!
W-Warden, wait a minute!
You're putting the rest of us in danger too!
Don't get carried away, scum!
Oh, crap!
It would seem I have to teach you...
just who the boss in this prison is!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Oh, crap!
He's brought out the Hydra!
What is he doing?!
Stop it, Magellan!
Hey, moron!
You're kidding, right?! Stop it!
Damn him...! He really did it!
It's...It's no use! You're gonna die!
A-Antidote! Give me the antidote! Damn it!
Don't forget that I posses the right and power...
to kill each and every one of you right now!
Well then, Hancock-dono.
Take your time, and say what you wanted to say.
I am done here.
Hey! What you just said...Was it true?!
I have no reason to lie to you.
That's right...
He was afraid that you would be upset.
That was all?
Did she tell him anything?
Who knows...I was too busy running away from you.
Ace-san...
What did that woman say to you?
She said that my brother...
is coming here.
The Straw Hat kid you keep telling me about?!
How reckless of him!
Huh? When'd I start going up?
I was trying to get further down...
Still, if I just keep running, I'm sure I'll make it eventually!
I'm hungry!
We've found him. He's entering sector C.
Yeah, I see him.
More Sea Stone-nets, huh?
That was close!
Oh, crap! The lion?!
D-Damn it!
Stop right there, lion!
I'm here to help you!
Zoro?!
Just kidding!
TL Note: Swan Arabesque
Swan! Swan!
Huh?
Spin, spin...I'm spinning!
That's not Zoro...
But I've heard that voice before...
Long time no see, Straw-chan! It's me!
What do you think of my hidden talent?
Awesome!
Quit joking around!
Now running away wouldn't be very Bon Kurei-like, would it?
If we risk our life to meet up with a friend,
and then abandon him for another...
would we be able to enjoy our breakfast tomorrow after doing that?!
Madame Hina! The sheep ship is sailing east!
We tricked you!
We're all masters of disguise, and...
we're also Straw-chan's friends!
Now, come at us!
We'll never, ever forget you guys!
Bon-chan!
I'm really disappointed that you're not Zoro, but at least you're still alive!
Now! Capture Straw Hat!
MOVE IT!
Get your asses out of my friend's way, you morons!
That's it, Sphinx! Take them down!
Right! Now that we've beaten 'em this badly, he shouldn't come again.
It's best to restrain beasts with brute force, after all!
Yakisoba...bread...
Hey, Bon-chan!
I was sure you died back then in our place!
Quit joking around!
A true Okama never dies!
Wait, is that true?
Explanation of Mister Two, Bon Kurei's powers;
TL Note: Mane = Imitation
He is a copy-man, who ate the Mane Mane fruit.
He can transform into a perfect copy of anyone he has touched with his right hand.
He was able to imitate Zoro because he has touched him once.
Another one trying to escape...
They just keep getting more and more allies the closer to the bottom of the sea they get, don't they?!
Blugori squad! Don't you dare let these guys get away!
While we're at it, Straw-chan.
Is it true that you want to go to Level Five?
That's right. Mind telling me how to get there?
Well, shall I accompany you, then?
After all, I also have someone I'd like to meet up with in Level Five!
Seriously?
Yes, so let us go together!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Next time, on One Piece:
Warden Magellan Moves
The Net to Trap Straw Hat is Completed!