Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
The crew received a distress call and landed on Punk Hazard,
a bizarre island that is split
between a burning side and a frozen one.
Luffy's group is headed for the frozen side of the island to rescue Nami's group,
who were kidnapped by an unknown organization.
But the crew is still unaware
that there are others whom they know well.
What business do you have at my vacation home...
White Hunter?
The Warlord!
Trafalgar Law
Trafalgar!
Even if you are a Warlord,
you must do as we say in this matter.
Please step aside!
We know for a fact
that there are other people on this island besides you!
Inside Dr. Vegapunk's old laboratory
-Nami's Group-
Daddy!  Mommy!
Hey, you said you weren't sick anymore, right?
Yeah.
What disease did you have?
None of you show any symptoms.
I don't know.  They just said "You have a disease",
and "You'll be fine after a year".
A disease that passes after a year?
Yeah.
Mommy and Daddy asked some people to cure me
and then those people took me here.
So, your parents told you to come here?
No.
It was those people,
they told me all of this outside of my house...
and then I was taken here.
They said that I could've infected Mommy and Daddy.
I didn't even get to say goodbye.
Was it like that for the rest of you?
Yeah.
Me too.
Yeah, right!  This definitely sounds like kidnapping!
So you were brought here by strangers,
and didn't even talk to your parents first?
You know what this sounds like?
You were suffering from a really terrible illness!
Are you a complete moron?!
Is all this running too much for any of you?
I'll carry anyone who's worn out.
You all... seem fine.
Yeah, we're fine!
Because Master has been treating us!
Master?
Yeah, Master!
Master!
Master!  Master!
But you've already been here more than a year, right?
Chopper, have a look at them after this.
Then we'll know for sure.
Sure.  Will do.
Huh?  The door's locked!
There's no way out!
They'll be here soon!
What'll we do?
We have to hurry!
Nami!
Out of the way!
One more time!
It's open.
You've gotten really powerful.
Amazing!
You're so cool, Raccoon Dog-chan!
Wait, I'm not a raccoon dog!
But you just acted like one.
You're right!
Everyone, let's hurry!
It's freezing!
Chopper, lend me your fur coat!
Alright...
Wait, I can't take it off!
What is this place?  Are we outside?
Or maybe a freezer?
It's so dark, I can't really tell...
This climate's perfect for me!
You're lucky that you grew up on a winter island.
Is this a road?
It's so dark, I can't...
Oh, now I see it!
There's a door at the other end!
You're right!
Let's keep going!  This isn't a dead end!
Alright!
Lady!  I don't wanna go in there!  It's scary!
What?!
What's wrong, everyone?
Hurry up!  They're still after us!
They took me through here
when I first came to this island!
Really?  Then it must lead to the exit!
It's pretty cold, but try to bear it everyone!
Hurry!
That's not the problem!
I mean...
around us...
Around us?
There's something...
inside the walls.
I'm scared of this place
because there are frozen people here!
Huh?!  What is all this?!
Frozen... corpses?!
They're above us too!
And under us!
Noooooo!
Ah!  Please, wait!  Don't leave us!
Well, that takes care of that.
Inside the laboratory ・ Biscuits Room
-Sanji's Group-
Hey!
You've blocked their way.  That's more than enough.
Let's keep moving!
I just felt a surge of emotion from Nami-san's heart!
She may have realized her feelings for me!
Still, what are these guys?!
They have sheep legs!
Isn't there some kind of mythical creature like that?
There's no point worrying about them now.
They'll have to wait
until we know what's going on here!
Anyway, Nami-san is our top priority!
Wait!
Leave me!  I will remain here!
I saw no sign of my son
among the children you helped escape!
There must be other rooms!
I should remain and search-
And how are you planning to move around?!
Leaving you behind
would be the same as abandoning you to die!
It would leave me with a terrible aftertaste!
But I came here to save my son!
You're such an annoying bastard!
Just ask us!  Say "Please search for my body"!
Where is your body anyway?!
I refuse to be indebted to a pirate!
I would sooner die than ask for your help!
H-However...
if you were to search for my body...
I would not complain.
Damn this guy!
Why is a detached head
acting like he's better than me?!
You intend to use violence?!
I-I have no regrets!
I will not beg villains for my life!
Hey, give it a rest!
Would crushing a defenseless head really make you feel better?
The moment that you took him out of the cell,
you'd already lost, Sanji.
But...
This guy is really getting on my nerves!
I was a fool to admire his resolve,
even if it was just for a second!
I don't wanna help him any more!
Alas, I would be defenseless if you left me here,
but if you want to take me with you...
I would not complain.
Damn... I'm gonna get you for this once you get your body back!
You show no mercy, even to a detached head.
Yes.  I should be careful what I say.
I wonder if Nami and the others have found an exit?
Let's go after them!
Damn it, that itches!
Punk Hazard Island, Central Lake
-Luffy's Group-
We've taken out the intruders!
No, they cut it down.
Look closely.
They lack skill.
Well done, Zoro-kun!  I commend you!
Hey!  I've got Legson here too!
He cut the cannonball in two?!
Damn that samurai!
Don't let up!  Fire!
They won't listen to us!
They do seem very thickheaded.
What's up with them?  We're on the same side!
Legson Balloon
What are you doing now -pooh?!
Legson isn't helping at all!
What?!  He bounced them away!
How can his body do that?!
Oh, a Devil Fruit user, is he?
That makes things easier!
Prepare to fire!
They're going to shoot again.
They never learn!  I'm counting on you guys!
Wait.
They're aiming for the water.
They're planning to make our boat capsize.
What?!  We've got two Devil Fruit users here!
Aim carefully!  We will knock them all into the sea!
Die, Devil Fruit users!
Dammit!
Fire!
Here it comes!
For now, let's hide behind a block of ice!
Good idea!
Looks like we got away somehow.
You have to help row too!
Devil Fruit users can't fight in the water!
Sink, Devil Fruit users!
A snowy mountain near the laboratory
-Brook-
Creepy!  This is much too creepy!
What is wrong with that ghost?!  Attacking me out of nowhere...
I have done absolutely nothing to deserve it!
And he was pretty strong too... Hmm?
Do my ears detect a faint sound... even though I have no ears!
You are indeed stubborn!
I have no choice!  I will take you on!
I'll just pretend that my eyes did not see that...
Even though I have no eyes!
Main entrance to the laboratory
Hello?  My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm the man who's gonna be the Pirate King!
You answered too soon, and you're saying too much!
Please, help me!
What's wrong?!
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
No, I'm not your boss.
My companions keep getting cut down.
The samurai's gonna kill us all!
Where are you?!
Somebody please save me, I don't care who.
I'm on...
Punk Hazard!
The name of the island,
plus the mention of the cold climate.
There's no doubt about it,
this call was sent from this island.
You know Straw Hat Luffy, don't you?
Gomu Gomu no...
Fuusen!
Repel!
Room...
Shambles!
He got me!
Two years ago, during the incident
with the Celestial Dragons from the Roswald House,
you, Kid, and Luffy worked together.
What's more, during the great war...
Bring Straw-Hatter over here!
I'm gonna take him away from this place!
Let me take care of him for now!
When Straw Hat was being pursued by Akainu...
you helped him escape.
What business do you have with me?
False distress calls is your specialty, isn't it?
Unfortunately,
this transmission wasn't one of our traps.
Quite a mystery.  But I don't know anything,
so this conversation is over.
Cut the crap.  Let us into the laboratory!
It's my vacation home now.  I refuse!
Is it so wrong for a pirate like me
to stay on an island that you've abandoned?
I'm the only one here.
If Straw Hat does show up, you can have his head.
If that's all you want, then you should leave!
Those frozen people were so scary!
I've had enough of this place!
Look!  There's a door!
We can get out of here!
Yay!
There's someone in there after all!
I'm out!
We're out!  It's freezing!
We're out of the building!  We can go home!
I can see Papa and Mama again!
It's so cold!
Clear a path, children!
The Franky...
Tank is here!
Out of the way!  Out of the way!  Super-out of the way!
I will crush anyone who's in my way!
But I will avoid crushing flowers!
The just a little kindhearted, Franky Tank!
Alright, let's go everyone!
Yay!
One!
Two!
Three!
Super!
The Straw Hats... and children?!
I can't tell what's the weirdest!
A giant raccoon dog, a winter bikini,
giant kids, a robot, or a detached head...
Am I dreaming?
A caterpillar!
How cool!
That tank is awesome!
It's the ultimate!
I travel the most treacherous road without difficulty!
Nami-swan!  You're alright!
You're still lovely when you're freezing...
but I don't want you to catch a cold,
so take my jacket!
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
I've seen you before!
Yeah!  It's the guy from Sabaody!
Were you the one who imprisoned these kids?!
You scum!  We're not giving them back to you!
And you!
Of all the atrocious fiends to run into... it's Smoker!
And with him is always a cutie-swaaan!
This isn't good!  We've run into the Navy!
We can't go this way!  We'll have to find another exit!
Hurry back inside!
Quickly kids!  Through to the other side!
There's gotta be a back door!
What's the Navy doing here?!
How should I know?!  Anyway, run!
Huh?  Isn't the Navy supposed to be good?
I suppose.  You can go to them!
No way!  They look like gangsters!
They're here, aren't they?!  Alone, my ass!
They were indeed here... to my surprise.
Soldiers!  We will capture the Straw Hats!
Right, let's go!  Follow the Captain-chan!
Wait!
Is everyone alright?!
They've made things much more complicated.
What's that sound?
No way!
The warship is floating!
Even the river is floating with it!
What is going on?!
I can't let you leave this island anymore.
Sorry that I said there wasn't anyone here.
This guy's bad news!
Stand back.
You can't lay a finger on him... He'd just pull it off!
Go, Smokey!
Get him!
Show him the power of G-5!
The Navy's G-5 unit is overwhelmed by Law's power,
which can even make warships fly.
Sanji, Nami, and the others find themselves
in an unprecedented disaster, thanks to Law,
and a crisis looms before Luffy and his group
as they try to cross the lake to the frozen lands!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Huge Jam
Luffy Sinks in the Icy Lake
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A Huge Jam
Luffy Sinks in the Icy Lake