It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has lost his brother Ace in the great war against the Navy...
Then he was taken to the Island of Women,
where he was overwhelmed by unbearable sadness.
But now, we go back in time ten years, to East Blue.
This story takes place when the brothers Luffy and Ace were still children.
Luffy was left on Mt. Corvo, in the care of the bandit Dadan,
where he met the two troublemakers, Ace and Sabo.
How are you doing, Poochie?
Who did this?!  Who'd dig a hole right in front of the door?!
It was Ace and the other kids.  They said it was a trap for boars.
This is my house!  Don't just let them do whatever they want!
Those brats!
Sabo!  Who said you could cause trouble on our turf?!
Your turf?  Hah!  You guys are full of it!
Don't just stand there yapping, show me what you got!
Fine by me!
Ace!
Don't look away!
Damn it!
You little runt!
His face got squashed!
It's the cops.  Let's get out of here!
Luffy!  Get moving!
Over here, Luffy!
I'm back to normal!
Let's have deer for dinner!
They're so tasty!  Let's hunt right now!
Wait up!
We're back!
Don't come back, you brats!
Here's dinner.
Roast it, fast.
Food, food!
Don't waste food!
I'm being eaten!
Don't come out until you've counted to ten thousand!
Cut it out!
You bastard!
Sheesh!  Why do we have to clean this whole place every night after we eat?
I swear I'm gonna chase those three out!
It's so beautiful!
Luffy!  Wait up, you...
B-Boss?
Good grief...
My bed is the only place where I can relax...
One last round of training before we go to bed!
I'm gonna win!
You never learn, do you?
Let's go!
Fairy-san.
Dammit!
Luffy, you alive?
This floor's pretty worn out...
You've done it now, you jerks!
Hey!
Let's go to bed.
Yeah.
We've gotta drive those kids out of here.
At this rate, those three will take over the Dadan Family...
Actually, I don't even think I'll last that long!
Now, now, boss...
They pretty much took over already...
Shut it!  I just can't look after them anymore!
Let's drive'em out!
Who cares about our promise with Garp?!
Hey!
Garp?!
Please forgive me!  I wasn't thinking clearly!
Excuse me, but we heard that Luffy is staying here...
Makino!
Luffy!
You look like you're doing well!
It's been six months, we got worried and decided to see how you're doing.
Oh, mayor!
Don't tell Garp-san about this.
Still, it's hard to believe that you're living with mountain bandits...
You got a problem with that?
Damn right I do!  Don't talk to me
like that, you damn bandit!
What?!  Are all the citizens of Windmill Village like this?!
I've got a present for you!
I expect Garp-san didn't think about stuff like this...
Ta-daah!  Some new clothes!
Awesome!
I'm glad you like it.
I can adjust the size too, so...
You two, come over here.
Alright?
Hey!
You too.
I heard that you were a naughty kid, Ace-kun...
But you're surprisingly well-behaved.
I-If you say so...
He's embarrassed.
Ace, your face is all red!
You guys!
Now, now, don't move.
I'll get you for this later.
I hope you like it.
Delicious!
It's going to be hard to get
good food like this on our voyage.
When I go to sea, the first thing I'm going to do is add the greatest cook in the world to my crew!
I'm gonna become a pirate first, so that'll be impossible!
That's not fair!  I'm going to become a pirate before either of you!
You two are still going on about that?
I'm telling you, you're gonna become marines!  Why is that so hard to understand?!
Dadan!
Yes, Garp-san?
Why'd you hit me too?
Because I'm not happy with the way you're raising these kids!
That's Garp?  This old guy is Ace and Luffy's grandfather?
Kid.  You were talking about going out to sea too, right?
It's not "Kid"!  His name is Sabo!
We all shared a toast of brotherhood and promised to become pirates!
You shouldn't have said that...
Oh?  So, in other words, now there are three
little idiots who want me to give them a workout?
You're not getting away!
Good grief...
I'm happy for you, Luffy.  You've got two older brothers now.
I said wait!
This old guy is a monster!
That's all for today.  Tomorrow, I'm going to give you an even harder workout!
So don't die now!
At this rate, Gramps is gonna kill us tomorrow.
And even if we survive long enough to go to sea,
we'll be beaten until we give up on being pirates.
I don't wanna die!
There's only one solution.
It's time to make a choice, brothers!
"We're moving out..."
What?!
What are we gonna do about this?
What a nuisance.
How can you be so relaxed?!  Their reputation has reached all the way into the center of the kingdom!
If they aren't protected by us mountain bandits, someone could try to kill them at any time!
My holiday is over.  Be sure to train them to become great marines by the time I come back!
You're pushing the responsibility on me again?!
Huh?!
Good bye!
Why does he expect mountain bandits to raise marines?!
That old man is insane!
Now, now, boss...
You're really worried about those kids despite all your complaining, huh?
Like hell I am!
Now that I think about it, this makes things easier.
They left on their own.
What a relief!
We've successfully escaped!
Dadan and her gang didn't chase us.
This is what they mean by "A devil's child has a devil's luck".
He is the child of a devil, too.
They're probably glad to be rid of us.
It sure is pouring down...
Let's take shelter here for a while.
This is kind of exciting!
I really don't want to be killed by Garp!
Just go search for those dumb kids already!
Understood!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Hey!
Ace!  Sabo!
Luffy!
Take a look at this!
What's this?
It's the blueprints for a base!
We can't sleep outside forever, you know!
So we're gonna make a secret base right here!
A secret base?
That's so cool!
Where're we gonna get the materials?
We've got more than enough...
down there.
Awesome!  It looks just like it did in the blueprint!
It's quite well made, I must say.
What is it, Ace?
If it's supposed to be a secret base...
then we've gotta set some traps.
I get it.  Good idea.
Yay!  The Gray Terminal, Windmill Village and East Blue!  I can see it all!
That isn't such a big deal, is it?
You should see it for yourselves.
This really is something else...
Luffy!  We've got a tailwind!  Raise the sails!
Roger that!
Sail forth, and let's find some treasure!
Enemy spotted to starboard!
It's Bluejam's ship!  Prepare for combat!
They're shooting at us, right off the bat!
Take evasive action!
Luffy!  Turn hard to port!
Sure, you got it!
No, that's not quite right.  In times like these, you're supposed to say "Steady!"
Oh, right.
Luffy!  Turn hard to port!
Hard turn to port!  Steady!
Time to engage them!  Board their ship!
It's payback-time, Sabo!
Leave it to me!
Don't you cry now, Luffy!
Right!
We took them down!
Alright!
Serves you right!
This is great!
Yeah, it's the best!
Our very own secret base!
Found them!
You still can't find the kids?!
We're sorry...
People said they saw them at the Gray Terminal and in the jungle, but nothing specific.
They've been gone for two weeks now!
You don't suppose they've been eaten by big tigers in the jungle, do you?!
Boss!
We found them!
Really?!
They're in the jungle, they built a fortress in a large tree!
We can take you there now.
I see...
That's a relief, right boss?
You were really worried about them...
W-What, they're still alive?
Those kids are irritatingly tough!
W-What?
Don't just stand around, go get something for dinner!
Yes!
Ace... Sabo... Wait...
At least their sleeping faces are no different from normal kids'...
Hey, you'll catch a cold like that...
The trap just got sprung!
Is someone trying to invade us already?
Huh?  Perhaps it was a malfunction?
Well, we did put it up in a hurry.  I suppose it's not too surprising.
Ace...
Sheesh!  I'm never gonna...
worry about them again!
Luffy and his friends are attacked by a large bear, and a lone old man saves them.
The old man claims that he once fought Gold Roger.
Hearing that, Luffy is overjoyed.
They get to hear stories of the Pirate King,
the likes of which they've never heard before!
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy Becomes an Apprentice?!
The Man who Fought the Pirate King!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!