Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
After bidding farewell to Fishman Island,
the Straw Hats have finally reached the New World.
Now they find themselves
in a devilish region called the waters of Mobedumule.
What is with this weather?!
These are the waters of Mobedumule!
Momemomejuban?
Mobedumule!
Or as they're also called, the Temperamental Waters.
Weather phenomenons
unlike anything anyone has ever seen or heard...
come one after another, as if by the ocean's whim!
In these waters,
they met a giant girl who's eaten the Mini Mini Fruit.
The crew decided to help free her father, Panz Fry,
from a Navy ship convoy.
But I'm gonna save Daddy, no matter what!
Before they can take him to Impel Down, I must...
take Daddy back, right here!
Lily.
Let me help you!
I want to try that Heaven food that only your dad can make!
But a mysterious group calling themselves the Neo-Navy are after her father's life.
Daddy!
This is just a little greeting.
Let's ascend, and take them out in one fell swoop!
Yes, Sir!
The Straw Hat Pirates, the Navy, and the Neo-Navy...
A heated battle between the three groups begins!
More cannon fire?
You're in my way!
A human?!
Move it!
Damn it!
I will not let you do as you please.
These ships are under the Navy's command!
I won't let anyone take Pops's heavenly food!
Board their ships!
Not gonna happen!
Kill the pirates!
You're worth 400 million?
And are you a pirate as well?
Yeah.
Then I'll send you both to hell together!
Leave this to me!
What a bizarre technique.
Are you a Devil Fruit user?
I'm a rubber man!
You won't be able to break my Tekkai with attacks of that caliber!
Is that so?
I told you,
I won't let you do as you please on this ship!
Roronoa Zoro?!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
How about continuing our fight?!
Go!  Kill the pirates!
Take aim!
I can't cover such a large target!
Daddy!
Robin-chan?!
Just... who... are they?
This is not good!  It's total chaos over there!
Hey, Nami!
I know!
I'm trying to figure out
the best course of action to save Lily's dad!
No way!
Is that... the Thrust-Up Stream?!
Bastard!
I can't believe that both Luffy-san and Zoro-san are unable to go on the offense!
Clearly, those two must not be taken lightly!
Take this, monster!
Hey, you!
I may be a soul without a physical form,
but getting shot still isn't exactly pleasant!
There's no doubt about it.
Jeez, why'd it come now!
Sorry for the delay!
Nami!
Franky, this is an emergency!
There's about to be a huge weather shift!
We're in danger too!
What?!
Everyone, listen up!
The Thrust-Up Stream is about to hit!
Thrust-Up...
Stream?
What's that?  Is it...
something like the Knock-Up Stream we took to Sky Island?
That's right, but it's not as big as that one was.
What a relief.
But still, it's more than enough
to blow a warship to smithereens!
Whaaaaat?!
The biggest problem is that several will appear over a wide area!
So get back to the Sunny as soon as possible!
G-Got it!
Color of Arms - Hardening
You still don't get it?!
What?!  Was that Haki?!
One-Sword Style
Franky, the anchors!
Roger that!
You little brat!
You're pretty good!
So are you.
Sanji-kun, Lily!
Nami-san!
Were you so worried about me that you...
It's about to get dangerous here!  An upward current like the Knock-Up Stream is coming!
What?!
Are the anchors firmly attached to the raft?
Yeah!
Then we're getting out of here with the Sunny,
right now!
Alright!
What's going on?!
Luffy!  Idiot swordsman!
We're getting out of here with Lily's dad,
using the Coup de Burst!
A-Alright!
I won't...
...Let you!
Usopp!
Luffy and the others are...
Don't get in our way!
T-T-That was so scary!
Hey!  Super-welcome back!
Usopp!
Franky, hurry and use the Coup de Burst!
I'm afraid that won't work!
What?!  Why?!
Now that we're closer to it,
I can see that the raft is way too big.
Huh?! What to do now?!
What should we do?
I know! That could work!
What?!
Use the force from the Thrust-Up Stream to fly?!
That's the only option we have left!
But, do you really think it'll lift us up so conven-
Shut up!
Sanji-kun, are the anchors still in place?
Yeah!
Then hold on tight!
We're flying away, raft and all!
Damn it! If it had just popped up a little away from where it did...
No, here comes another one!
Nami, now?
Hold it...
Hold...
Now, Franky!
Luffy!
A flying ship?!
You're not getting away!
The rescue mission was a complete success!
Alright!
Now I'll get to eat the Heaven food!
Umm, don't forget me!
They got away again?!
Once we set our sights on someone, they never escape!
The same goes for you, now that you know our secret!
Die!
That was a pointless waste of time.
Let's hunt them down!
What an insane fight.
They've been going at it for five hours now!
Are they evenly matched?
No, Shuzo-san has the upper hand.
She must have used up all her energy by now.
It has to be painful for you...
Time to end this!
I missed?  You won't get away next time.
What?!
Damn Devil Fruit user!
Enough!  The winner is Ain!
Ever since that fight,
Ain has served at Z-sensei's side...
while I just command this raiding party.
But now, he should understand
who is truly worthy to be his second in command!
It looks like we made it out of Mobedumule.
There's no trace of that weather we were experiencing!
We should be safe here.
We traveled pretty far, after all.
I can't see any ships chasing us either!
Of course!  That was a full-power Coup de Burst!
Even the speediest vessel couldn't keep up with us!
And these reefs are the perfect spot to hide.
It seems that we can finally catch our breath.
Yeah.
How are things over there?
It was a pretty serious wound,
but he should be alright
after two to three days of rest.
Thank you, Chopper-sa!
I'm so grateful!
Grateful... Even if you say that,
I won't be happy at all, you jerk!
Well, whatever the case, I'm glad you're safe!
So, make some of that Heaven food!  Right now!
What are you, a devil?!
What?  Chopper said he was alr-
Weren't you listening to me, Luffy?!
I said he had to take it easy!
Huh?  Then what about the Heaven food?
Sheesh!  Even if Lily-chan's dad was alright...
what about the damn ingredients?!
The ingredients for this Heaven food?!
We've got 'em!
Where?  Lily, where are they?!
Look, over yonder!
It's true!  When did she...
Tons of food rained down
when that warship got blown apart earlier.
I thought it'd be a waste to let it sink...
so I quickly gathered it all up!
Well done!
You were thinking about food in that chaos?  Just how gluttonous are you?!
That's right!  What was I doing,
when Daddy and Luffy-sa were in danger?!
But I've got some booze too!
Well done!
Hey!
But even if we have the ingredients, Old Frypan can't cook them now, right?
Of course he can't!
Instead, I'll do-
What are you doing?!  I said you can't yet move around!
Ow-ow-ow.
I should be fine if I take it slow.
Daddy! Ya gotta listen to what Chopper-sa says!
Your name... was Luffy, right?
Yeah!  I'm the man who's gonna be the Pirate King!
Daddy!
Hey, Lily...
Daddy?
Luffy was saying
that he wants to eat my cooking so badly!
As a cook, I'm fated to cook for him.
Well, that might be, but...
Besides, he saved the both of us!
If I can't repay his favor, it'd be a shame to chefs...
No, a shame to all giants everywhere!
Daddy!
Now, bring the ingredients over here!
I'll cook up some of that Heaven food!
Seriously?!  Thanks, Old Frypan!
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Thank you, Luffy.
Lily-chan, I'll make something too!
Alright, I'll help!
I'll bring the ingredients!
As will I!
Gimme the booze!
Now, you help out too!
Alright!
Shuzo-san, the target has been spotted!
They're hiding in the reef!
How impudent.  All ships, prepare for battle!
We'll blow up that entire reef!
I-I'm sorry to say, but...
we used up all our torpedoes in the earlier fight,
and we're running low on cannonballs too.
I see.  In that case...
No, we do have torpedoes!
That's impossible.
This submarine is a torpedo!
We are proud soldiers of the Neo-Navy's raiding squad!
We've made it this far
by believing in Z-sensei and Shuzo-san!
Shuzo-san, let me fight for you!
Please!
Me too!
And me!
I'm proud of you.  I'll care for you until you die!
Fight to your hearts' content, as soldiers of the Neo-Navy!
Yeah!
All torpedoes, fire!
This time, you will not escape...
Stinking pirates!
Next time, on One Piece:
"Z's Ambition" Arc
Luffy VS Shuzo!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!