All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
The Straw Hat Pirates landed on Punk Hazard,
an island split between fire and ice.
After finding out about inhumane experiments being run by the island's ruler, Master, or Caesar Clown,
they went to find out what his true intentions are.
During their journey, the crew entered into an alliance with the Heart Pirates' captain, Trafalgar Law.
And Luffy finally found Caesar!
You really underestimated me.
Who's... there?!
Why... are you...
here?!
How many years has it been?
You've grown, Law.
The Samurai Who Cuts Through Fire!
Foxfire Kinemon
Did you honestly think
he didn't know what you were up to?
We do not trust Caesar.
That is why he went to great lengths to infiltrate Caesar's operations...
using Monet.
I hear you're one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea now.
How mighty you've become.
When'd you get here...
Vergo?!
I just arrived.
I happened to be in Dressrosa...
and an S.A.D. tanker was heading here, so I got on it.
Looks like I made the right choice.
What do you mean by that?!
Have I ever harmed you?!
If any harm had been done to us, you would already be dead.
But if you try to keep secrets from adults, you will inevitably be caught, Law.
Then... I'll just have to...
get rid of you!
Oh, and there's one other thing.
You misspoke.
It's "Vergo-san".
In Front of the Laboratory - Luffy's Group
What just happened?
I have no idea.
What should we do?!
Tashigi-chan!
That's Vice-Admiral Smoker!
I never thought I'd see the day
when he was beaten unconscious twice!
The three Straw Hats were all beaten too!
Could it have been the Haki of Conquerors?
No way!  There couldn't possibly be
that big a gap in their power!
Then what was it?!
He took them all out without lifting a finger!
Serves you right, Navy!
That's the true power of our god of salvation, Master!
Master!  Master!  Master!
My mighty soldiers!
Put all five of them in chains!
Use Sea Stone on the Devil Fruit users!
You can leave the marine grunts where they are,
and follow me inside the laboratory.
It's dangerous here.
Strange creatures seem to be raining down on us,
but do not worry!
I will make sure our place remains safe!
Yes, Master!
The Cool Brothers seem to have failed me.
Well, there's no helping that.
Fighting Straw Hat and Law
must have been too much for them.
Central Lake - Zoro's Group
Disgusting!
Alright, Brook!  Reason with them.
Don't be absurd!
Do you really think
diplomacy will work on these monsters?!
They merged!
How about that... They're merging and growing bigger.
T-T-They're growing!
Of course I'm going!
Blood will be on my hands if I don't!
As a man, this is something I must do!
Sanji-san!
Just do something about the Slimes around us.
Please, take care!
That clumsy cook is such a pain.
They're doing it again!
St- Sto- Stop it, please!
Big!  Too big!
Stop!  I would really appreciate it if you stopped!
Stop!  Save me!
You did it!  I knew I could count on you, Zoro-san!
Gas!  Run away!
I've had enough of this!
I-I-It's poison gas!
My eyes!  My eyes!
Wait!  I had no eyes in the first place!
Why would you do that?!
You're just some freak with jelly for a body!
More poison gas!
What should we do, Zoro-san?!  It spews poison gas!
I just did that, didn't I?!
Try to learn from others, skeleton!
I thought maybe you just had bad luck.
We are surrounded!
This is not good.
It's so cold!
Where is that samurai's torso?!
Alright, I'll use...
Haki of Perception!
There's nowhere left for us to run!
I know!  The enemy is jelly!
You should eat and digest them.
No way!
Stop bullying me like that!
I am at least seventy years older than you!
Sorry... Grampa.
Who are you calling Grampa?!
I am still a fit young skel-
What's wrong?!
Samurai-san!  C-Calm down!
It's so cold!  Sorry, Nami-san.
Could that be...
the Slime's toxin?!
Come on, now!
I hope that the samurai's torso
hasn't been consumed by the toxins!
I've been using the Color of Perception for a while now, and yet...
He must be quite weak.
His life-signs are getting mixed with the fish,
so I can't tell where he is!
A shark?!
Hey, are you kidding me?!
A-Are you alright?
Hey, what is it?  What's going on?!
Hold it right there, damn fish!
Don't eat him, shark!
I-It hurts not!  It merely itches!
What the hell?
He's obviously in pain.
It hurts... not!
What if something has happened to Sanji-san?!
Let go of him, damn you!
Now!
Alright!  The final piece is safe!
With this, the samurai puzzle is completed!
I've gotta hurry and get back...
before the path is gone!
Damn it!
The poison's spread this much?!
Not good!  I've been cut off without realizing it!
Can Nami-san's muscles do what I need them to?
This'll cause her trouble later, but...
This is bad!
The poison has
almost completely spread through the lake!
Sanji-san, hurry!
Don't close!  Don't close!  Don't close!
Sanji-san!
Look at that, he got him!
He really did!
What can I say?
Never before have I been so happy
just to have the body I was born with!
Samurai from the Wano Kingdom
Foxfire Kinemon
Oh my!  Samurai-san, you certainly are big!
You're as tall as I am!
I just realized, I have not introduced myself properly!
My name is Kinemon!
I was born in Kuri, Wano Kingdom!
H-H-Hurry it up!
I'm gonna die here!
Very well!  I am most sorry.
Doron!
I'm still cold...
That coat will disappear if he takes it off, right?
Man with the eyebrows,
will you give me your name in return?
I'm Sanji!
And what do you mean by this?!
Just because you've got your body back,
you suddenly want a polite introduction-festival?!
You took full advantage when you were helpless...
and spouted countless cheeky rude comments at me!
You haven't forgotten, have you?!
You people are pirates?!
That explains your savagery!
I loathe pirates.  They make me vomit!
You're such an annoying bastard!
Just ask us!  Say "Please search for my body"!
I refuse to be indebted to a pirate!
I would sooner die than ask for your help!
Alas, I would be defenseless if you left me here,
but if you want to take me with you...
I would not complain.
I have not forgotten!
I will never...
forget what you've done for me!
For as long as I live!
I can never repay this debt!
Also, I never stopped doubting you until you gave me my torso back.
Please, forgive me for that!
I beg of you!  I beg of you!
Cut it out, idiot!  Raise your head!
A man shouldn't bow so easily!
But... if you had not shown up, I would have never...
Uh, I hate to interrupt, but... Sanji-san...
We do appear to be in the middle of a hopeless crisis.
Look.  See?
Laboratory Three
The drugs.
I just need to figure out
how the drugs used on the children were made.
Is that...
It is!  A book about drugs!
Now I just need the sedatives.
Master, we've prepared the airship.
Good...
Then, let us go and fetch our friends!
I'm sure they'll be wanting these.
Throw Straw Hat and the others into a cage
and take them to my room!
Yes, Master!
There's nowhere left to run!
Hey, you guys!
Didn't I tell you to take care of these things?!
We tried but nothing worked.  Not our fault.
Exactly.
Don't be so lax, idiots!
I can't let Nami-san's body be hurt!
This body...
This body absolutely must not...
You don't want to give it back, do you?
Of course I don't.
Shall we try to ignite them?
Foxfire Kinemon, I am called.
My blade is one that scorches its enemies.
I shall make that creature combust, and thus open a passage for us!
Scorches its enemies?  That sounds like magic!
He... cut the flames!
The way is open.
I am coming for you now, Momonosuke!
What the?!  We're unharmed!
I'm sure that we were
just engulfed by the flames of that explosion!
K-K-Kinemon-san... What just happened?
I merely slashed the explosion apart.
You cut it?!
My Foxfire Style scorches enemies with flames,
and furthermore,
one of its special techniques is to cut flames apart.
There is no fire I cannot cut!
Now then, I shall head for the laboratory to rescue Momonosuke.
Please excuse me!
Wait!
Your samurai fighting style has caught my interest.
I'll help you save your son.
The true identity of the mysterious man with the ability to completely dominate Law becomes known...
and it sends massive shocks throughout the crew.
And then the identity of the man
controlling both Caesar and the mysterious man...
is finally revealed!
Next time, on One Piece:
Shock!
The True Identity of the Mysterious Man, Vergo!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Shock!
The True Identity of the Mysterious Man, Vergo!