It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered,
and Luffy has broken into the world's largest prison, Impel Down,
to free his brother Ace, who is held captive by the Navy.
On the fourth level, the Inferno Floor, he was ambushed by Warden Magellan.
After capturing you, I'll take my time with you to learn just how you managed to break in here.
I'd die before telling you that!
NO!
Straw-chan...!
Bon-chan!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING, BON-CHAN?!
Like I said, it won't work!
If you get soaked in his poison, or even touch it, you're gone.
It doesn't matter how hard you struggle...
You won't ever leave this place!
Magellan is capable of silencing the prisoners in the world's greatest prison...
He's the ruler of Hell...
Let's see some determination, Bon Kurei!
No matter what I do, I can't win!
I'm so sorry!
I don't stand a chance of winning!
I'm running away!  Sorry!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan!
I'M SORRY!
You still have no intention of giving up?
I won't let Ace be executed!
If I'm doomed to lose because you're poisonous and I can't touch you,
then I'd rather touch you and...
give up my arms to beat you!
Sheesh, what a pain.
If you'd just passed through and caused a ruckus up above, I could've blamed the Warden!
Reporting in from Level Three Archway.
We've suffered some casualties from the escapees' bomb attack.
Yes, we've captured Buggy the Clown and Mister Three.
I told them they could go through, yet they still attacked me!
Freaking morons!
S-So strong!  I never expected him to be that strong!
That Hannyabal...
I don't want to be tortured...
If I'm to be tortured, I'd rather bite off my tongue right now...
I'n godda bide id!
I'll bide id!
I'll weally bide id!
H-Here he comes!
Outta my way!
Move it, dammit!
If you don't wanna get hurt...
then get outta my way!
Don't let Mister Two get away!
Damn!
Don't get in my way!
TL Note: Shabby Swan Ball
Is it really impossible to stand up to him?
I don't dream of such reckless things.
If I go over there, the odds of getting killed are 200%...
I'm running away!
No looking back!
There's no option... But to run!
Straw-chan!
To think you could bring me to my knees...
A cornered mouse is a frightful thing.
No matter, the poison covering your arms will be more than enough!
It'll rob you of your strength, bit by bit.
You're suffering, aren't you?  How shameful.
You're still not done?!
TL Note: Poison Pufferfish
It didn't work?!
Mist...?
TL Note: Poison Cloud
It's pointless.
This poison is part of me.
It's a living being!
Is your eyesight growing blurry?
Are your ears ringing?
TL Note: Rubber Balloon
I'm telling you it's pointless!  Don't you get it?!
No matter how hard you struggle, there's no escape for you.
Both your hands must be useless by now.
The poison will take everything away from you before long!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
I'm gonna bite it!
I'll really do it, you know!
There's no use trying to stop me!
I JUST CAN'T DO IT!
Dammit!
Take 'em away.
Yes sir!
Sheesh.
S-Stop!  Stop it!
TL Note: Goumon = Torture
I don't wanna be tortured!
TL Note: Koumon = Anus
Asses stink!
Indeed!
Hey, wait a second!
What?
This voice...
Could it be?!
TL Note: Swan Arabesque
Who are you?!
You're...!
Mister Two!
The third escapee!
Damn!
Don't get cocky!
Un!  Deux!  Trois!
You're pretty good, but I won't let you get away!
Who are you?
So cute...
W-W-What?
You don't know when to quit.
Do you really want to save your brother so badly?
It'd be easier for you to just lie down and shut your eyes.
Hey, guards!
Tell me the truth!
What's going on up above us?
Nothing at all.
Stupid fool.  Why would you go so far?
Portgas D. Ace is a felon sentenced to death!
And you are an intruder trying to rescue him!
I will not forgive any sin!
Ace's fated death at Marineford has long since been set in stone!
There's nothing you can do about it!
SHUT UP!!!
Stay away...
Don't come down here...
Luffy...!
You're only hurting yourself.
That's quite enough, isn't it?
GIVE ACE...
BACK!!!
This is your punishment.
After exposure to this much poison, no antidote will save you.
You will agonize for 24 hours...
and then you will descend to the REAL Hell!
Ace...!
After his defeat by Magellan, Luffy is thrown into Level Five.
Though he knows there is no antidote for Luffy's severe poisoning, Bon Kurei stands up to save his friend.
But a pack of Army-Wolves stand in his way!
Next time, on One Piece:
Because He's My Friend
Bon Kurei's Do-or-Die Rescue
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!