The great war that united Navy HQ and
the Seven Warlords of the Sea
to fight against the Whitebeard Pirates
ended two years ago.
This is the uninhabited island of Ruskaina,
located northwest of the Island of Women.
Luffy!
Yeah, I'm coming now.
Time sure flies.
It's already been two years, huh?
Hey!
Have a good look.  She is my friend.
Luffy, the ship is ready.  We can set sail any time.
Sure, thanks.
Incredible.
He's become the boss of this island.
Still, since I went and befriended these guys,
I don't get to eat them.
They look tasty, too.
It's fine, Luffy.
All your favorite foods are waiting on the ship.
I think that, since I am so thoughtful, I would make a fine wife for you.
I'm not marrying you, but thanks for the food.
I love that blunt side of you!
Rayleigh left half a year ago,
I'm sure he'll be waiting for you on Sabaody.
I managed to learn all the basics in a year and a half, after all.
Now it's time to say good bye to
you guys and this island.
Right...
Time to go!
Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
It's been two years... Sure doesn't feel like it.
True.
I'm looking forward to seeing how much they've grown.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It remains to be seen if they can regroup safely.
The name of the crew is known throughout the world now, after all.
Oh my...
Oh?  So you're the first.
What, none of the others have come yet?
Those guys are hopeless.
Have you heard that Navy HQ has relocated?
What, really?
Yeah.  They switched places with G1,
the base on the other side of the Red Line.
Just goes to show, the new Fleet Admiral who replaced Sengoku is ambitious.
I mean, he put his headquarters in the New World.
It's the territory of the Four Emperors!
Well, as a result, the Navy's presence here
has dropped off,
and the lawlessness on these islands has increased.
I thought this city was a little wilder than it was two years ago.
Hey, did you see this?!
Yeah, I was surprised too.
I never thought the Straw Hat Pirates
would come back!
You can say that again!
They haven't made a noise for two years
so I thought they were gone for good.
And now they're recruiting new members!
This island is still filled with pirates who survived the first half of the Grand Line.
He must be planning to expand his crew and cause a stir in the New World!
How exciting!  I wonder if he'll let me join?
Don't be a fool!  There are plenty of pirates with bounties exceeding one hundred million on this island.
Do you really think he'd waste his time on you?
What's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, old geezer!  Bring me some booze!
And food, too!  Gimme all you got!
U-Understood, right away!
Hey... Could that be?
No doubt about it.  They're...
The Straw Hat Crew!
Please, don't say that!
Can't you work something out?
The tickets are sold out.
Did you really think we'd have any left?
This island is the last stop of the megastar Soul King Brook's World Tour!
The concert hall is completely filled up!
Manager!
I'm gonna make this the best damn live show ever!
Yeah, we'll be counting on it!
The TD sales are at an all-time high.  They've exceeded one million!
You truly are the king of the soul music world!
Just listen to the audience!
Soul King!  Soul King!
Manager...
Actually, I've got somethin' important to tell ya before the concert.
What is it?
Come on Baby!
Yeah!  I'm just bones!
Bone!
Bone to be wild!
Bone!  Bone!  Bone!  Booone!
Macho, yet unpopular with the ladies.
That's the brutal truth.
Soul King, mysterious...
He's nothing but bones!
I was wondering what he'd say.
How self-centered!
Hey!  Hand me the Snail Phone!
I won't let you get away with this, Brook!
Let's make this the best anniversary ever!
Yeah!
Long time no see, Sabaody.
I'm back at last.
It's a woman!  A real woman!
There's no doubt about it!  Those are honest-to-god, genuine ladies before my eyes!
Real women live on this island,
I've dreamed of this for so long!
Viva Sabaody!  I need ladies!
Sanji-kyun!
So, this is where we part ways.
It's quite sad, but I'm sure we'll meet again someday.
I never want to see you again!  Thanks for taking me here!
Give my regards to Iva, and good bye!
Sanji the Man has just returned from hell!
Hey, did you know?  Men tend to
unconsciously act mean toward the girls they like.
Yes, I think I've heard about that.
I'll never forget about him!
Wait for me, Nami-swan!  Robin-chwan!
Huh?  Did I hear you right?
Your bounty's fifty-five million beli?
Take another look at the poster!
Your bounty has to be at least seventy million beli!
I won't deal with any captains worth less than that.
I can't believe you made it this far with such a miserable bounty.
Dammit...
Get lost, brat.
I am the son of Dragon the Revolutionary, you know!
You'd just slow us down!
We are the destined pirates!
We're on different levels.
Don't think that we'll accept just anyone!
Get lost!
Straw Hat Luffy is merciless.
What can we do, though?  He's really strong.
Hey, Franky!  How many have we got so far?
About a hundred in all.
Three entire pirate crews have joined us.
Ten of the pirates have bounties on their heads.
Sounds great.  And among those ten, we have two infamous rookies.
The Marine-Killers,
Wet-Hair Caribou and Blood-Splatter Coribou.
A pair of brothers, both captains, with bounties of
190 million and 210 million respectively.
We'll put them to good use!
More of our underlings are comin' here!  Old geezer!  We'll need more booze!
R-Right.
Make it quick!
Oh, and you, the girl who's been sitting there this whole time!
Don't just sit there and sulk by yourself.
Come over here!
That's one fine lady!
Hey, woman!  Didn't you hear me?!
He's calling for you.
No thank you.
I'm waiting for a man.
She turned him down!
Hey, hey!  You'd better listen to what he says!
That guy is Straw Hat Luffy!
That insane pirate who charged into the great war two years ago!
Don't you know about him?!
You're waiting for a man?
I'm sure he's some weakling who'll cry and beg for forgiveness when he hears Captain Luffy's name!
Get your ass over here!
I'll only say it one more time.
You're not my type.  I refuse to drink with you.
Are we clear, Straw Hat...
Who did you say you were?
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Did you just ask who I am?!
I'm Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, you!  Apologize quick!  This is bad!
You've got some nerve!
Huh?!
I'll deal with this.
You're quite an interesting girl.
Right, I'll give you two choices.
Will you accept Captain Luffy's invitation?
Or will you die?
For the record, I'm wanted too.
They call me the Cat Burglar, Nami.
Don't underestimate me!
Sure-Kill Green Star
What is this?!
H-Hey, what the hell is going on?!
Save me, Captain!
Don't come any closer, you idiot!
What is that plant?!
Well Miss, would you like to drink with me instead?
Usopp!  It's been so long!
I see you've gotten a little bit manlier!
I-I see you've blossomed too.
What the hell?!  The man she was waiting for
was that geeky guy?!
Was that your doing?
You bet it was!
That's my new weapon, the Pop Green!
It's not like I've spent the past two years
staring blankly at the sea!
Sorry to say,
but I've graduated from the "weakling-trio" I used to be in with you and Chopper.
No matter what happens, I won't be scared!  That's the kind of warrior I've become!
H-Hey, brat!  Don't tell me you did this?!
What?!  Sogeking?!  But how?!
Just ignore that idiot, Usopp.
Let's get out of this bar.  I've got a favor to ask.
Wait a second, you bastards!
Huh?!  Luffy?!
Come on!
Wait, customers!  You haven't paid!
Keep the change!
Damn, they're making us look bad!
Get them back here!
Damn it.
Huh?  What are these black soap-bubbles?!
What are these things?  Clouds?!
What's going on?!
So you see, I gained some new technology myself.
Seriously?!  You were in the sky?!
Those two...
Find them...
and kill them!
A report from Sabaody Archipelago!
What?!  The Straw Hat Crew?!
Yes, Sir!  Apparently, they're recruiting new members on the island!
Contact HQ!  If it's true then he's still alive
and we must do something!
Request backup immediately!
And order a search of the Sabaody Archipelago!
Yes, Sir!
Did I lose them?
Brook's holding a live concert?
The Straw Hat Crew is recruiting new members?
What is going on here?
Soul King?
I don't believe it.
Not a single scratch!
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Sunny!
We'll set sail soon!
These Gramans are really delicious!
I wonder how the others are doing?  I really want to see them soon!
Hey!  Are you alright?  Hey!
How could he?!  He just shot her without warning!
How awful!
Hey, hang in there!
How could you do this?!
What did we ever do to you?!
I said I was sorry, right?  I got the wrong people.
Sorry.  I just happen to be
looking for someone who looks like you.
A woman with a man who has long hair and a long nose.
You got the wrong people?!  And then you just shot her?!
That Straw Hat Luffy is terrible!
Huh?  Did you just say that
you don't like what I'm doing?
Seems like you did.
If you're gonna blame anyone, then blame them!
Hey hang on!  Are you alright?
Hunt those two down, you guys!
I won't let them get away with what they did!
We'll kill them to set an example!
Oh, did I bump into you?  Sorry about that.
See ya.
What's he doing?
Doesn't he know who Straw Hat Luffy is?
H-He's dead.
Wait just a minute!
After running into the fake Luffy,
Luffy's new power is activated!
Next time, on One Piece:
An Explosive Situation!
Luffy VS Fake Luffy
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!