It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and is hurrying toward Navy HQ to save his brother Ace.
At Navy HQ, Ace's execution drew ever closer...
when suddenly the Whitebeard Pirates appeared.
I take it my beloved son...
is still doing well?
Old Man!
And finally, total war broke out!
What are these tremors?!
Here it comes.  The seaquake that he set off earlier...
is coming back as a tsunami!
It's a tsunami!
Huh, what's this?  You're gonna fight now?
I merely wish to measure...
to see for myself...
the true distance between us and that man.
Oh, crap!
Run!
Old Man!
He stopped it... The most powerful slash in the world!
T-That's...!
The Commander of the Third Division...
Diamond Jozu!
This is no time to get distracted!
Advance, men!
Intercept them!
How naive.
They're trying to take us head-on?
Artillery units!
Shoot the enemy ships and the advancing pirates!
Yes, Sir!
Forward units, do everything you can to prevent the pirates from reaching the plaza!
Honestly...
It's what I expected, Whitebeard's Commanders all possess monstrous power.
In order to keep our losses as low as we can...
I suppose we've got no choice but to remove the "head" first.
I-It's too bright!
What's that?
K-Kizaru is here!
Hey, now.  That's really bright, you know.
He blocked the Admiral's attack!
What is that?
He's covered in blue flames!
Blue flames?
You can't just...
go straight for...
the King, you know!
You Whitebeard Pirates sure are scary!
What's with his body?
He took Kizaru-san's attack head-on, yet he's still alive!
His ability is as powerful as the rumors said!
A power even more rare than the Logia Fruits...
The Mythical Zoan Type.
Look! His wounds are disappearing!
I don't believe this!  How could that attack not work!
Oh, it worked, alright...
You liar.
That's the First Division Commander!
No matter what hits him, he recovers by flame...
Marco the Phoenix!
I've never seen a bird like this before...
Well, this is working, alright...
You liar!
Kizaru-san was sent flying!
You're kidding, right?
Kizaru-san!
Hmmm, well... It looks like...
I won't be able to take the "head" that easily.
Giant unit!  Watch out for attacks coming from the sky, too!
Sure!
The giants are coming!
Aim for their legs!  Bring them down!
You guys, stand back!
Jozu!
What power!
Get out of the way!
What is he planning to do?!
Try stopping THIS!
It's a block of ice!
It's way too big!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
I swear, those two are just...
They simply went and left their stations!
If we're not here...
then WHO will protect this area?!
Akainu-san!
That enormous ice-block...
He completely vaporized it!
This is bad!
Get out of here!
Volcanic rocks!
We can't let them hit us!
Damn bastard!
One of our ships has been hit!
Get away from the ships!
It's like watching the end of the world!
These flames are too flashy.
Why don't you go light some candles on a birthday cake instead, magma-brat?
You don't like flashy funerals, Whitebeard?
Three ships left!
Fire!  Don't stop!
Don't hesitate!
Advance towards the plaza!
Stop the Commanders!
Don't let them reach the shore!
Sink the Moby Dick!  Kill Whitebeard!
T-These are pirates...
This is a real battlefield!
It's hopeless!
My legs are numb... I can't move!
This is impossible!
We wouldn't stand a chance against these guys!
You think so too, right?
These guys are all monsters!
This is no place for youngsters like us!
Let's run away, okay?
Hey!
But...!
Are you stupid?!
If we seriously try to fight this battle,
we won't last a second!  You know that, don't you?!
You want to become an Admiral, right?!
Someday, I will...
become one...
of the Navy's Admirals!
You're gonna fight me, aren't you?
So, of course you gotta advance that far!
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
That's just another reason!
Neither of us can afford to die here!
It's still too soon for us to die!
But, I promised Luffy-san!
W-What is it now?
Here he comes!
Fire!  Shoot it!
Break through the blockade of warships!
Ace-kun!
Alright, go!
Little Oars Junior!
He's the descendant of the Continent-Puller, Oars!
He's enormous!  Far larger than an ordinary giant!
Don't let him into the bay!  He's trying to breach our defenses!
So, Oars's descendant is one of Whitebeard's men?
I want him!  I want his corpse!
He makes me tingle!
Oars!
Ace-kun is a nice guy!
I ain't lettin' ya kill him!
The Demon Oars once caused the Straw Hats a lot of trouble...
Now his descendant, one of Whitebeard's allies, opens a path to the bay to rescue Ace.
What will the Navy do to stand up to his strength, which overwhelms even the Giant corps?
Next time, on One Piece:
The Demon's Descendant!
Little Oars Junior Dashes!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!