Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew find themselves drawn into these events.
Looks like everyone's super fired up!
An army of fifty thousand...
This is an ideal stage to reveal my surprises!
Surprises?
What are you talking about, Franky?
The Sunny's got some new weapons!  Two of them!
Anyone want to try them?
New weapons?!
It won't stop!
It's a tornado that slices anything it touches!
Run!  It'll cut you into pieces!
How far is it gonna chase us?!
All the way to the ends of hell.
Huh?  He's not here.
Amazing!  Sanji is flying!
You can bring a hundred thousand men, or even a million...
We'll send 'em all flying!
Grrr...
This isn't over yet, Moss-Head!
As if I'd lose to you, Nosebleed!
Why are they competing with each other?
Don't mind them.  They're always like this.
Honestly...  In that respect, they haven't matured at all.
The battlefield seems to have really heated up.
I guess it's time to bring them out.
Them?  You mean...
We finally get to use the new weapons?!
Indeed, my friends!  This way!
I've been waiting for this!
Hey!  Wait for me!
H-Hey!  Don't leave me out here alone!
You're in my way!  Go fight somewhere else!
No, you get lost!
Cut it out already, you freaks!
Shut the hell up!
They're... too strong...
What did you just say?!
You think humans are strong?!
And you dare to call yourself a fishman?!
C-Captain...
I-I'm sorry.
You shouldn't disappoint me too much.
I have no need for an underling...
who's afraid of humans!
Go kill Shirahoshi already!
This is amazing!
Something's changed here.
Doors five and six weren't here before.
You're right!  The zeros are gone!
I've done some renovations!  I modified the
old Dock Zeros, and renamed them Five and Six!
The new weapons are stored in Dock Four,
which used to be empty...
and the new Dock Five!
Whatever, just hurry up and show us the new weapons!
Alright, I understand how you feel...
Look and be amazed!
This is it!
Amazing!
Let's finish this -dosun!
Bombarding Squad!
Aim for Shirahoshi!
I'm afraid I cannot allow that.
How could you try to hurt the Mermaid Princess,
who is beloved by the whole world?
What's going on?  It got dark all of a sudden.
Welcome to festival night!
What?
Is this...
an amusement park?
Now, let's dance!
Are we...
dreaming or something?
Now, launch the fireworks!
This is great!
It's so beautiful!
Hey!  I told you to aim for the Princess -bokan!
But...
Dosun-san, we're at such a fun festival.
Alright!  You have already been cut.
What?!
Such a large mob charging at a fragile maiden...
How barbaric!
Feet?!
Sorry for this.
It's really noisy outside.
What's going on?
Hey, you two get out of here!  It's too cramped!
You don't even care about the new weapons,
do you?  You get out!
I got in because it's too scary outside!
I don't want to be left outside either!
Franky, can we use the weapons yet?
Don't be so impatient.
Now, it's time for the show!
I'm starting to get excited too!
Hey wait... I'm supposed to be steering this thing.
It got bigger!
What's going on?
Now, the Sunny Soldier Dock's new weapons...
So excited!
What's gonna happen?
...will be unveiled!
Lethal Poison Squad, go!
Yeah!
Giant feet, giant hands, or whatever...
A single hit from our poisonous weapons
will take them down!
Now wait just a minute!
Soldier Dock System...
Channel Four!
There's an opening!
Smash that ship to pieces!
The Black Rhino...
FR-U 4!
Soldier Dock System...
Channel Four!
The Black Rhino...
FR-U 4!
That's so awesome!  A motorcycle!
What is that thing?  It looks powerful!
What was that about poisonous weapons?
What is that?!
You think they'll work on this steel monster?  Just go ahead and try to stab it!
Well?  Super cool, isn't it?
Stop them!
Right... Fight steel with steel!
Leave it to me!
Take this!  I'm gonna flatten you!
Hey!
The New Number, Channel Five!
Brachio Tank 5 has arrived!
There it is!  A dinosaur!  I wanna try it!
Amazing!
Did you see my bombardment skills?
Looks like it's got plenty of other features, too.
But... he's supposed to be a shipwright... isn't he?
Commander Chopper reporting in!
A group of enemies spotted at nine o'clock!
Fire!
Commander, you're so cool!
Keep fighting, damn you!
Amazing... Those guys are truly amazing!
There's only ten of them, yet they're fighting
an army of a hundred thousand like it was nothing!
The Straw Hat Pirates.
Perhaps they really can save us and Fishman Island?
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
Beat Hody!
That's it, Straw Hat!
Boss Jinbe!
If you win,
you can have all you can eat at my restaurant!
You can drink all the booze you want from my store too!
Straw Hat!
We're counting on you!
Boss Jinbe!
They're all getting carried away.
Show yourself, Kraken!
It's huuuge!
They're just ten people.  Flatten them!
That'll be the end of it!
Oh no!  He summoned the legendary beast,
the Kraken!
Get out of the way!
It doesn't matter how strong the Straw Hats are,
if that thing smashes them they're dead for sure!
Alright, it's the Kraken!  He's the captain's slave!
He's freakishly strong!
It's time you learn how terrifying deep sea creatures can be!
Hey, isn't that...
What are you doing?!
Don't hesitate.  I brought you here from the North Pole!
You're my slave!
Serve your master!
You can do it, can't you?!
P-P-Please wait!
Retreat!
Hey, wasn't he...
There can't be more than one giant beast like that!
Huh?  You guys know that thing?
I never expected that
this would be the place we saw you again.
Hey, Surume!
It's me!
Surume!
Huh, you forgot?
You're just hopeless!
I made you my pet earlier.  We're friends, right?
Wah! The Umibouzu...
Hey, that's enough!
Cut it out!
You did great!
Unbelievable!  You actually tamed it?!
That monstrous octopus?!
That's right!  I'm using him to travel like a pro!
Isn't that right, Surume?
Let me ride you again!
He did it!
Luffy-sama!
That tickles!  C-Cut it out, Surume!
What?!
Alright... Surume!  Let's get going!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Stop, Kraken!
You stupid octopus!
Go get 'em, Surume!
Help me... Captain...
Kraken, over there!
Damn it, what's going on?!
The Kraken is acting all friendly with Straw Hat!
Listen up, Surume.
You stay here and protect Weak-hoshi!
I can't believe you're friends with the Kraken.
The relationships you have always take me by surprise!
Really?
Uhm... I'm very pleased to meet you, Surume-sama.
There's still plenty of them left.
Right!  Let's do this!
The Sunny's two new weapons
activate the Docking of Dreams!
A miraculous robot is born!
Next time, on One Piece:
Iron Pirate!
General Franky Arrives
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!