The goal is the last island Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached the legendary island except for the King of the Pirates, Gold Roger.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gomu Gomu no Mi.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates
is making its way through the vast sea
with their sights set on One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
the island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island
that is as high as the clouds is,
as its name suggests, an elephant
who has been alive for a millennium.
Now, we're gonna go.
So can we have lots of food?
That's... really bad!
Quickly, I gotta let everyone know!
Save the Zunisha
The Straw Hats Rescue Operation!
Yeah, yeah! You can take
as much food as you want!
Carrot. Show Straw Hat the way to the food storage.
Yes!
Thanks!
We have a problem!
What's wrong, Musatobi?
Don't tell me Jack is back again!
N-No! It's not about Jack!
One of Zunisha's forelegs is...
It looks really terrible...
The wound is so large and deep...
It's miraculous that
he's still on his feet.
Are we safe now?
I'm sorry!
No, that's okay.
So this is what Jack left us with.
We must do something as soon as possible!
Say, Luffy...
Can we delay our departure a bit?
You wanna treat the elephant's leg?
Uh-huh!
All right, got it! Treat him quickly!
No, we're grateful to you but-
What are you saying?
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
Alliance?
But...
With this many people, we'll be finished quickly.
Yup! Count on us!
That's right!
Yes, yes!
I knew this is what we'd do.
Okay, let's do it!
Right, Chopper?
Uh-huh!
First, we need tons of medicinal herbs! That, I can get!
But the problem is the bandage.
A bandage, huh?
How can we wrap his massive leg?
I mean, is there a bandage for an elephant in the first place?
I think I can get a bandage.
Really?
Yes, leave it to me!
Counting on you, Robin!
Now, let's talk about how
we apply the bandage.
Hey, when you found out Jack was alive,
you said "Send out the ships", didn't you?
Yeah.
How do you launch them?
Don't tell me you simply throw them down, do you?
It's so high. They would break.
Let me show you!
This place was affected by Jack's attack too! It's a mess!
Oh, Franky, over there!
I see. They move the ships
up and down with these.
Unlike other stuff, they look fine. Yosh!
Zoro! Brook! Kin'emon!
Fell some trees from the forest!
Got it!
Did you hear that, you all?
Devote all of your strength and,
with the Straw Hats, save Zunisha!
Yeah!
We're really getting so much
help from you-teia guys.
How can we thank you for going this far-
It's fine, it's fine! Don't mention it!
We'll definitely repay you for this somehow.
Oh no, please...
Oh yeah!
Say Wanda, do you have a sea chart
that shows the way to Big Mom's island?
A sea chart?
Yes. If you do,
I wanna do my homework before the voyage.
I'd rather not have any trouble navigating.
A sea chart...
I think we have one.
Everyone!
Collect this herb!
As much as you can!
Understood, Chopper-sensei!
Oh, you can use it as medicine?
I didn't know that.
The leaf part is for hemostasis
and the stem part is for sterilization.
Both parts work very well
but since it's a very rare herb,
you don't often see it in encyclopedias.
I see! That's why.
There are so many here so that's great!
Chopper-sensei, is there
anything you don't know?
It's going well!
Ready and!
Here we go!
There!
Are you ready?
We are!
Yes!
Hands came out!
Needlewoman!
The sheets have been sewn together!
There are so many hands! Cool!
We'll repeat this over and over
to make it one big bandage.
Now, lay them side by side again.
Yes!
All right! It's going well here too!
Now then, let's begin.
Okay, I've cut them.
Wow! When did he-
That was awesome, Baron Corpse!
This again?
Garchu, Baron Corpse!
Hey, please...
Never mind.
Just do whatever you want.
Okay, it's my turn!
That's cool too, Kin'emon!
But don't set the wood on fire!
I-Is that ninpo?
Th-This! It's not.
Hey! Take those to Franky now.
Where did they all go?
It's the other way around.
You walked off on your own, Zoro-ya.
Are you that ridiculously terrible
with directions?
Boo! Boo! You stray swordsman!
Shut up! I can carry them on my own!
Then you'll have no problem, right?
That's a waste of time.
We don't want you to get lost again.
You bastard! How could you say-
Eh? Eh!
He disappeared?
That bastard...
A little old. Does it help?
Yeah, it's good enough. Thanks.
I appreciate it.
Big Mom's headquarters is down this way.
Unfortunately, we don't
have a map of the island.
I see. If we travel at normal speed,
it'll take more than a week.
Maybe.
We gotta get going!
We have to make it in time for the tea party!
To return the favor...
To help them-gara make it
to Big Mom's island safely...
We have no choice but to travel with them!
Oh, there's a small isolated island here.
You're right. It's as tiny as a rice grain!
Not even an ant could live on such an island!
No, no! It looks that way
because this is a sea chart.
It'd be nice if they have a restaurant there!
I don't know about that!
I mean, when did you guys get here?
Yosh! Everything's going well!
Jeez...
Is that...?
Oh, they're finally here!
One, two!
All right, shall we begin?
Oh, so cool!
It's beautifully done! They look brand-new!
It barely looks like the work of a human!
That's because I'm a super cyborg shipwright
who's beyond human understanding!
Hey, Franky! The medicine is prepared!
The bandages are completed too!
Huh? Where's Robin?
She's making extra bandages to change later.
How thoughtful! That's our Robin!
Laying the tracks is complete too!
Yosh, guys!
Bind the gondolas to the ropes
and get on board!
Yeah!
I thought so!
What's wrong, Nami?
It's a Silent Supercell!
What's that?
It's a massive thundercloud that
appears without warning.
It'll cause a severe storm.
Even if it breezes by, it'll wreak enormous havoc!
What?
Luffy! Tell them to stop the elephant's treatment!
We gotta evacuate everybody right away!
Wind it up!
Down! Down!
Okay, stop!
This is really a terrible wound!
Yes.
I'm sure it's unbearably painful,
but he's staying calm and letting us treat him.
Yosh, yosh, you're doing great!
It won't be long!
I bet Zunisha senses Chopper-sensei's
passion to cure him like we do.
It'd be so nice if I could
study medical care under him.
It's done here! Apply the bandage!
Got it!
Hey! Move the gondola down slowly!
Roger!
Wind it up!
This is bad! We can't make it in time like this!
I'll go on ahead!
Carrot! Go assist Luffy!
Yeah!
Hang on tight!
Don't get shaken off!
The wind is so strong!
If nothing is done, the gondolas will...
This is pretty bad. With this much
wind, the tracks and the ropes will...
Pull it up now!
I'm gonna be blown off!
Luffy! This way!
There!
Usopp!
This is it...
Hang on!
Grab on!
Luffy!
Made it in time!
You're okay now! Move slowly!
It stopped.
Luffy!
Thank goodness! Way to go, Luffy!
But he can't hold out forever!
We gotta lift everyone up quickly!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now everyone, climb up!
We're okay now!
Robin!
C-Climb now!
Thank goodness!
Oh, that was a hell of a storm.
Let's get to work!
Yeah!
Here we are!
Great! It hasn't collapsed!
Food!
There are tons of it!
But it's so messy...
It doesn't matter if it's messy.
It's still food!
Still, you guys are awesome, Luffy!
Awesome?
So awesome! You have Chopper-sensei
who can cure anything,
and you have Nami the navigator
who can predict weather like a prophet!
Baron Corpse is a famous musician, isn't he?
Yeah.
And you have...
God Usopp who has 8,000 followers,
and Robot Franky
who is like a jack in the box!
You have the great, but-tends-to-stray.
swordsman Zoro
and a good sewer Robin who
can sprout many hands!
Robin is an archaeologist!
She's very smart!
Oh, is she?
And Sanji. He saved the whole country
and made delicious soup for us!
He's such a good cook!
And the awesome captain who brings together
those awesome members - Luffy!
What's with that? The backpack is already full!
I should've brought a bigger one!
Say, Luffy,
can I come along with you guys?
I forgot!
What, what?
Pekomamushi!
Peko...
That was close! I almost left without him!
Sorry to ask you this but
could you take this to the gate for me?
That's where our ship is!
I'll go pick him up and be there soon too!
But...
See ya! I'm counting on you!
Gee...
One, two!
Yosh! That's good!
A little more to go! You can do it!
Now I think we can finish this.
I was worried at one point there.
Truly, thank you very much, you-gara all!
Thank you, Robin!
Thank you!
That's not enough! Get out of my way!
You brave ones who saved our country
not only once but twice!
Truly, truly, truly,
thank you!
That's too much.
The sea is beautiful.
I wanna sail out to sea even just once.
Yeah, I guess I have no choice!
This is for you, Bariete.
Hey!
Pekomamushi!
In preparation for taking down Kaido, Zoro and the others go on ahead to the Wano Kuni!
Meanwhile, Luffy sets out for Whole Cake Island, where Big Mom resides, to take back Sanji!
They finally set sail on the sea where the yonko reign!
A dramatic new adventure now begins!
Next time on One Piece!
Descending the Elephant
Setting Sail for Sanji’s Retrieval!
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
Descending the Elephant
Setting Sail for Sanji’s Retrieval!