It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
In order to save his brother Ace, who has been captured by the Navy...
...Luffy is heading to the great prison, Impel Down.
Meanwhile, his companions have been sent to different islands.
How many times must I repeat myself before you understand?!
You ought to remember it after the first time, you imbecile.
My meals must weigh no less than 100 kilograms!
Any less than that, it will not satisfy my hunger!
Do you wish for me to turn you to stone again?!
N-No! Please forgive me!
I'll be more precise this time!
Someone bring her another meal now!
Here, Luffy. Dig in!
This is delicious!
And the fact that you're feeding it to me makes the meal even better!
Oh, you don't mean that...
If only that would happen...
Hey, what're you doin' over there in the corner?
You're not eating anything? This Sea King-meat tastes awesome.
I-I am fine...
My heart is already full...
Damn, I can't see her!
She's got the curtains up!
It's true. I can't see!
Maybe I can see through this crack...?
TL Note: Madly in love
What happened?
Oh, there were two ill-mannered mice sneaking around...
I got rid of them both.
Really?
I-Is that-?
They're examples...
That's what happens to anyone who tries to peek into Hancock's room!
Scary!
Once again, we will go a little back in time.
This is a certain island in South Blue.
Luffy...
Guys...
Why is none of them here?
Did they all get killed by those three?
That can't be it!
I'd never accept that!
GUYS!
Chopper!
Luffy!
You guys!
I wasn't scared at all, even though I was on my own...
It's true...
That hurts... Cut it out, Luffy, Usopp...
I said stop it, jerks...
That hurts, you jerks.
What's with these birds?!
They're too big!
You wanna eat me?!
My body's not listening to me!
Stop that...!
Let go of me!
You damn jerk!
What is WITH this island?!
Is this a dream too?
PLEASE BE A DREAM!
Please stop...!
Please don't play around with me...!
I'm... safe...?
Where am I?
Is there nobody else here?
Luffy!
Guys!
Seems like I'm the only one on this island...
What should I do out here?
I'm thirsty, and hungry...
If only Luffy and the others were here...
...then even this uninhabited island...
...would become a party!
It's a party, let's dance!
Maybe I won't ever get to see them again...?
I DON'T WANT THAT!
Where are they?
Luffy... Guys...
That's right!
I have this!
We all promised to meet up at the place this Vivre Card is pointing towards!
If I go there, I'll get to meet Luffy and the others!
No matter what happens, there's no way those guys will die!
I'll return, no matter what!
I don't have time to sit around moping here!
This is for the sake of reuniting with the others! I'll eat what I can find and survive!
This fruit is bitter!
But it has lots of water!
This one's salty!
Gotcha!
I guess I can eat meet too, huh?
But there's no way this'll taste good...
Well, you can't expect much from a deserted island anyway...
Wait, damn you!
You're not getting away!
Who...
...was it that knocked me out...?
Something's hot...
THEY'RE PLANNING TO EAT ME?!
It's a raccoon dog. How rare!
We having raccoon dog stew.
I'd rather kill damn bird, eat bird stew.
If we could do that, would have no troubles.
Have to settle for raccoon dog.
Stop it! I'm a REINDEER!
Then we be having reindeer stew...
Huh? It talk just now?
Reindeer can talk?
LET ME GO! LET ME GO!
Is terrible!
We try attacking bird's nest, but they find us!
The birds be attacking!
We have to run!
We go too!
Go!
Hey, wait! Untie me before you leave!
It looks like the birds are stronger...
Oh crap!
The birds used me like a toy...
The people tried to boil me in a stew...
What is WITH this island?!
Legends say that this is a treasure island...
Torino Kingdom where birds reign over humans...
What will become of Chopper?
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
This is the Island of Dreams in the Grand Line...
Momoiro Island.
To my dear Nami-san and Robin-chan...
Are you doing well?
Right now, I'm...
I'm...
Where am I?
Damn it... This is all that Warlord's fault...
U-Um... Mister?
Mister?
Are you alright?
What is this feeling?
This sweet scent...
Is this the lap of a beautiful lady?
Could it be... Nami-san?
No... Robin-chan?
Guess it's just a dream anyway...
I don't care if it's a dream... I want to stay like this forever...
W-Wait! Please!
Is this...?
Um, your handkerchief!
Huh?
It wasn't a dream?
Elizabeth?
Still, where is this place?
It couldn't be Heaven, right?
Elizabeth, huh?
If this is Heaven, is she an angel?
Oh, my heart is in pain!
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Indeed, this must be...
...love!
And the birth of romance!
Sanji-san!
No, no...
Nami-san and Robin-chan are waiting for me!
But...
First, I've gotta repay her for what she did.
I'm not the type of man who forgets his manners!
Nami-san, Robin-chan! Please forgive my unfaithful heart!
ELIZABETH-CHWAN!
It has the same writing on it as the handkerchief.
Could that be Elizabeth-chan's house?
Is Lady Elizabeth here?
I am Sanji, whom she helped out earlier.
Um, I am here to return her handkerchief...
D-Don't be like that, Elizabeth-chan!
There's no rush.
She is a shy and reserved lady.
I've got to stay calm here.
Um, I'm sorry about that.
Your hands were just so charming...
so... I... should I say, was just overwhelmed for a second...
So, how can I persuade you to forgive me?
What do you say? Perhaps we could eat something together?
I'll prepare whatever you like!
I may not look it, but I'm an excellent cook!
Oh well...
Um, do you like cooking?
Yes! I love it!
Then, do you like western clothing?
Western clothing?
Uh, of course!
Unlike a certain idiot swordsman, I care about my appearance!
Really? So, you like western clothing?
Uh, yes!
Then, do you like dresses?
Dresses?
Could she...?!
Is this sudden rush of interest perhaps a sign that she's...
...taken a liking to me?!
What do you think about this dress? Do you like it?
I like them! I like them! I love them!
I could look at them all day!
Then what about floral prints?
FLORAL PRINTS... OH, FLORALS ARE GREAT!
THEY'RE SO CUTE!
In that case...
At last, the door to Elizabeth-chan's heart has...
You've got really good taste, Elizabeth-chan.
You need not be ashamed.
You have already opened the door to my heart.
Sanji-san.
Don't hesitate! Please, throw yourself straight at my chest!
Elizabeth-chwan~!
I think...
...this would look FANTASTIC on you!
That hurts...
Despite your looks, you're really strong, huh?
Elizabeth-cha-
Is this... a dream...?
If so...
It's a nightmare!
I was sure you'd think that!
It must have been hard! But you don't need to deceive yourself any longer!
Indeed! This is a country of freedom!
Now, please wear this dress! Open the door of my heart!
I don't wanna open it!
Wait!
This is the island known as the second Island of Women.
Everything from the trees to the sea is purely pink.
The humans and animals gathered on this island...
...all possess maiden hearts.
WHAT KIND OF HEAVEN IS THIS?!
Wait up~!
You're like us!
You are, right?!
Shut up! Don't follow me!
I keep telling you, I'm not!
To my dear Nami-san and Robin-chan...
Are you doing well?
Right now, I'm...
I'm...
I'm...!
Wait! Wait!
Wait up, dammit!
NO WAY I'D WAIT!
WELCOME TO THE CROSSDRESSER KINGDOM!
Right now...
I'm in Hell.
In a kingdom where the snow falls silently...
...and people have been slaving away for 700 years.
This is where Robin regains consciousness.
At the same time, Usopp is about to be eaten by a mysterious plant!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew's Whereabouts
The Bridge Connecting Islands and the Man-Eating Plants
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!