It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The Straw Hat Pirates have been scattered,
and Luffy, in order to save his brother Ace, who has been captured by the Navy,
has broken out of the world's greatest prison, Impel Down.
Now, he sails for Navy HQ.
Meanwhile, after being blasted off Sabaody Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
what's happened with the Straw Hat crew?
I see.
Navy HQ sounds even worse than Impel Down was.
Navy HQ is afraid that old Whitebeard will attack them,
so they've called their greatest forces together to one place.
I wanted to avoid an all-out war, but it seems inevitable now.
We now go back in time a little.
This is the Kamabakka Drag Queendom, located on Momoiro Island in the Grand Line.
Sheesh, what's with all the Okama on this island?
You're one of us too, right?  You're just like us, right?!
Wait!
Damn it!  Stay away from me!
WHAT?!
How can they be so strong?!
Those people are definitely...
not normal Okama!
Nami-san!  Robin-chan!
When will we ever meet again?!
I see.
There were other Candies who had a hard time being honest with themselves when they first came here, but...
I suppose it's time we offered a helping hand.
By the way, is this boy strong?
He's nothing too impressive, but his kicks are rather fierce.
Then we should try and win him over with our traditional method, we haven't used it for a while.
Don't you ever give up?
Why...?!
Why are you...
chasing after me?!
Wait!
LIKE HELL I'LL WAIT!
What is this place?
And more importantly...
WHAT IS WITH THESE GUYS?!
Damn it...
I've been waiting for you, dear!
Who the hell are you?!
Do not be rude!  You will refer to her as "Carol-sama"!
So you're the queen of this country?!
Queen? Oh, no...
To be precise, I am the queen's...
substitute!
I'm Caroline!
Sign: "Substitute"
Carol-sama!
Substitute...?
I'm a temporary replacement for the legendary queen of the Kamabakka Drag Queendom...  Iva-sama.
I'm not worthy of being called "Queen"!
I don't care if you're the substitute queen, or whatever.  Let me be perfectly clear!
I've had enough of this place!  Let me go!
Is that so?  Very well.
Huh?
So long as you're able to defeat Kamabakka's strongest fighter.
What do you say?
Perfect!  I accept your challenge!
Then you'll have to wear the Kamabakka Drag Queendom's traditional battle-outfit!
Battle-outfit?
So their "battle-outfit"...
was this thing?!
Cute!
SHUT THE HELL UP!
Do you seriously think I'll stay like this?!
I'll finish this in a second, with just one kick!
And then I can say goodbye to this damn island!
Sexy!
What's this?
You're my opponent?
As substitute queen of the Kamabakka Drag Queendom...
I am also leader of the Kamabakka forces and Newkama Kenpo's grandmaster...
...'s substitute.
YOU'RE JUST A SUBSTITUTE FOR THAT TOO?!
Well, let's get this over with!
I will show you my secret technique!
I don't plan on giving you a chance to show me!
I'll finish this battle with this one attack!
This meal's done.
Huh?  There's nobody there...
Here I am, little Candy!
Damn it!
This is strange...  Why do I keep missing?
And what's with those eyes?
And these strange movements...
Don't tell me this freak's...
They look really good on you!
H-Hey, don't look!
No, wait!  Why should I get embarrassed because people can see my underwear?!
Such is the true nature of your honest maiden's heart.
Shut up!  That's just ridiculous, damn you!  I'm a man!
I don't give a damn if you can see them!
You're not kicking as high as you did earlier...  You are embarrassed, aren't you?
Look!
Don't measure it!
This means that your heart is astray.
There's no way!
Really?
H-H-Hey, cut it out!
As I thought, you have been deceiving your own heart!
Please be honest to yourself.
Well?  Aren't you going to kick me?
If you're not gonna attack, then I'll attack you instead!
TL Note: Newkama Kenpo Secret Technique
TL Note: A Maiden's Awakening
Why...  It's just some underwear...
but why am I so embarrassed about it?
W-What?  D-Did I just scream like a girl?!
T-T-That can't be...
But...  What is this strange feeling?
I don't get it!
I...
I think I'm...
...losing sight of who I really am!
Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan...
Are you doing well?
I can't wait to see you again.
When I do, I'm sure we'll become great friends.
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
This is the island where birds rule over man...
the Torino Kingdom in South Blue.
I want to leave this island as soon as possible.
This island is the worst.
The birds treat me like toys...
The people want to cook me in a stew and eat me...
And on top of that, the people and the birds...
are constantly fighting each other.
What should I do?
Here.  I've found some food for you.
How are your feet doing?
Have they gotten any better?
Let me take a look.
Stay still, ok?
They've already healed up!
Well, go ahead and eat.
You were really lucky.
I had found plenty of medical herbs...
This will work nicely against stomach-ache...
What was that?!
Are the humans trying to catch me again?!
Oh, crap!  They'll put me in a stew!
A bird chick...?
Did he fall from his nest?
He's still a baby so I can't understand what he's saying, but...
he looks like he's in pain...
He's injured?
Well, he fell from all the way up there, so I'm not surprised.
Don't move, or your injuries will get worse.
Calm down.
I'm a doctor!
You sure eat a lot...
I'm worn out just finding food for you.
But I'm sure you'll grow up and be able to fly someday.
And then, you can return to your nest.
I know!
When you're big enough to fly, will you let me ride you to the Sabaody Archipelago?
Luffy!
Guys!
Yes!  Now I can join Luffy and the others again!
That's a promise, okay?  Don't forget!
Hey...  Cut it out!  That tickles, you jerk!
Cut it out!
So you're treating me like a toy, too?
So warm...
We're finally back together, everyone...
I wasn't lonely at all...
Huh?  Where'd he go?
Oh, right.  Now that he can walk again, he probably went out to play...
WHAT?!
That's odd...  Looking at his footsteps,
he should be around here somewhere...
Me hungry.
That raccoon dog we tried to make into raccoon dog stew should still be here somewhere...
Not raccoon dog, reindeer.
When we catch it again, we make into reindeer stew.
T-This is bad!  Really bad!
It's you!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Not here.
Why not we look somewhere else?
Yeah, we do that.
They didn't see us.
Did you get lost?
Looks like you're fine now.
But you've gotta be quiet.  Otherwise, they'll find us.
Wait!  Be quiet!
Oh, crap!
There it is!  Over there!
Bird is there too!
Today we have feast!
Bird stew and reindeer stew!
Oh, no!
There's nowhere to run!
You surrounded.
We tired of chasing you.
Birds attacking.
Kill!
Did you come here to save us?
I took care of your baby...
but you don't need to thank me, you jerk!
So it's still like this, huh?!
They're fighting again, huh?
So he was that bird's baby...
Aren't you happy?
Hey!  Don't forget!
When you've grown up and learned to fly,
you'll take me to the Sabaody Archipelago, right?!
I'm counting on you!
But when'll that happen?
I CAN'T WAIT THAT LONG!
I hate this place!
Why do the people and birds on this island hate each other so much?!
Luffy!  Guys!  Save me!
Robin is imprisoned in Tequila Wolf.
The security is very tight but the little girl, Soran, disregards her own safety and thinks of a plan to save Robin.
In the meantime, Usopp eats like crazy, trying to catch up to the hero of the forest.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Crew's Whereabouts
The Revolutionary Army and Trap of the Forest of Gluttony!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!