It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has gone to Marineford...
where he's trying to save his brother Ace from execution.
An intense battle rages in the bay as the Navy tries to stop the Whitebeard Pirates...
as they advance on the execution platform.
On the shore, the Pacifista Army has begun a vicious attack on Whitebeard's allies.
Drop the charade already, Whitebeard!
You made a deal with the Navy, didn't you?!
A deal to ensure that Ace and your Whitebeard Pirates would get out of this alive!
You traded away the lives of the forty-three captains of your alliance...
in exchange for Ace's life!
You realize what you've done, don't you...
Squardo?
You've turned your blade against your own father...
You foolish son!
Though you're a fool, I still love you, my son.
So Squardo, try to get along.
Don't think that Ace is a special case.
You are all my family.
You really haven't changed, Sengoku.
You sure duped him.
Me, sell out my own sons' lives?!
So he's given the pirates an escape route...
I shouldn't have taken him so lightly.
If you're pirates, then decide for yourselves what to believe!
Those willing to come with me, follow me even if it costs you your lives!
Attack!  He's on the move!  The strongest man in the world!
Whitebeard... He's coming!
Do as the Old Man says!
Open a path for the Old Man!
Don't let them advance!
Fire!
Whitebeard...
Now raising the walls!
Hurry up!
Yes, Sir!
What's wrong?!
W-Well...
The ice is in the way!
Do something about it!
Yes, Sir!
What...
is the meaning of this?!
They said the Old Man sold us out for the lives of Ace and his own crew,
and that was supposed to be the end of it...
So then,
why is the Old Man...
still fighting to save us all?!
That's not right!
This isn't how it was supposed to be!
Squardo...
The Navy tricked him into going after the Old Man!
How stupid can you get?!
And how bad must he be feeling now?!
But then...
What...
have I done?!
I'm sorry, Old Man!
I'm sorry, Ace!
Squardo.
Are you gonna cry, or are you gonna make them pay?
You played us all for fools!
That old guy sure is amazing... Even with that wound...
But I've got to focus on Ace!
Luffy-kun!
Jinbei!
Look at that!
All our enemies have retreated to the plaza without us noticing!
I have a bad feeling about this...
But the Old Man has made his move!
This is no time to be second-guessing!
Indeed!  It's too late to stop now!
Still not ready?!
Sorry, Sir!  The ice is much stronger than we anticipated.
Fire!
You alright?
It's just a scratch.  Keep moving!
Charge!
The walls should be up by now...
This is bad!
I'll buy us some time!
Vice Admiral!
I won't let you reach the plaza, Whitebeard Pirates!
I-It's one of the Navy's Vice Admirals, John Giant!
You're in our way.
My balance...
Vice-Admiral!
Hey!  The ground is tilting!
Stay away from the Old Man!
This isn't just an earthquake!
Whitebeard!
That hurt...
The sea...
Unbelievable...
The whole island and the sea...
are being tilted!
What a crazy old geezer!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Luffy-kun!
Jinbei!
I've got you now!
You saved me... Thanks!
You needn't thank me.
Can't that guy tell his allies from his enemies?
His crewmates knew to take refuge by the flanks.
Are you alright?
Ow... Is the world ending or something?
You're kidding me!
So this is how the world's strongest pirate fights...
What awesome power...
But the Navy's Absolute Justice is at stake...
I can't let you pass!
It's not stopping!
It's gonna reach the execution platform!
Go!  Tear it apart!
Hey... Is the execution platform still standing?
Did it work?
It didn't hit the execution platform?!
Why did it veer off?
T-That's...
The Three Admirals!
This happened because they didn't raise the walls in time.
Because your ice is in the way!
Why don't you just melt it, Sakazuki?
Damn it... They managed to deflect the Old Man's attack!
Don't falter, men!
Commander Jozu!
Let's break through, before the Navy carries out whatever plan they've got!
Take advantage of what the Old Man's done here!
Let's go, Whitebeard Pirates!
Charge!
They all seem pretty fired up...
Scary!
What happened to the walls?
Sir, it's...
I don't care if we shut down the city's whole electric grid.
Use all the power we have to mobilize those walls!
Yes, Sir!  Right away!
Ace!
Luffy!
I'm coming now!
Ace!
Power input, maximum!
W-What?!
W-Walls?!
We're surrounded!
What is this?!
Dammit!
Did I get it?
It's hopeless!  It won't budge!
It must be incredibly dense steel!
So the walls they were talking about earlier were these enormous defensive walls?!
Dammit!  So you're not gonna fight us then, Navy?!
Hey, look at that!
All the cannons are pointed at us!
Run!
We're surrounded!  Where are we supposed to...
There's an opening!
Hey!  What's going on?!
Raise all of the walls!
Well... The walls can't handle the massive weight of Oars' body!
And it looks like his blood leaked into the system and damaged it!
Seriously?  Damn demon!
Oars... You...
What an incredible guy!
He's still fighting... even now.
Admirable!
They may not be closed in...
but proceed with the operation, Akainu!
The lava's shooting into the sky...
W-What is he doing?!
They've disappeared in the clouds...
What's that sound?
What's going on?!
We're not letting you escape!
Melt the ice and take away their footing!
The Whitebeard Pirates are trapped in the bay.
Through the Navy's concentrated bombardment,
they use the path over Oars' body to break into the plaza,
just as the order to execute Ace is finally given!
How will Luffy react?
Next time, on One Piece:
The Execution Order is Given
Break Through the Walls!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!