Translations, Vegard Aune
Timing, SockPain
Typesetting, DeSi, SockPain
Editing, mithrandiryod
Encoding, SockPain
Song Translation, Vegard Aune
Karaoke AFX, jaga01
QCing, mithrandiryod and Vegard Aune
Wealth.
Fame.
Power.
The man who once owned everything,
The Pirate King,
Gold Roger.
The words he said before his death,
Sent all the people of the world...
Out to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, I'll give it to you!
Find it!
I left everything in that place.
Men, searching for romance,
Pushed forward towards the Grand Line.
The world is now...
In the Grand Age of Pirates!
As Luffy and the others continued their journey towards their next destination, Fishman Island,
They reached the halfway point of the Grand Line.
Chopper!
Coup De Burst!
I can't see the top! It's huge!
They had finally made it to the Red Line.
There, they encountered Caimie the mermaid and Pappagg the starfish.
Thank you so much for saving me!
Caimie, you're still alright?
Caimie asked them to save her captured friend, Hacchin...
and so the crew set their course for the base of the Flying Fish Riders.
What? What's wrong?
They're here! The Flying Fish Riders!
Hey, did you see that?!
I saw it! No doubt about it, it's the Straw Hat Pirates!
I'm sick of waiting... I really was sick of waiting! That pirate ship is the one I've been waiting for!
I'll kill him! That man who screwed up my life!
The Fated Reunion!
Save the Imprisoned Fishman
The Flying Fish just... left?
Even though they were really on the attack back there...
It seemed like they recieved some kind of message.
Maybe they were ordered to retreat? Although I wouldn't know why...
I wanna ride those! Those Flying Fish can stay in the air for five minutes, huh? Awesome!
Anyway, the place we're headed now is their base, right?
In that case, we'd better be prepared to fight them again.
But who'd have guessed that they'd come at us from the sky?
How about getting the cannons out on the deck? I'll shoot them all down!
Nice going!
I wonder if Hacchin is alright...
You know, Macro is really after you! You've gotta be careful too!
I guess you're right...
Duval-sama! The three of them have returned!
Duval-sama, why'd you order us to pull back?
I'd like to know that too. You could have just left the capture of the mermaid and the pirates to us!
You idiots!
Do you guys....
...have any idea how long I've been anticipating...
...the arrival of...
Duval
those pirates?!
Whenever I think of dat man...
This huge, great scar on my back starts throbbin' like Hell!
Oh, crap! The Head's mad!
Ev'ry single day... I've cursed dat man's name ev'ry single day!
Head, please calm down!
I'm gonna kill dat guy right here, today! Got it?!
Dat's my life-long, immortal wish!
DO YA UNDERSTAND?!
Yes! That guy can't be allowed to live!
And dat's why ya gotta make sure to do this properly! Dat's how we'll get'im!
You punks just follow my orders exac'ly!
Yes, Head!
Hey, Macro-crew!
Huh? You called?
What is it, Duva?
"Duva"?" Whaddaya mean, Gyaro?! And what's with the "Huh", Tansui?!
Ya guys should learn some better manners!
Gyaro                                                          Tansui                                                                                                                                                                              Macro
Heh, "Duva", that's funny!
Geez! Oh, you called, Master Duval?!
Boss... This guy's totally freaked out...
Oh, shut up!
Ahhh, I apologise profusely, Master... These guys are complete idiots, they don't even know what they're sayin'!
Oh, it's fine, you guys. To me, you're like my angels of good fortune. I can't even say how thankful I am to you.
Go on.
I told you to shut up, Tansui!
Thanks to you guys... At last... at last... I can meet them! The Straw Hat... pirates!
Straw Hats? Who're they?
The Straw Hats? Then, it wasn't just my imagination?
Listen up... Dat guy... dat guy I bin waitin' all my life ter kill is on dat boat, a'ight?! I ain't never gonna forgive dat punk!!!
Head! Calm down, please!
He really does hate that guy, huh?
I never thought I'd hear the name "The Straw Hat Pirates" here...
Hey, you, the big guy!
It's Duval-sama! Show some manners, you damn octopus!
Are you saying that Caimie has been captured by the Straw Hat Pirates?!
This is bad... Of all the people to run into...
Are they coming here as well?
Yeah, they're heading here right now. But ain't it your mermaid friend who's turned to the pirates for help?
I dunno the details, but it doesn't seem like she's been caught.
Well, no matter who she brings with her, as long as we're here, we'll just catch'em all and sell them to the Human Shop!
As if they could do that! Those guys are terrifyingly strong!
This is a problem... I wonder if Nami's there too...
I wonder if she's still mad at me...
Well, of course she would be...
I did those horrible things to her when I was with Arlong, and all...
If I don't hurry up and escape before those guys get here, they'll definitely beat me up, too... I'm in trouble!
That's...Duval-sama! The Straw Hats are here!
So, they're finally here?
Say, Macro...
Huh? What is it?
I'll give you lots of takoyaki, so could you please let me go?
Yeah, right! Dumbass! What kinda glutton do you take me for?!
Is that man on the ship?
Yes! He's definitely there!
It's about time for you to pay the piper, an' all! Prepare yourself!
Hey, Gyaro! I'll give you lots of takoyaki, so please let me go!
Like I said, who'd fall for such a stupid... Hey!
You'd seriously do it?!
Get to work, you maggots!
Hey, Tansui! I'll give you... Huh?
Shaddup you! Just get over here!
Huh? I can see something now!
Looks like that's the Flying Fish Riders' base.
And this Hacchin-guy is being kept over there?
Hacchin...
Hey, let's hurry up and go save the takoyaki!
We got it already! Just wait a minute!
I'll go in there and save him in a flash, Caimie-chwan~!
Thanks a lot, Sanji-chin!
Oh! But everyone! Please be careful!
The Macro Crew alone have captured me about 30 times!
You get captured too much!
You get eaten too much, too.
Seems like we've entered their territory, huh?
I'm getting that old "I shouldn't get on this island-disease" again...
This isn't really an island, though. It seems like someone built a village on top of the water.
It's the "I shouldn't enter this village that someone built on top of the water-disease"!
But why would they want to set up their base here?
Who knows...
Anyway, it sure is quiet here.
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Luffy! Should we really...
FORWARD!
Hey, shouldn't we at least think over the plan for a second?!
HEY~! HACCHIN! ARE YOU ALRIGHT?!
GET OUT HERE, MACRO! GIVE HACHI BACK!
Oh, damn! It really is the Straw Hats' ship!
Damn it!
I really can't get out... Well, in that case...!
Octo-Hachi Black!
It seems like someone is inside that cage.
Who's that black guy?
Huh?! Move over...
Could that be Hacchin...?
This is great, Caimie! There aren't even any enemies around! They must all be off having a snack!
Seems like it.
Are you guys even serious?! Anyone could tell that this is a trap!
Everyone is obviously hiding in there, waiting to ambush us.
WHAT BRILLIANT DEDUCTION!
I NEVER WOULD HAVE CONSIDERED THAT!
THAT'S WHY YOU KEEP GETTING CAUGHT!
I'm here! Caimie, I'm okay, so you don't have to worry!
Hacchin, it really is you!
YOU'RE ALL BLACK! WHAT HAPPENED?!'
Well, this is kinda my own fault... Anyway, this is a trap, so hurry up and turn back!
You know that I'm strong, right? So it's fine, just go!
That voice is really familiar, and then there's that unusual silhouette... Hey, Nami, what do you think?
There's something very suspicious about him...
What?
We'll know if we ask him, right?
Hey! Is Arlong doing alright?!
Huh? Arlong? No, him, Choo, Kuroobi and everyone else got caught by the Navy.
I was the only one who escaped, and I'm now living out my old dream of running a takoyaki-stand.
Arlong...?
I knew it...
SO IT WAS YOU, HUH, YOU DAMN SQUID?!
DAMN IT!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
D... damn it...!
So you're that damn squid who was with Arlong?! You're that takoyaki-seller, Hacchin?!
What?
Well, it was a while ago now...
But Nami's hometown was once under the control of a nasty crew of fishmen called the Arlong Pirates...
Nami was in quite a terrible situation herself... And that octopus was one of the top-members.
Nami, you're planning on running away, huh?
Well, if you do, everyone from Cocoyashi village will have to die for it, you know!
Which one's Arlong?
Ah, so he's an old enemy, huh?
Of course, I took Luffy and the others along, and kicked the crap out of the whole crew!
Usopp, you're awesome!
Y... yeah, I guess...
I thought all the fishmen were arrested by the Navy... but it seems like that guy managed to get away...
I see. You have experienced quite a lot...
HEY, SQUID! Now that we know it's you, there's no way we'll save you!
B... but...
I... is...
Is your takoyaki really as good as I heard it was?!
Oh, come on! Getting caught between your appetite and your reason?
How stupid.
You mean, you know Hacchin? Is Hacchin an old friend of yours?
HE'S NOT OUR FRIEND!!!
Turn the ship around!
Nami-chin...
Sorry, Caimie... We never would have thought your friend was that guy...
No way... Then, you won't help me save him after all? Hacchin!
Caimie! That's okay! Just turn back! This is a trap!
No... I'll save you... Hacchin, you're always saving us, after all! Pappagg!
That's right! I never thought you guys would be such a load of unfeeling halfwits! Idiots! Idiots!
Shut up!
Wait for us, Hachi!
We definitely won't abandon you, Hacchin!
Here we go!
Caimie-chan!
That idiot!
Are they gonna be alright?
I'm sure they wouldn't just jump in like that... They should have some sort of plan...
We've got you now, Caimie!
Oh, come on, that's just pathetic!
Now, we're gonna be rich!
With Hachi, who always saves you, in that state and all!
You won't get away, Caimie!
That's why I told you to run! Caimie! Pappagg!
Why, you... Caimie hasn't done anything!
Wait, Sanji-kun!
I'll save you right now, Caimie!
Fine, let's save Hachi as well.
Hachi isn't that bad. Actually, he's harmless! And we promised Caimie, too.
N... Nami-swan... That firm, determined appearance is just wonderful!
Hey, Nami...
Is that really fine?
Luffy!
If you say so, then I guess there's no choice. Let's save the octopus as well.
Your eyes turned into takoyaki!
Are the preparations ready...
...Flying Fish Riders?
Of course, we're always prepared!
Gum Gum...
...Pistol!
Wait a minute!
He's a Devil Fruit User?!
Straw Hat?
Damn him!
Luffy-chin!
You...
Alright! I got them back!
Straw Hat! Thank you so much! I'm indebted to you!
Zoro! Cut the octopus' ropes and the cage!
Sure!
Straw Hat! Be careful! You've already sprung the trap! The Flying Fish Riders have you surrounded!
Charge!
Yes sir!
Luffy-chin...
Whether it's from the sea, or the sky, we're ready for'em!
We're gonna beat'em all!
YOU GUYS!
PREPARE FOR BATTLE!
YEAH!!!
Damn it... Now, while we have the chance, let's take Caimie back!
Caimie! Pappagg! It's dangerous, so stand back!
Get them~! Go, Luffy-chin!
Now, come, Flying Fish!
~Get them, get them, go, go!~
They're here!
Right!
I've found you, Black Leg Sanji!
Does he know Sanji?
It's your fault that my life was ruined!
He really hates him, huh?
Fall into Hell!
What did you do, Sanji?
Next time, on One Piece:
Tragedy!
The Truth of the Unmasked Duval
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Tragedy!
The Truth of the Unmasked Duval