It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
The curtain has fallen on the great war of Marineford, which will be engraved forever in history.
Ten years earlier, in East Blue...
The seven-year-old Luffy met Ace for the first time.
I won't tell you!
Die.
Stop it!
Move it!
That's him, Porchemy-san!
He's the one who stole our money!  Dammit!
What?!
A-Ace!
Showing up on your own makes this much easier!
I didn't know what to do, your pal was so tight-lipped!
Ace!
L-Let me go...
Sabo!
Porchemy-san!
Ace... Sabo...
That hurt pretty bad, you know.
You know what happens when you make fun of grown-ups, don't you?!
Your opponent is right here!
Sabo!  Help Luffy!
Ace!
The guy has a sword! Be careful!
My knife!
Porchemy-san!  The kid!
Let's get out of here, Ace!
You go on ahead!
You idiot!  C'mon!
Once I've chosen an opponent...
I won't run!
What?!  You brat!
Don't!  He's on a completely different level than the delinquents in town!
Don't you get it?
Hey, playtime ends now!
You stole our money!  You will obediently return it to us, you insolent brat!
I'm sure you realize that you've done a bad thing.
I won't hurt you if you give the money back.
We're gonna make much better use of it!
Wh-
What did you say?!
You... wait just a minute!
You're being too reckless!  Why are you always doing this?!
I never back down!
Don't be ridiculous!
If I lose to a pair of kids, I'll quit being a pirate!
Then we'll make you quit!
I'm gonna slaughter you!
I heard what happened, Porchemy.
How pathetic!
You really lost...
to a pair of kids?
I'm so sorry, Captain Bluejam...
The money...
Don't look at me. I don't want to see your face.
So, who's going to get my money back?
You're not gonna let them get away with this, right?
Of course not.  We'll get it back immediately.
That's a real bad habit you got, Ace...
Refusing to run when you're up against real pirates.
Why are you so eager to die?
This doesn't feel quite right... It was better before.
After this, Bluejam's crew will never forgive us.
They'll be after us from now on.
That was so scary!  I thought I was gonna die!
You're so annoying!  Shut up!  How long're you gonna keep crying?!
I really hate weaklings and crybabies!
Thank you...
For...
For saving me...
Why, you...
Come on, now... He's just thanking us.
Anyway, why didn't you tell them?!
Those guys would kill women and children without a second thought!
If I'd told them...
I could never be your friend.
That'd be better than dying, right?
Why do you want to be my friend so much, anyway?
Because...
After all the stuff I put you through...
Why did you still follow me out here?!
Because...
Because there isn't anybody else!
I can't return to Windmill Village,
and I hate those mountain bandits...
If I didn't chase after you, I'd be all alone!
Being alone is much worse than getting hurt!
What about your parents?
Just Granddad, nobody else.
It isn't so bad when I'm here?
Right.
And it'd be bad if I wasn't here?
If Roger had a kid?
It'd be real bad if he had one!
He'd be a demon who wouldn't deserve to be born, or to live!
You want me to live?
Of course I do!
I see.
But still, I hate spoiled kids like you.
I'm not spoiled!  I'm strong!
Strong?  How are you strong?!
You're supposed to be a man but you keep crying all the time!
Have you ever been punched with a spiked glove?!
I'm only seven!  I won't cry when I become a ten-year-old like you!
I'll be much stronger!
I didn't cry when I was seven either.
You idiot!  Don't compare yourself to me!
I'm gonna be stronger than anyone else!
I promised Shanks that I'd become a great pirate!
A pirate?!  You?!
That's right!
As if!
I'm gonna be one!
Okay, that's enough.
Oh, by the way, I've got a problem here.
A problem?
Because of what happened today, Bluejam's crew will be trying to find and kill all three of us, right?
Yeah, I guess.
I've been living in this forest but it's close to their base, the Pirates' Cove.
What do you think would happen if I fell asleep somewhere and they attacked me?
You'd die.
You'd definitely die.
Indeed.
So I've gotta ask you something.
Hear me out.
What's with their injuries?
They're covered in bandages!
Hey, what's this?
Boss!  Boss!  This is unbelievable!
Why're you so noisy so early in the morning?
What the hell is this?!
One, two...
One...
Two...
Ace... Luffy...
Ace!  Luffy!  Who is that?!
Who's who?
You're so noisy this morning... Do you know what time it is?
Why's there suddenly a third kid here?
Who are you?!
Who, me?
I'm Sabo!
Hi!  You're Dadan, right?
Sabo?  I've heard that name before.
Really?  That makes it easier for me, then.
Let's try to get along starting today!
Get along?  Don't tell me you think you're staying here?
Don't answer with a fart!
You gotta be kidding me!  If you're the Sabo I heard about,
then you're supposed to be one hell of a little brat!
Really?  And I heard that you're an old hag!
You really shouldn't say things like that!
I don't want to deal with any more unruly kids!
But you're a nice old hag who can't turn down any requests from other people too, right?
I heard that you're an old hag who's like a man among men!
"A man among men"... I'm a woman!
Can't you tell?!
Ace!  Luffy!  Sabo!
Since you're all under my care, you'd better hurry and get to work!
Thanks, Dadan!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Then, we're off!
Hey, Luffy!  You're supposed to do the laundry and clean the house!
No way!
Ah!  Ace, Sabo, wait!
Sheesh, what an annoying bunch of kids!
Oh, right...
I forgot to say...
Hey, Dadan!  While we're out, Bluejam's crew might come around.
So be careful!
Bluejam might be coming...
Why?
We got mixed up with one of their crew, and beat him up!
See ya later!
Dadan sure is an understanding old hag.
But she's still an old hag.
True!  She's a bandit, after all.  And her face is scary!
So, what now?
First off...
Food!
Alright, let's get some food!
Luffy, you're a Devil Fruit user?
Yup.
That explains why you can't swim.
Here, you have some too.
Thanks!
You're too soft, Sabo.
It's no big deal.
So, which fruit did you eat?
The Gomu Gomu fruit!
Gomu Gomu?  You're made of rubber?
Yeah, that's right.
So you became unable to swim in exchange for being a rubber man?
That's stupid.
It's not stupid!
I've got bunches of unbeatable techniques!
Oh, is that right?
A guy who can't even catch a fish shouldn't talk like that.
You really are made of rubber, huh?  That's cool!
Don't play with me like that!
Still, rubber can stretch, shrink and expand...
It might be pretty useful in a fight.
I know, right?
Oh, hey!  I thought up a new technique yesterday!
Fuusen: Balloon
It's called Gomu Gomu no Fuusen!   It can deflect anything, even cannonballs!
Really?  Show me!
Alright!  But this is a special show!
I won't show you, Ace.  So don't watch!
Here I go...
What?  What's this?  It's incredible!
He keeps growing bigger and bigger!
What do you think?  Amazing, right?
No... I can't tell if it's amazing or not...
Some exercise will help me digest my food!
What're you doing?!
Sabo!  Kick him back!
Uh, sure.
Cut it out!
This is supposed to be an invincible technique to deflect cannonballs?
Stop already!
Then try to deflect my kicks!
Stop!
Wait up, you!  We won't let you just eat him and run away!
You bastard!
Here we go!
Well, you know...
Don't be mad.
Of course I'm mad!  I was almost eaten!
Oh, shut up.  You can eat as much as you want when we eat this crocodile for dinner.
Ok, I forgive you.
You're just gonna forgive us?
I wanna eat that crocodile now...
I can't wait until dinner!
Ace.  There's something I wanna check on.
Come with me.
So?  Did you find it?
Look closer!
Good thing we moved our Pirate Fund...
Yeah...
Wanna go take a look around the Gray Terminal?
Yeah, I guess.
You should go back to Dadan's place first.
No!
Telling him to do that is pointless...
The place is swarming with delinquents from town and Bluejam's crew...
This is serious.
Bluejam must've gotten really mad.
Hey, guys!  Somebody here is looking for you.
I see them!  Over there!
Wait!  You won't escape!
Looks like they've even gotten the guys from the Terminal helping them...
Guess it's better if we just lay low for a while,
at least until things calm down.
It doesn't matter.  If we run into them, we can just fight.
Well, sure, we could...
but there's no point in picking a fight.
I agree with Sabo!
You just shut up.
Bluejam, huh?  They started a fight with one hell of a guy...
Knowing him, he'll definitely find out where we are and come straight here!
And there's no way we can beat them in a fair fight.
It looks like the Dadan Family is done for...
We'll have to say goodbye to our humble, fun life as bandits...
We'll be lucky if the Family only falls apart...
Worst case scenario, we might all get massacred.
Quit spouting pathetic crap like "we can't win" and "we have to disband"!
Don't you have any pride as bandits?!
It's simple.
If they come here...
we'll just hand Ace and the others over to them.
But boss... What are we gonna tell Garp afterward?
Besides, Bluejam isn't the type of guy who'd be satisfied even if we handed them over.
Then...
Then?
Then we'll just have to feign ignorance!
Alright, we'll give it a try!  Let's practice!
"You've got Ace and Sabo here, right?
Tell me where they are!"
N-No idea...
No way... That sucked.
Boss!  Boss!  Ace and the others have returned!
After they got chased out of the Gray Terminal, Ace's friend Sabo moved in with them.
Ace.  Sabo.  Luffy.
Before long, these three spent all their time in the jungle and on the mountain paths fighting beasts,
as well as the delinquents from town and even the pirates from the Cove.
Their reputation soon reached all the way into the center of the kingdom.
A meeting within the kingdom greatly changes the destinies of Luffy and the others!
Next time, on One Piece:
Someday, We'll Cast off to Sea!
The Three Pranksters' Toast of Brotherhood!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!