Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Two years have passed since the great war at Marineford.
Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates have all been training on their own,
and now they return to the Sabaody Archipelago in order to move on to the next stage - The New World.
Huh, what's up?  Everyone suddenly got so tense.
But Rayleigh!
Luffy, the most important one, isn't here yet!
It'll be alright.
Captain!
Is this the guy you were looking for?
Luffy has already arrived at the archipelago.
I gave Sanji a Baby Snail Phone when he was here earlier.
He's with Zoro right now.
That's it, I'm gonna kill you!
Using these legs, which I've trained for two years in hell!
Bring it on!  I'll cut you in half!
Really?  That's good.
You have to hurry, the Navy is almost here.
Monkey-chan is the only one
we can't get in touch with, huh?
Anyway, I'll give the Vivre Card to you.
He'll be following this, I'm sure.
Grove 42 should do since it's by the coast.
Take the ship there and gather your crew.
I'm sure you've all been busy,
but now you've all made it through these two years...
and it's time to set sail again!
Read this carefully before you set sail.
It has all the details on how to operate a coated ship.
Got it.  Thanks!
I wonder how much Luffy has changed in the past two years?
I can't wait to meet him!
I agree.
Alright, let's get going!  To Grove 42!
Oh, wait, I have to contact Zoro and Sanji first.
Still...
I hope Luffy doesn't get himself into trouble.
True.  This is Luffy, after all.
I'd be surprised if we actually
set sail without any problems.
Leave it to me!
I'll go get him!  I have a great idea.
Listen up, you lot!
Anyone who gets in our way will be arrested!
What are you doing, Navy?!
Don't get in the way of the Soul King!
Hey, what happened?!  What's going on over there?!
It's total chaos!
The Navy broke into the Soul King's concert but the fans won't get out of the way.
Now it looks like he's fled in the confusion!
Damn that traitor!
Oh, I have big news!  The musician Brook was a companion of Straw Hat Luffy...
He was a pirate!
I truly appreciate this.  Your timing was perfect.
It was an order from Big Sis Shakki!
Your crewmates are waiting in Grove 42!
How nostalgic... My chest is swelling in anticipation.
Ah!  Though I do not have a chest to swell.
What's with these guys?
No human could have that kind of strength!
You seem to have gotten a little better,
third-rate swordsman.
You taught yourself a bunch of new kicking techniques...
But you've neglected your cooking skills, haven't you, you pathetic cook?!
The hell did you just say?!
So that's the situation.  The Navy's on the move
and Luffy's on the archipelago.
We're moving the Sunny to Grove 42,
so both of you hurry over!
Roger that.
What was that?
Huh, you didn't hear?
Let's see...
Navy.  Coming.  We.  Ship.  Run.
Understand?
Of course I understand!
Why're you using one-word sentences?!  Speak normally!
I figured it would be easier for
a muscle-brain like you to understand.
Huh?!
Okay... You.  Later.  Kill!
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, it sure is noisy over there.  Don't you think?
You're right.
There.  Noisy.
What's all this?
Quiet down, you lot!
We've already found...
one of the people who disrespected me!
It's this guy!
Now it's time to teach him a lesson...
about how terrifying I can be!
Furthermore, let the punishment he is about to receive...
serve as a warning to you, my followers,
should you ever decide to defy or betray me!
Is that clear?!
Yeah!
A man worth 400 million sure is intimidating.
Who's this guy?  Zoro, Sanji, is he a friend of yours?
Huh?
You see, earlier-
This is the end for you, pirates!
Straw Hat Luffy and his underlings!
We demand that you surrender quietly!
Huh, the Navy?!
All the exits from Grove 46 have been sealed off!
There's nowhere for you to run!
How'd the Navy know I was here?
Huh?  What are you talking about?
Captain!  We're surrounded by marines!
You dumbass, don't let this freak you out!
Why do you think we gathered companions?
Some of our underlings
are worth more than 100 million!
But there are so many.
Just watch, you idiot!
Hey, Caribou!
Use that marine you captured as a shield
and force them to clear a path!
A marine?!
Apparently they captured one of our scouts!
Damn, this is not good...
Huh?!  What was that, Boss?!
I told you to use that marine as a shield,
you dumbass!
I get it.  Use that guy as a shield, huh?
What are you doing, Caribou?!  Use him
as a shield so we can get away from here!
Sorry Boss, no can do.
Because this marine here...
He lied to me when he said
he didn't call for reinforcements!
Stop it, you fool!
T-That crazy guy ignored my orders-
the Captain's orders!
Aah... He killed'im.
You guys have an unwritten rule that it's alright to lie to villains...
Something has to be done about that!
Looks like they have no intention of surrendering!
Kill the pirates!
You idiots!  Our boss is the 400 million man,
Straw Hat Luffy!
Counter attack!
This is bad, Captain!  Let's flee!
Fools!  Don't attack without my orders!
Why are those guys calling me their boss?
Again, what are you talking about?!
Don't be afraid!  Get them!
You're...
Lip Service Doughty, wanted for 88 million!
Your swordsmanship is impressive.
Don't be afraid!  Take aim!
He's the 92 million man...
Albion the Gashed!
Don't be afraid!  Justice is on our side!
Right!
I do hate the smell of the blood of hypocrites.
Pirate Wet-Hair Caribou, wanted for 210 million!
Huh?
Surrender!
D-Don't tell me you ate a Devil Fruit?!
Please stop struggling.
Straining yourself like that is bad for your health, you know?
My sword...
This might work, Captain!  These guys are strong!
You got that right.
Hey, men!
The one who kills the most marines during this battle
will become my right-hand man!
Wipe them out!
Right!
Right-hand man?!
What about us?!
You two shouldn't just stand around either.
With all these troops at my command, I can rule the world!
What is it now?!
Pacifista!
What?!
What are the Navy's human weapons doing here?!
It's those guys who look like bears!
Even though Hancock told me to not cause a scene...
Will you quit spouting nonsense, already?!
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy has been identified.
The Pacifista?!  For real?!
Am I their target?!
The Pacifista, eh?  Interesting!
Lip Service Doughty, the man with the
88 million beli bounty, has been taken out.
Captain Doughty!
Follow the Pacifista!  Capture the pirates!
Yeah!
They got him with a single hit!
How can a man worth more than
80 million be completely helpless?!
This is not good!
Captain, where are you going?!
Hey!
You fool!  I won't fight anyone who can crush Doughty like that!
We're getting out of here!
Boss Straw Hat, please do something!
At this rate, those human weapons will wipe us out!
Boss!
Huh?
The boss is gone!
"Boss"?
Are they talking about Straw Hat?
W-Wait up, my stomach hurts!
Fool!  Run, or you'll get killed!
Get out of my way, you twat-
Huh?  Who're you?
That's...
Boss!
This'll be interesting to watch!
Look at that, Coribou!
Right, Bro!
Wrong way, you imbecile!
I'm sorry!  So sorry!
Take him out, Boss Luffy!
Show him the strength of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
H-Hey, you!  You know who I am, don't you?!
Get out of the way, unless you want to get killed
and have your innards ripped out!
Listen, and be amazed!
I am the son of Dragon the Revolutionary.
The grandson of Garp the Hero.
The one who wreaked havoc during the great war!
The great pirate with a bounty of 400 million.
St-
Straw Hat was not a piece of trash like you!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
H-Hey, you!  You know who I am, don't you?!
Get out of the way, unless you want to get killed
and have your innards ripped out!
Listen, and be amazed!
I am the son of Dragon the Revolutionary.
The grandson of Garp the Hero.
The one who wreaked havoc during the great war!
The great pirate with a bounty of 400 million.
St-
Straw Hat was not a piece of trash like you!
What?!
Boss... Straw Hat!
I get it.  All these guys were tricked into joining a fake Straw Hat Crew.
PX-5.  Who is this guy?
The pirate Triple-Tongued Demalo Black.
Bounty: 26 million beli.
26 million?!
Which means, this guy is...
a fake?!
We've been busted!  Let's scram!
What the hell is with this brat?!
He used Straw Hat Luffy's name and tricked us?!
He took advantage of the fact that
the real one is dead!
Dammit!  I can't believe I let some
26 million weakling tell me what to do!
They were imitating me?
So Sanji and Zoro were fake too?
They looked just like the real ones!
Guess I'd better get out of here while I still have the chance.
He was a fool for trying to deceive me,
but you guys who fell for it are also out of luck!
We're taking all of you into custody!
And by some kind of crazy coincidence, the real Straw Hat is here too.
PX-5 locked on to him the moment we entered this area.
Target him now, PX-5!
That was close!
What're you doing?!  I've got a lot of valuable lunches
stored in this backpack, you know!
T-That's the same face...
as the one on the wanted posters!
That guy was the real Straw Hat!
Don't be taken aback!  We were prepared to fight the real one in the first place!
Right!
Straw Hat!
Huh?!  You're gonna get in my way again?!
She told me it'd be harder to set sail
if I caused a commotion.
Don't worry.  You're not going to set sail.
Things have changed these past two years.  I've officially become a marine now!
I will capture you right here!
PX-5!
Too slow.
What?!
That Straw Hat...
He coated his fist in Haki!
Haki: Aura of Dominance, Drive
He destroyed the Pacifista with a single punch?!
See ya later.
I'm sure I'll be seeing you again.
Wait, Straw Hat!
Don't let Straw Hat get away!
Right!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy!  This was you after all!
How can you already be in trouble?
There's no mistaking it this time!  I really missed you guys!
Roronoa!  Black Leg!  So they really are alive!
PX-7!
Move it!
I cut him down!
I broke his neck!
It's the Straw Hat Pirates!  The real ones!
They're nothing like the fakes!
Hey, Luffy, you're ninth.
Shut it, you!  Stop bragging!
Hurry up, Luffy!  Everyone's waiting at the ship!
Right!
Don't let Straw Hat and the others escape!  Capture them, if it's the last thing you do!
Yes, Sir!
It's been so long!
I wonder how everyone's doing?
I'm so happy!
Hey, what is it?
Rayleigh!
What?!
Could it be...
The Dark King, Rayleigh?!
I decided to come and have a look, but it seems you're doing just fine.
You've gotten even stronger since I last saw you.
Right!
Then hurry up and get going!  Back to your friends!
Rayleigh!  Thanks for everything these past two years!
This isn't like you.  Hurry up and go!
Rayleigh!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna be...
the Pirate King!
Luffy and the others prepare to set sail,
but the Navy appears and chases after them!
Next time, on One Piece:
Everyone Together
Luffy Sets Sail for the New World
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!