All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
After a fierce battle, the Straw Hat Pirates
have finally entered the New World,
the strongest sea, ruled by the Four Emperors.
After forming a pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally found Master Caesar Clown, who controls the island, but then...
You really underestimated me.
I hear you're one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea now.
How mighty you've become.
When'd you get here...
Vergo?!
This is important turf for Joker.
We cannot allow anyone to return alive
once they've figured out what's happening here.
Hey, Traf.  Who's this Joker?
A member of the World Government sanctioned Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Protect the Kids!
Master's Demonic Hand Approaches
Doflamingo...
Dunno who that is!
Didn't you meet him at Navy HQ?
At Navy HQ?
Oh, back then!
Hey now, Crocodile-man!
You're ditching me to team up with Whitebeard?
It's enough to make a guy jealous, ya know...
That bird-guy, huh?
You shouldn't take him lightly.
You can say that again.
Also, rumor has it
that after the showdown at Marineford...
he also attacked Moriah.
Moriah?
Ruins of Laboratories One and Two
- Nami and Usopp's Group -
Master!
So...
you're the one who kidnapped these kids?!
What's he doing here?
Did Luffy and the others go the wrong way?
You've done something terrible.
Terrible?
Why did you take them away?
Can't you see that the children are suffering?
What?!
Hey, don't be an idiot!  Cut it out, Nami!
And whose fault is it that they're suffering?!
Stop it!  Didn't Law say he was
a Logia user with a bounty of 300 million?
What drugs have you
been giving to these young children?
All of them really want to go home!
Their parents must be searching for them too!
We're definitely going to
take the children away from this place!
They don't look like they want to go home.
Master!
Hold on!
Hey, wait!
Don't go!  You don't want
to go back to the laboratory, do you?!
Get out of my way!
Usopp!
Candy.
Master... please give me candy...
That's right.  Come on home, children.
Please, stop!
You can't go to him!
Don't you want to go home?!
Don't touch me!
Cockroach!
Get away from me, cockroach!
Nami, are you alright?!
Y-Yeah.
Don't get cocky, you bastard!
No, Usopp!
Let go of me!  We've got to use force to stop them.  It's the only way!
They're hallucinating!  He just called you a cockroach!
But...
these children are victims!
They haven't done anything wrong!
Take these chains off me!
It hurts!
But if we don't do something...
these kids will kill us!
Then direct that anger...
at him!
Take them off!
Take these chains off me!
You've got to be kidding!
They broke their chains?!
Magnificent!  How strong you have become!
That little...
Candy.
Master.
Please...
Just you wait, damn gas bastard!
The most effective thing against gas would be...
Stay back, kids!
Were you expecting me to explode?
So you know that I have gas powers.
But you see,
I can extinguish fire before it touches me!
Poison gas isn't the only kind of gas there is.
Air itself is a gas as well.
So that means that I can control the air around me.
He can even...
control air?
Remove the oxygen and all flame dies out...
and you become unable to breathe!
Master?
Like so!
Usopp!
Thunder Cloud
Master.
C-Candy.
Candy.
Now!
Did I hear you say that
you think Straw Hat missed me?
As a matter of fact, we did meet!
I suffocated him and the other two!
Come on...
Candy!
Master!  Candy!
Now!
Master!
Gimme!  Gimme!
Children.  Only good kids
who return to the laboratory get candy.
Only... good kids?
That's right.
We'll be good!  We'll be good kids!
Then you can be patient for a little longer,
can you not?
Let's go back now!  Please, Master!
Very well, but first...
these demons took you away
and made your disease worse.
Exterminate them!
Exterminate.
Take those big pipes...
and smash their heads in!
Yes.
Stop... it.
Head... spinning...
Caesar!
Brownie!
His name is Brownbeard!
Straw Hat Pirates!
I see now!
Who are you again?
Oh, I remember!
My powerful subordinate, Brownbeard!
Did you forget that I even existed?!
Of course not!
What happened to you?
It looks like you were badly burned. It's painful just to look at you.
You were the one who ordered them to do this to me!
Of course... Now I remember!
Brownbeard?
You're on the hit list as well.
He's an idiot so he's easy to use,
but he has become a burden.
We don't need him anymore.
Kill him.
The Cool Brothers, am I right?
So that's why you were burned!
I trusted you!
You shouldn't be so upset.
You survived an attack from the Cool Brothers.
You're quite lucky, really!
Silence!
Caesar!
Children!  It's dangerous here!
Get aboard the gas balloon outside!
Let's get away from this place!
Wait!  Don't go with him!
Caesar!
The fact that you deceived me doesn't really matter.
I... don't care.
But you will return my crew to me!
I will not let them suffer the same fate that I did!
Huuuuh?!
Imbecile!  You have no crew!
All of them, including you,
belong to me now, remember?
How long are you gonna keep pretending that you're a captain?
You're the most pathetic pirate scum
in the New World!
Hey, Nami!  We've gotta chase after the kids.
Yes.
They will continue to obey me,
believing that I am their god of salvation!
They're just too stupid to realize...
that they're merely being kept alive
so I can use them as human guinea pigs!
You filth!
Brownbeard?!
What happened?!
Punk Hazard - Central Lake
It sure is persistent!
How long till we reach the lab?!
It looks like everything that was
on the far side of the lake is over here.
Meaning that this one is the final piece?
It's merging with the smaller ones?
It keeps growing bigger!
Anyway, we have to get to the lab!
Indeed!  I am coming, Momonosuke!
Open the door!
Give back Captain-chan!
Give back Smokey!
In Front of Caesar Clown's Laboratory
They're starting to move!
Not only that, they're all moving in the same direction!
Where are they going?
Caesar's Laboratory
I found out the chemical structure of the narcotic
and got ahold of some sedatives.
Now, I just need to figure out
a way to rescue Luffy and the others!
Carefully... Carefully...
W-Who was that?
Please give me candy.
Where did Master go?
Master.
Hey, where did Master go?
Caesar speaking.
Is Monet there?
Yes.
I have successfully retrieved the children.
Has Smiley's food been prepared?
All the preparations you ordered us to perform have been carried out, Master.
The Marines are outside the sealed gates,
the Straw Hats can be moved whenever you want,
and the Surveillance Snails are outside, ready to go.
So we can begin the live broadcast
of our fun experiment as soon as Smiley arrives?
Indeed.
Good.  Connect me to all receivers.
Understood.
Distinguished underworld brokers from all over the world...
Pardon the abruptness of this experiment,
but you are lucky to get to see this.
The gas weapon I am about to show you...
is even more effective
than the one from four years ago,
and it's an item that the trash
from the World Government could never produce.
Uninvited guests
wandered onto my island earlier today...
and I will be performing this experiment on them.
Conquest.  War.  Dominion.
This weapon has many possible uses.
If it is to your liking, shall we make a deal?
Are you interested
in this weapon of mass destruction?
Nah.
But... it can't hurt to see it in action.
Law and Caesar made a contract.
While the secret of that contract is revealed,
a large object appears before Zoro's group, who are being chased by Smiley.
This is the beginning of Caesar's terrifying plan!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Shock to the New World
Caesar's Nightmarish Experiment
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A Shock to the New World
Caesar's Nightmarish Experiment