Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
To defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law and invaded Dress Rosa,
but then Law was captured by Doflamingo.
Luffy has broken into the royal palace to free Law.
Sugar fainted!
All the workers we've gathered over the past ten years...
are reverting to humans!
The Hobby Hobby curse is being lifted!
Operation SOP is a success!
Who's that?!
Kyros!
All the toys used to be human.  They'd been erased from our memories!
Now that Sugar has been defeated, our memories have returned!
He is the former captain of the Riku Royal Army...
Kyros!
It's you!
Kyros?!
Yes!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting for ten years!
I'm here to save you!
I've come to restore the true Dress Rosa!
The Fire Fist Explodes!
The Power of the Mera Mera Fruit Reborn
Ten years.
We've had to endure your rule for ten years!
Doflamingo-sama!
Young master!
Damn you!
It's time for all your lies to be exposed!
Mingo died!
But I wanted to send him flying...
I see them!
Over there!  Damn you!
We've been spotted.
Fire!
Let's save Traf!
What is going on here?!
The toys in the Colosseum suddenly turned into humans and animals!
I couldn't possibly begin to describe what I'm seeing!
What's a gorilla doing in the spectators' seats?!
Run!
This is a disaster.
Trébol, you were supposed to keep an eye on Sugar!
You fool.
This is just insane!
Hey, you done crying yet?
I ain't your babysitter.
You don't understand...
I just remembered...
Mother, look at all the flowers I picked.
My!  Aren't they beautiful, Rebecca.
Would you like one?
Thank you, I think I'll take one.
This is from mother to you.
Would you like one?
Thank you for the meal.
You're welcome.  Eat up.
...someone very dear to me.
I'll go to the palace.
Scarlett, Rebecca, listen to me.
Father?
If the danger reaches here,
then wait for me at the red flower field.
I swear I'll come for you.
Father!
Father...
I...
I have a father!
What are you talking about?
That seems to have been this country's secret, Rebecca.
Everything has a core.
If you can just find that core, you can turn any situation around.
Now you're spouting confusing nonsense too, grand senpai?
The same goes for this arena.  It has a core.
How about we put an end to this match?
What the...
The arena is cracking apart!  Is this Lucy's doing?!
Dragon Claw Technique...
Dragon's Breath!
Amazing!  Lucy's attack is unbelievably powerful!
The arena is sinking!
The arena exploded!
I'm losing my footing!
What have you done?!
Something came up.  I'm going to win now.
Oh.
I heard a really loud noise from up there.
Hack?
Did he do something crazy again?!
He's on his way to the underground now.
The arena has been completely destroyed!
And is it just me, or is the water level sinking?!
I can't guarantee that the Colosseum is safe any longer!
Everyone, please evacuate as fast as you can!
We're being sucked in toward the center!
The floor beneath the arena must have cracked too.
The water's flowing underground!
I give up, I give up!
Watch what you're holding on to, you're gonna choke me!
This is nothing!
It's spirit!  All about spirit!
That's it!
I've found it!
That bastard!
Like hell!
The water...
My strength's...
Stop!
We weren't going to actually give that prize to anyone!
They're all outside the arena!  I win!
The one who gets the fruit wins, right?
The Mera Mera Fruit?!
I can eat it, right?
A winner!  We have a winner!
This might not be the best time...
but the one who managed to take advantage of the chaos to claim the Mera Mera Fruit...
is this tournament's ultimate dark horse, Lucy!
He has won!
Yuck!
Ah... can't hold on... any more...
Grand senpai... Save me too...
You're a man, right?  Save yourself!
I thought you'd say that.
Here comes another shot, so watch out!
What?!
Dammit, he ate the Mera Mera Fruit!
Isn't that the Revolutionary Army's...
Hot!  The flames really did appear!
I've got his clothes!
No wait, it's just my imagination.  It's not hot at all.
I've become fire!
Ace!
I'm using your technique!
You're...
Fire Fist!
Underground Trade Port
Curse you, Straw Hats and Tontattans!
How dare you knock out Sugar?!
How dare you free our workers?!
I'm not letting you out of here!
Usoland!
Are you alright?
Everyone, take care of Usopp.
Understood!
We're getting out of here!
Don't let them lay one finger on Usoland!
You're out to destroy the Smile factory.
Right, Nico Robin?
Beta Beta Chain!
Hold it!
A giant?!
Are you guys gnomes?  I'll be taking your friend for a bit.
U-Usoland!
You fought for us, until you were half dead.
All of you, behold!
From what I hear, there are people here who were toys for a decade.
I can't even imagine your suffering.
Ow.  Don't move me.
If it weren't for you, we would have remained toys forever.
We had been turned into slaves, and you saved our lives.
Have a good look, warriors!
This man...
is the hero who lifted the curse on us!
Didn't I tell ... you ... to cut it ... out?!
His name is...
Captain Usopp!
Thank you!
Usoland!
What's that?!
The ceiling is collapsing?!
A light from the heavens!
D-Don't tell me... this man...
is a servant of God?!
Are we... seeing...
a miracle?!
He's divine!  Truly a god!
Hey, listen close!  God Usopp is trying to say something!
I ... will ...
lead ... you ...
Huh?!  W-What did he say?!
I ... just want to rest, you bastard!
Will ... you just stop?
You're so annoying!
See my face ...
b ... leed ... ing all over.
You ... piece of shit!
"I will lead you"?
"I will lead you"!
You... really are...
our savior, sent from Heaven!
God Usopp!  God Usopp!  God Usopp!
Usoland!  Usoland!  Usoland!
Please guide us, God Usopp!
What must we do?!
Yeah!  This time, it's our turn to help you out!
We want to serve you!
Please guide us!
Show us the way!
Tell us what we must do!
Alright...  Then destroy that factory behind me...
and rescue my tiny friends.
As you wish!
Yeah!
Usopp...
Usoland!  Usoland!  Usoland!
What's... wrong with...
these guys?
The Fire Fist has been reborn at last!
The mysterious Lucy, inheritor of Ace's powers, descends into the darkness of Dress Rosa.
When his shocking true identity is revealed, the three brothers' story begins a new chapter!
Next time, on One Piece:
A Dashing Entrance
Revolutionary Army Chief of Staff, Sabo!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
A Dashing Entrance
Revolutionary Army Chief of Staff, Sabo!