It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has come to Marineford...
to save his brother Ace, who is about to be executed.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates were headed towards the execution platform.
However, they have been trapped inside the bay by large defensive walls.
With Jinbe's help, Luffy breached the walls...
and has finally made it to the plaza.
Luffy!
Here I come!
Ace!
What's happening?!
We're surrounded!
What is this?!
Proceed with the operation, Akainu!
The magma is shooting into the sky...
We're not letting you escape!
Melt the ice and take away their footing!
Forgive me.
The plan is progressing smoothly.
The execution of Portgas D. Ace... will proceed...
immediately!
Jinbe!
I've got...
a favor to ask!
Oh, my.  You finally made it here.
Quite an entrance, son of Dragon.
This youngster sure is scary...
Give Ace...
back!
He's attacking the Three Admirals head-on!
He's clearly an idiot!
He'll be killed for sure!
I don't have time to fight these guys!
How cunning of him.
Too slow.
Luffy-san!
What did I tell you...
Damn it!
On my mark!
Yes sir!
Do it!
Ace!
Ace-san!
Ace!!
Who did this?!
Bastard!
Considering your old grudge against Whitebeard, I had thought we were lucky...
Crocodile!
Him!
Huh... it wasn't my turn yet?
You were hell-bent on killing the Old Man.
What's this sudden change of heart?
That dying old man?
I'll eliminate him later.
But right now...
I don't want to see you enjoying victory!
Hey now, Crocodile-man!
D-Doflamingo!
So you're ditching me to team up with Whitebeard?
It's enough to make a guy jealous, ya know...
I don't team up with anybody.
That's the same as brushing me off.
More or less.
I don't get what's going on... but we were saved.
End of the line, Straw-Hat!
Die!
Get out of...
my way!
Stop right there, Straw-Hat!
I will not let you go any further!
Move it!
Stop Straw-Hat!
Don't let him get any closer!
Admiral Sakazuki!
That hurts!
Damn it!
I'm indebted to your granddad, but...
I have no choice!
You have chosen your own death!
You!  Do not lay a hand on Luffy!
Admiral!
That's...
The Commander of the First Division... Marco!
Thanks for saving me.
Don't mention it.
Three people have penetrated the plaza!
Devil Fruit users are passing over the walls!
T-Three people?
I wonder if I am included in those three people...?
How on Earth did they find out?!
I escaped Admiral Aokiji's attack by a whisker...
and confronted death countless times!
I'd finally made it this far...
but no matter how many lives I have, it's not enough!
There is no safe place any more!
My pursuers!
Was that...
Cross the water and head for Oars!
Whatever happens, get to the plaza!
Fleet Admiral!
The pirates in the bay are acting strangely!
What?
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Cross the water and head for Oars!
Whatever happens, get to the plaza!
The pirates are getting desperate.
Defend the gap in the walls!
Yes sir!
Even after losing their ships and their footing, they're still as frenzied as ever.
Foolish pirates.
They're sitting ducks!  Fire!
Don't give up!
Keep going straight ahead!
Head toward Oars!
Get up to the plaza!
What's gotten into them?!
Even in this situation, their morale isn't dropping at all!
Charge!
Everyone, get on board!
Yeah!
Hold on tight!
No way!  A ship...
Big trouble!
Another coated ship has emerged from the bay!
Damn it!
It was hiding underwater the whole time!
I don't remember saying that we'd used all of our ships!
It's a paddle ship!
It's going to ram us!
What the?!
Sink it!  Just like the Moby Dick!
No, not the ship!
Shoot Oars!
Huh?  Oars?
Too late!
Here we go, everyone!
H-He pulled the whole ship in!
The intruders have breached the walls!
We're in the plaza!
Let's save Ace!
Time to overthrow Navy HQ!
Hang in there, Ace!
They got us.
There was one tiny mouse hole in the walls, and they swarmed right in.
Those walls may wind up working against us.
Old Man!
Whitebeard...
Still got your head, Ace?
We made it!
Now Ace-kun can be resc-
Oars!
Save... Ace-kun...
Oars...
Whitebeard has entered the plaza!
Stand back, my sons.
Men!
Rescue Ace, and destroy the Navy!
Garp...
Yeah.
It looks like even we have to take a hand in this!
Here I come, Ace!
Whitebeard has finally made it to Ace.
However, Aokiji and Akainu take on Whitebeard together,
and the battlefield erupts into a brawl.
Meanwhile, Marco exploits an opening and quickly makes a move for Ace.
Next time, on One Piece:
Luffy at the Limit of his Strength!
All-Out War in Oris Plaza!!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!