It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew,
and then he broke into Navy HQ to save his brother Ace from imminent execution...
but his efforts were in vain.
Thus, the curtain came down on the great war of Marineford, which will be engraved forever in history.
And now, we go back in time ten years...
To East Blue...
Luffy.  That's Ace.
Starting today, you'll be living with these people.
Take me with you!  Let's be friends!
I'm out of the forest!
We got a lot of money out of him.
It went just like Porchemy-san said it would.
As soon as we told that greedy merchant it was treasure from the Grand Line,
the look in his eyes changed and he paid us immediately!
Even though it was just some trash that washed up on the beach.
Good thing we were dealing with some chicken who's never even been out to sea.
Granted, neither have we...
What's with this place?
To the north of Mt. Corvo, where the Dadan family lives, lies this place.
Smoke constantly rises from the mountains of discarded trash.
Things that are no longer needed are gathered here.
The inhabitants are all outlaws who have been banished from the kingdom.
Naturally, it's a lawless zone.
Without so much as a doctor, both crime and disease runs rampant.
This is the Gray Terminal.
Ace!
What's that?
He ain't here...
Hey!  Where'd you go?
Ace!
What, it's already past noon?
Treasure... Treasure...
Isn't there anything valuable here?
I found treasure!
Hand it over!
No, it's mine!
You gotta be kidding!  I found it!
Don't touch it, you bastards!
I'm gonna take it to town and sell it!
I won't let you have it!
Wait!
Damn it!
Give it to me!
You wouldn't have gotten hurt if you had just given it to me right away.
Good job!
Why, you...
Are you kidding me?!
Thief!
Get outta my way, kid!
Hurry it up!  If you don't move soon...
He ran this way!
Sabo!  Sabo, are you there?
Oh, Ace!
Sorry I'm late.
You sure are!
I've already done some work in the city.
Really?  Truth is, I have too.
Here we go!
Amazing!  You've even got more than me!
This is a lot of treasure!  How'd you get it?
I stole it from some hoodlums near the main gate.
Damn... You beat me again today.
It doesn't matter who wins, does it?
We're gonna spend the Pirate Fund together one day.
It must be five years since we started saving, huh?
We've worked hard.
We sure have!
To leave East Blue and head into a world these islanders don't even know about...
I get excited just thinking about it!
Hurry and close the lid.  We don't know who might be watching.
I wonder how much we need to buy a pirate ship?
Who knows... Hundreds of thousands, or maybe even millions...
Whatever it is, we still got a long way to go.
A pirate ship?!
Are you guys gonna be pirates?!
So am I!
Hey!
Be quiet!
Ace!  So this is where you've been going every day?
Shut up.
So this is the Luffy-guy you've been talking about?
You've been telling him about me?
Yeah, I've been complaining about how clingy you are!
And how you never think about what you're doing!
I see!
Doesn't he realize that we're insulting him?
He finally made it all the way here.
And I made sure to avoid the paths that ordinary people can travel...
Hey you!  Are you Ace's friend?
Be my friend too!
Shut your trap!  And stop calling me "You"!
Then, what's your name?
Sa-
I won't tell you!
This is why I said you should just live here!
Taking that round trip and training in the mountains each day just caused us a lot of trouble!
What are we gonna do?
Now that he knows our secret...
I'm sure he'll just tell everyone if we let him.
Let's kill him.
Right.  Let's do that.
Don't kill me!
Someone save me!
I don't wanna die!
You idiot!  Be quiet!
Sabo!  Hurry and do it!
Why do I have to do it?!  You do it!
I've never killed anyone before!
Neither have I!  I don't know how to do it!
Please don't drop me in the water!
Right!  The river!
Why'd he tell us?
'Cause he's an idiot!
Somebody help me!
Shut up!
I don't wanna die!
I heard a voice from the forest.  A child's voice!
Oh no!  Someone's coming!
For starters, let's untie him!
If we don't get away from here, they'll find our treasure!
Those brats are pretty famous around these parts... Ace and Sabo.
You're absolutely certain...
it was Ace who stole your money, right?
Yeah... We're really ashamed.  We let our guard down.
I can't believe that kid!
Stealing money from our pirate crew!
If Captain Bluejam hears about this, we're all dead!
Damn it!  Those hoodlums were Bluejam's underlings?
Hoodlums?  You mean you got that money from those guys?
We've got some dangerous money on our hands.
That guy carrying a real sword is Bluejam's underling, Porchemy.
He's absolutely crazy.  Have you heard?
He tears the skin off the face of the people he defeats, while they're still alive!
We can't let ourselves be seen...
Huh?  Where'd he go?
Let go of me!  What're you doing?
How'd he get caught?!
Let go of me!  You jerk!
Who is this kid?
Help me!
Ace!
Please save me, Ace!
That idiot!  He shouted my name!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Did you just say Ace?
Yeah, so?
Do you know Ace?
He's my friend!
Oh, but he was going to kill me just now...
He never shuts up!
I should ask...
Ace stole our money and ran away earlier today...
You wouldn't happen to know where he is, would you?
Oh, crap!  They're gonna take all our treasure!
That fool had better not tell them anything!
Hey!  Answer me!
No idea...
He's a terrible liar!
Alright, then.  If you don't know, then that's that.
I'll help you remember, so don't worry!
What the hell?!  Let me go!  Where are you taking me?!
Damn it!  Idiot!  Let go of me!
Idiot!  Let me go!  What the hell?!
What are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?  Well...
Let me go!
I'm not telling you anything!
You damn kid!
I tried to tell you, I'm a rubber-man who ate the Gomu Gomu fruit!
Quiet!
A Devil Fruit, huh?
Yeah, you're a real Devil-Fruit user, alright.
Get my gloves.
Y-Yes, Sir!
Hurry!  Hurry up!  If Porchemy and the others come back, we're done for!
We've gotta move the treasure somewhere else, and fast!
It's only a matter of time before that Luffy-guy spills the beans!
If they find this, they won't just take back what we stole from them...
They'll steal our entire Pirate Fund that we gathered over the past five years!
Listen up, you brat!  The cash that your friend Ace stole...
was our pirate crew's precious money!
And you know where they hid it!
I will make you tell me!
Never!
That's gotta hurt!
You shouldn't make a pirate mad!
Our captain, Bluejam, is inhumanely brutal!
That hurt!  I'm scared!  Somebody save me!
You guys, go search for Ace and Sabo!
We don't have time for you to just stand around here!
Yes, Sir!
You want to know where Ace and Sabo are?
You guys are delinquents from town, aren't you?
You're better off not getting involved with those two.
You shouldn't underestimate them just 'cause they're kids!
They're a pair of mad dogs who can even kill tigers!
Ace and Sabo, huh?  I haven't seen 'em...
But more importantly, pal...
Why don't you hand over your valuables?
P-Please don't!
Let's go look somewhere else!
They still don't know where we are?
I really thought we'd be busted by now...
No way!
Before I know it, the sun's setting...
Alright, I'm done!
I've moved all of the treasure!
What was with him?
Ace!
Sabo, what's wrong?
Have they gone to our old hideout to look for the money?
No, they haven't...
There's no way they'd know where to go!
What do you mean?
That Luffy-guy...
still hasn't told them a thing!
There's no doubt that he's being tortured...
I thought that he would spill the beans right away since he's such a crybaby and an idiot...
This doesn't make any sense!
At this rate, he'll...
They're late...
Who was in charge of finding treasure today?
It was Porchemy, Captain Bluejam.
The sun is already setting.
No matter how you look at it, they must have cashed it in by now!
You think the bastard just ran away with the money?
No, there's no way!
I'm sure he values his life!
You're right.
Just tell me already!
Porchemy-san!
It's no use!
He doesn't even have enough energy to scream!
He probably won't tell us anything and, to be honest, this is so brutal I can barely watch!
Let's just let him go!
If you have the time to protect this kid, then go look for Ace and Sabo!
Our lives are in danger here!  Don't you get it?!
The scheduled time when we were supposed to give Captain Bluejam our money is long past!
Poor kid... Should we call the sheriff from town?
It's useless.  The country's laws don't mean anything out here.
Besides, that guy is a member of Bluejam's crew.
They pay off the Nobles!
No matter what crimes they commit in this country, even if they kill someone, it'll be overlooked!
No matter how many corpses pile up around here, nobody will pay any attention!
Answer me!
I won't!
You damned brat!  Quit trying so hard to keep the secret safe!
Tell me!
I won't...
I won't!
I won't tell you!
Fine.  I don't care anymore!
Die.
Stop it!
Ace and Sabo break into Porchemy's hideout to rescue Luffy.
Even when he's overwhelmed by the pirates' strength,
Sabo fights to free Luffy, taking advantage of every possible opportunity.
This inspires Ace to make an unexpected decision!
Next time, on One Piece:
I Won't Run
Ace's Desperate Rescue Plan
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!