Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Two years have passed since the great war at Marineford.
Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates have all been training on their own,
and now they return to the Sabaody Archipelago in order to move on to the next stage - The New World.
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
H-Hey, you!  You know who I am, don't you?!
Get out of the way, unless you want to get killed
and have your innards ripped out!
Straw Hat was not a piece of trash like you!
What?!
I get it.  All these guys were tricked into joining a fake Straw Hat Crew.
And by some kind of crazy coincidence, the real Straw Hat is here too.
That was close!
T-That's the same face...
as the one on the wanted posters!
That Straw Hat...
He coated his fist in Haki!
Luffy!  This was you after all!
How can you already be in trouble?
It's been so long!
I wonder how everyone's doing?
I'm so happy!
I decided to come and have a look, but it seems you're doing just fine.
Right!
Rayleigh!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna be...
the Pirate King!
The islands...
seem to have become rather noisy.
What are you doing?!
Hurry and take down Straw Hat!
Oh, right!
Hurry up, Luffy!
Rayleigh!  Sorry for the trouble!
Then, Rayleigh...
Thank you so much.
I'm off!
Right.
They went over there!
After them!
Don't let them get away!
Keep going all the way to the top!
The Straw Hat Pirates are headed for Grove 42!
Do not let them escape!
What was that?
The Dark King Rayleigh?!
My apprentice is setting sail.
Please do not interfere.
T-This line...
I'd advise against crossing it.
Oh, bubble bags!
Sure are a lot of them.  What's inside?
It's all provisions.  I'm sure everyone's stomachs
have grown in these past two years too.
You'll have plenty to eat later.
Really?!  I'm looking forward to eating your cooking again!
We found them!  Over here!
They've got us surrounded, huh?
Guess we've got no choice...
All troops, charge!
I... wanna become a flea.
What's wrong?!  What are you...
I wanna become a mite.
What?!
What is going on here?
I... wanna become a louse.
Hey, isn't that...
So you were the ones causing all this commotion?
Honestly!
Why are you still dawdling around here?
You're the woman from Thriller Bark!
Who?
What about you?  Why are you still here?
That's no way to speak to the one who brought you to these islands!
If I hadn't been here, you'd probably be...
Know your place!
A real woman... A real woman...
Well, duh!  Are you diseased or something?!
Anyway, you have to set sail quickly.
Warships have appeared around the islands.
If you don't hurry, your escape route will be cut off.
That is bad.  But for some strange reason...
I can't bring myself to move from this spot.
What nonsense are you spouting?!
Real ladies are the best!
I'm... human trash.
What's that?
I finally found you!
That voice!
Usopp-san!  Nami-san!  Robin-san!
Franky-san!
Brook!
I'm impressed that you left behind your life as a superstar.
Great!
Seeing you all brings back such fond memories.
The two of you have become even more beautiful.
Well then, Nami-san...
It has been two years, so...
Oh, you're gonna sing a song?
May I see your panties?
Like hell!
I didn't show them to you two years ago either!
M-My chest is trembling with joy at our reunion...
Though... I do not have a chest that can tremble.
Hey, the great star is having a fit.
I swear, you guys haven't matured at all.
Incidentally...
It doesn't look like everyone is here yet.
No need to worry.
Chopper just went to pick up the others.
Hey!
So you're finally here!
You guys!
Here they are!
Luffy, Zoro, Sanji!
Hey!
Luffy-san!  I've missed you so much!
You've gotten pretty manly!
We're all together again!
At last...
Hi guys!
Sanji!
Alright then, thank you!
Give my best to everyone in Torino Kingdom!
Usopp!  Is Sanji alright?!
One... One... One beautiful woman...
Hey, hang in there!
Two beautiful women...
This is bad, Chopper!  Please stop his bleeding!
F-F-Franky, you're...
What is it?
Is there anything that bothers you -mecha?
"Mecha"?!  I wanna push that!
Wait, Luffy!
I don't understand how you're feeling in the slightest,
but save it for later!
I just received a report saying that
the warships are almost here!
Damn it!  When'd they get here?!
Three warships!
Hey, are we gonna fight back or what?!
We're gonna get killed!
Fire!  Sink them!
Not good... Those'll hit us!
What just happened?!
T-Those are...
The Kuja Pirates!
Who would be so insolent...
as to leave...
a warship in my path?!
That's the Kuja's mark.
The Kuja?
A fierce female pirate crew led by the Pirate Empress,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
One of the Warlords?!
The Empress, Boa Hancock.
Rumor has it that anyone who sees her beauty...
is completely overwhelmed and turns to stone.
S-So bright!  She's shining!
Her beauty knows no bounds!
I can't believe her unsurpassed beauty!
Unsurpassed beauty?!
Where?!
Beauty... Beauty...
He turned to stone!
Oh, it's Hancock and the others!
Move your ship, Boa Hancock!
Are you trying to interfere with our mission?!
Cease these accusations.
I merely do not wish to let you pass.
H-How selfish!
Is that wrong?
Now, Luffy...
Now is your chance!
She just... winked at me...
We're saved.  Let's set sail now, while we have the chance!
You know that Warlord?
Yeah.  I was sent flying to the Island of Women.
They're all friends of mine.
That legendary island populated entirely by women?
You mean it really exists?
You're on friendly terms with the Empress.
Hey!  Did you even train at all?!
Yeah, heaps!
And I was... I was...
What happened to you, Sanji?
So that's Luffy's crew?
The saga of "It's Filled with Creatures I've Never Seen Before."
One, two, three, four...
They look kinda fun.
Alright, prepare to set sail!
Yes, Nami-swan!
Is something wrong, Usopp?
Come to think of it, did you guys
take out all the marines on the islands?
No... We heard plenty of marines shouting while we were flying here.
But nobody's attacking us from the coast.
Requesting backup!  This is the third platoon!
Do you hear me?!
What is it?!  What's going on?!
It's unlikely we'll be able to reach Grove 42!
Why?!
W-Well...
Enormous bugs appeared out of nowhere
and blocked our path.
What?  Bugs?!
What are these things?!
Shoot it down!
I will not let you get in the way of
Usopp'n's new adventure!
In a parting between men, there is no need for tears'n!
I pray for your good fortune'n, Usopp'n.
If our enemies aren't coming then it's a good thing.
Lucky for us if they've ran into trouble.
Let's set sail before they get here.
Nami!  I'll leave the course to you.
I'll handle it!
Alright!
This is the fourth platoon.  I sincerely apologize!
Due to a sudden downpour,
our ammo got wet and our weapons are useless!
Rain?!  Where is it raining?!
The Sabaody Archipelago is sunny everywhere today!
No lightning!
What would we do if civilians got hurt?
The soap-bubbles here sure are a nuisance.
Even so, what a fine breeze!
It allowed us to get to
the Sabaody Archipelago in good time.
That's because Nami-chan is such a good girl.
Do your best!
Weatheria will be lonely without you though!
It's swelling up!
What?  The jelly's getting inflated?
Oh!  It's a soap-bubble roof!
Listen up, everyone!
The coating can reduce any level of water pressure,
so we need an airbag underneath the ship
to keep us floating.
Once it's removed, the buoyancy drops and
the coated Sunny will sink toward the ocean floor.
That's how it works.
I see...
You obviously don't understand.
Anyway, unfold the sails!
Sails?
A coated ship catches the ocean currents like wind, and moves with them.
So we won't get there just by sinking?
Now, if we don't hurry, the Navy will catch up!
This is the fifth platoon,
reporting from the center of Grove 42!
It's an emergency!  The second platoon dispatched ahead of us have all become negative!
What are you talking about?!  Negative?
I wanna become moss.
It's hopeless... I just wanna become a water flea.
According to their reports, Straw Hat Luffy
fled on the back of a giant bird!
Bird?!  What's going on over there?!
We're in battle with an unidentified enemy!
Sheesh!  That guy was nothing but trouble,
right until the very end!
I'll have to find another toy now.
Reinforcements from the Navy!
Just when we were about to set sail...
Everyone!
Straw Hat's ship is almost within range!
Wait a second...
An enormous bird is headed straight for us!
He's-
They're coming at us from behind too!
I'll handle it!
What do you think, Nami-san?
Do you see...
how much I've matured?
Sanji!
Answer me, fifth platoon!  What are you doing?!
W-We're...
We're currently...
being held back by an unforeseen obstacle.
Please, stop!
You're refusing our invitations?  How could you?!
Are you that shy?
You don't have to be embarrassed!
Let's have a tea party!
M-My heart... My heart feels like it's gonna shatter!
Oh my, what a cute face!
Stop it!  Please, anything but that!
What's going on?!  Fifth platoon, answer me!
Sanji-kyun, now's your chance!
H-Hey, what's wrong, Sanji?!
N-No idea.
All of a sudden, it felt like
someone was crushing my heart.
I've removed the airbag!
Roger that!  What about the sails?
Ready at any time!
Are we ready to set sail, Nami?
Yes.  Give the order, Captain.
Well then...
You guys!
There are loads of things
I've wanted to talk to you about...
But for now, I'll just say thank you for going along
with my selfishness for the past two years!
You're talking as if we've never dealt with
your crazy whims before.
Got that right!  You're always like this.
Rear Admiral!  The ship is escaping into the sea!
What?!  Damn it...
You scum!  Do you have any idea how dangerous...
those people are?
Rear Admiral!
Take care, Luffy.
Unfold the sails!
Right!
Set sail!
Yeah!
Let's go to Fishman Island!
The Straw Hat Pirates have finally set off for the New World.
While everyone gazes up
at the underwater scenery for the first time,
Franky begins to tell the crew about a man they owe a great debt.
And at the same time,
a dark shadow approaches the Sunny from behind.
Next time, on One Piece:
The Astonishing Truth
The Man who Protected the Sunny
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!