It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy has been separated from his crew...
and has finally reached Marineford,
where he's trying to save his brother Ace from execution.
An intense battle rages as the Navy tries to stop Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates...
as they advance on the execution platform where Ace is held.
Why are all of you here?!
This is my failure!
There's no need for anyone else to get hurt!
Stop this!
Why are you all doing this for me?!
I'm your little brother!
Kuma!  Kuma, come to vyour senses!
It's vme!  Have vyou forgotten vmy face?!
Come to vyour senses, or Vi will fight back!
There's a limit to how much Vi can take!
I don't know what sort of history you two have,
but just give it up.
There's no point in talking to him, Emporio Ivankov, Commander in the Revolutionary Army.
Vyou're...
What are vyou saying?!  What's going on?!
The man you knew was probably named Bartholomew Kuma, right?
If you're thinking of the man once called Kuma the Tyrant...
he's long dead.
You can't defeat me with your ability.
Damn, it's that... jutte...
Get your filthy hands off him!
She managed to hit me, even though I'm smoke...
That's...
The Pirate Empress protected Straw Hat!
Hancock!  What are you playing at?!
Do you intend to quit being a Warlord, too?
Silence!
I am so infuriated, I don't care what you say!
How dare you beat and hold down my dearest?!
I will not let you live!
I have never been this angry before!
I will rip you apart and feed you to a beast!
So that was the Haki of the Kuja Tribe...
W-What's going on?  Why did
the Pirate Empress protect Straw Hat?
No, that's not it!  She didn't protect him!  She's gonna petrify him herself!
I always believed that you would make it here alive.
Take this.
This is the key to your brother's handcuffs.
That's it!  The Empress' witchcraft!
Straw Hat has been petrified!
Did she turn him into stone?
Hancock!
He said my name again!
Luffy's hand... Luffy's hand...
touched mine!
Hancock!
You're... You're...
Thanks a lot!  I owe you one!
I-It's alright!  It's alright!
Do not worry about it, just...
Just keep moving forward, Luffy!
Oh, yeah!
Thanks!
It can't be!  The Pirate Empress lost!
He crushed her attack!  He must have countered it with Sumo wrestling!
Look at how much pain she's in!
He managed to overpower one of the Seven Warlords... Straw Hat Luffy is unbelievable!
So... So... So...
His embrace was so strong!
I can still feel Luffy's body in my arms, and on my chest.
So this is...
So this is what I heard so much about...
Marriage!
Big Sister, congratulations!
Snake Princess!
She's so beautiful!
I hope you'll be happy!
Snake Princess!
Luffy...
Hancock...
You look really beautiful.
I am so happy!
I'll make you happy forever, Honey.
Yes!
Honey...
Honey!
Luffy!  I see it!  I can see it!
The bond between us, it cannot be broken.  No matter what happens!
This red thread, like a great snake, cannot be cut by anyone!
Luffy!
I'm not letting you go, Straw Hat!
Insolent one!  I shall not let you past me!
Look at that!  It's her Extreme Looking-Down Pose!
She's looking so far down her nose, she up looks up instead!
Don't you know what'll happen if you get in the Navy's way?
No matter what I do, I shall be forgiven...
for I am beautiful!
I'm really grateful for this!  I'm in her debt again!
Wait for me!
Ace!
What was that?!  Kuma is dead?!
Then who's the man standing in front of vme?
He's clearly alive!  Don't be ridiculous!
Damn you!
Iva-chan!
It's that bear-like guy!
Be careful, Iva-chan!  He'll blast you away!
Vi'll be fine.  Now, Kuma!  Move!
Iva-chan, you know this guy?
Yeah... But he's acting a little odd.
It seems like the two of you have memories of Kuma,
but the Kuma you know, and this guy,
are two different people!
Different people?  What's he talking about?
That's not possible!  This is, without a doubt, the one who ate the Nikyu Nikyu Fruit.
He's Kuma!  Kuma, answer vme!
This is so irritating!  But, then again, he was always a man of few words...
I keep telling you that it's useless, no matter how much you talk to him.
Just a couple of days ago...
the Government's head scientist Doctor Vegapunk completed his final modifications on him...
transforming him into a perfect human weapon.
In other words, this is the former Bartholomew Kuma!
Modifications?  A weapon?  What are vyou talking about?!
Basically, he was selected...
by the Government's human weapon project to be a test subject.  He volunteered for it himself.
They started with his hands...
then his legs...
Leaving his consciousness intact,
the scientists replaced his body parts one by one over long periods of time.
Don't lie!  Kuma hates the World Government!
He would never...
offer his own life to the Government!
Well, I don't know what kind of deal this guy had with the Government.
A couple of days ago, there was definitely some human left in him.
But now, he's lost all memory of being born human.  He's as good as dead.
He's become a monster who only fights according to the Government's orders.
The Pacifista, PX-0!
The past is gone, you should just forget it!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Kuma!  What happened to vyour body these past years?!
Now that I think about it...
We will never meet again.
Farewell.
That's the last thing he said to me...
What's wrong, Kuma?  It's vme!  Ivankov!
W-Where is he?  Where did he go?
He's dangerous, you guys!  Be careful!
Damn vyou, Kuma!
Vyou scared yet?
How dare vyou attack vmy adorable Candies?!
Don't think Vi will hold back any longer!
Take this!
He sure is strong!
This is the first time anyone Vi met has...
forgotten...
forgotten vmy face!  That has never happened to vme before!
Oh... Yeah...
However!
Vi don't know if it's because vyour memories are gone,
but if vyou have even forgotten how terrifying Vi can be...
then Vi will just beat the fear back into vyour body!
Get ready!
He sure recovered quickly...
Vi will take care of him.
Vyou all, go help Straw-Hat-boy!
Roger that!
Now, let's go, Straw Hat!
Thanks for the help, Iva-chan!
Forward to the execution platform!
Yeah!
They suddenly vanished into the ice!
It didn't look like Admiral Aokiji used his Ice Age attack again.
Where did they...
This ice isn't cold!
What's wrong?
Listen, you guys, and pay attention!
Blah, blah, yada, yada... Buggy is amazing.
Whisper, whisper, mutter, mutter... Buggy is a genius.
Right?  Then, we've got them.
That's incredible!
The world will tremble in shock, at the birth of a brand new hero!
That's a perfect plan!
Oh, really now?
Let's go, men!
Damn that cheeky Straw Hat!
Don't let him get too far ahead!
It's time to initiate Captain Buggy's Great Plan to Increase his Reputation!
Yeah!
If we succeed, the entire world will be forced to acknowledge my awesomeness!
Don't fall behind, and carry out my plan!
Will this plan really work?
Crocodile!
There's no end to them!
I was thrown pretty far from him...
We're not letting you get anywhere near the Old Man!
Don't interfere...
with my goals!
What a troublesome fellow... He just won't give up.
He's so big, yet so fast...
Here he comes again.
The Captain of the Third Division, Diamond Jozu.
I'm impressed you got out, Crocodile-man.
How was your bath in the pond of blood?
Doflamingo.  Don't interfere.  You wanna die?
What an unpleasant thing to say...
How 'bout it?  Wanna team up with me?
You think you're getting past?
Think you can stop us?
Go, Straw Hat!
Thanks!
Ace!
Forgive me, Red Hair...
I will not go easy on him.
He's...!
Hawk-Eyes!
Now then, fate.
Will the life of a promised child from the next generation... end here?
If not, how will he escape from the Black Blade?
Luffy must get past another one of the Seven Warlords, Dracule Mihawk.
Slashes from the world's mightiest swordsman cut through almost anything...
even the enormous walls of ice.
How will Luffy fight against this overwhelming power?
Next time, on One Piece:
The Swordsman Mihawk
Luffy Faces the Slash of the Black Blade
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!