It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
During their adventure, Luffy and the others try to get a giant beetle to join their crew.
They chase it to a nearby island.
Now, giant beetle! Join my...
There's no way...
Boss would ever...
...become a pirate!
The giant beetle is the guardian of the island,
which is home to the pirate-hating girl, Yoko,
and others who have come from the same place.
This is the village of people who came from East Blue, Kansorn Island!
Also known as Little East Blue!
At the same time, the Amigo-pirates, acting on orders from the legendary pirate Shiki,
are heading toward Kansorn Island.
Oh, there are boulders surrounding the island?
It'd be too risky to go any faster than this.
Ready, and...
NAMI-SAMA!!!
Here we are!
This way, this way!
What is that?
Look!
Nami-sama is here, right in front of us!
She's mega-cute! Even cuter than on the wanted poster!
Dammit! I'm so happy to be alive!
Yeah! Yeah!
Um, what's with you guys?
I'm glad you asked!
We're the special Nami-sama fanclub...
Also known as the OreNami group!
OreNami?
YES I L...
O...
V...
E...
WE LOVE NAMI-SAMA!
QUIT THAT! YOU'RE ANNOYING!
Hurry and take me to Luffy and the others.
Yes! Gladly, Nami-sama!
Seriously...
And could you drop that whole "Nami-sama" thing?
Yes, Nami-sama!
This feels great!
This thing is awesome!
So you like it?
I'm sure it feels nostalgic to you, Luffy-kun, what with you being from Windmill Village and all.
Yeah! We didn't have one this big, though.
That windmill is like the symbol of Little East Blue, after all.
See? This is our dojo.
Kuina! Let's have a duel!
You want to fight me?
Sure!
There!
That's my 2001st victory.
This place brings back memories...
Ok, lunch-break is over!
Time for our afternoon lessons!
Yes!
Ouch! Ouch! That hurt.
He's come to destroy the dojo!
Come on, now! He's not here to destroy the dojo.
Take a closer look!
He's the Pirate Hunter, Zoro-san!
Huh?! Seriously?!
Please, give me your autograph!
How pathetic...
This looks just like Kaya's mansion!
That sure takes me back...
Kaya used to talk with me from the second-floor window...
Usopp-san!
Hey, Kaya!
Did I keep you waiting?
What adventure will you tell me about today?
Yeah, let's see... Today...
I'll tell you about the giant goldfish I fought at the South Pole when I was five!
A goldfish?
The first thing that surprised me was how big and long its droppings were!
I thought it was a continent, and landed on it!
I wonder if she's doing well...
Wha-? It's so thin!
W-What's going on here?
I heard Luigia-san, who lives here,
based it off the mansion she once lived in.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
That couldn't have been this mansion!
W-Wait...
If she lived in the mansion, then could she be related to Kaya?
N-No way! K-Kaya?!
Who is she?! Who is she?! Who is...
So, you're part of the Straw Hat crew?
Yeah, I'm the cook.
Where'd you learn to cook?
At the sea restaurant in East Blue.
Baratie!
Are you really one of the chefs from Baratie?!
Um, well, yeah.
Is that so? Man, I'm so happy!
I fell in love with Zeff's cooking,
and ever since, I've gone there whenever I could to steal more ideas from him.
Really?
The restaurant looks just like the real one, doesn't it?
I'd be too frightened to actually build one at sea like Zeff, though.
But I wanted to use the same style, at least.
Will you please try some of my food?
Well, sure, but I'm afraid I don't have any money.
Oh, that's fine.
Here, have some!
Really? In that case...
This...
I did it!
I managed to get a taste of that damn geezer's food!
How is it?
Does it taste like Zeff's?
Yeah. It's even better than the old man's cooking!
Really?!
This is the happiest day of my life!
Sheesh! Even the cook.
You're tiny.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
So, you say you're from Syrup Village?
Uh, yeah...
You're Yasopp's kid, aren'tcha?
Huh? You know my dad?
Well, yeah.
His pranks caused all sorts of trouble for the village.
Dad?
Oh, that's right!
I heard you used to live in this mansion, is that true?
If you're from Syrup Village, you should know!
That mansion is the symbol of the village!
Everyone admires it!
Yeah...
I've wanted to live in that mansion ever since I was a kid.
After holding on to that dream all my life, I finally made it come true after coming here!
So, you've got no connection with the real one...
The people here know me as a high-class, grumpy old lady!
If you don't wanna die, you'd better not tell anyone about this!
Damn! Even the old lady!
Ah, watch your step.
This sure is an impressive place.
This is a natural maze.
Really?
It's connected to all the various spots on the island.
That's fine and all, but are we still not there?
We're almost there!
Wh-Wh-What the hell is that?!
It's OreNami's symbol!
It sure was hard to make!
We only had the wanted-poster as a reference.
N-No, I mean...why is it naked?!
That was our idea!
Don't worry! We made the parts in front too!
Cut it out already!
Yes...
Boss...
They're all idiots.
How could they let pirates land on the island Dad and Boss protected?
They're... They're...!
That tickles, Boss!
Cut it out!
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com/
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
Listen up men!
We will offer today's prey to the legendary pirate Shiki,
and then we'll be accepted as his true brothers!
The prey is the giant beetle who ran away from Shiki's hideout!
You got that?!
Failure is not an option!
Now, go capture it!
AYE, AYE SIR!
Oh, sorry Bro.
I guess you should be the one saying that stuff, being captain and all...
We've finally arrived, and now it's his siesta-time?!
Oh, crap! He's not gonna wake up for a while now.
Damn you!
Don't do it, Corto-san!
Even you should know what happens if you wake the captain during his siesta!
That's right! We don't wanna die just yet!
He goes and dozes off at such a big moment for the Amigo Pirates...!
Since it's come to this, we've just gotta do it ourselves!
Let's go, men!
Olé!
It's done!
My special steel beetle-cage!
Amazing! You did it in exactly one minute!
With my skills, I could make something like this before breakfast!
Just as I'd expect from you.
Now, we'll have no trouble getting that beetle to join our crew!
Sure! We'll be able to catch it, no problem!
Awesome!
It's a welcome-party for your crew.
Mitsuboshi really wanted to put this together.
Eat up, everyone!
Cheers!
Delicious!
A party in honor of the pirates?!
What are they THINKING?!
We're here.
The plain where the village is lies just beyond here.
Sheesh, you've been saying that all along.
How many hours have we been walking?
We thought we'd give you some time to really appreciate the island...
Are you a pirate as well?
Even the woman... Pirates, pirates...
What a ridiculous time we live in!
Hmph! Pirates, pirates...
Yoko! How can you say that to Nami-sama?!
That hurts! Cut it out!
Hey, wait!
We're sorry Nami-sama.
Her father was killed by pirates.
I see...
What?!
Right, everyone! This is an important message, so pay attention!
We are the Amigo Pirates, and this island is under our siege!
If you don't wanna die,
then hand over the beetle!
Beetle? How does he know about Boss?
Seems you didn't hear me...
How about this?
Wh- What?!
What's going on?!
I don't know!
Watch out!
Wh- What is this?
That giant beetle is this island's guardian, right?
But if there's nothing for it to protect, the beetle won't have any reason to stick around!
Ain't that right?
They're after Boss!
No, Boss! Don't come here!
You mustn't come out!
The restaurant...
The restaurant...!
Old man!
You alright?
Yeah...
I am the representative of this island.
I see. So, where's the beetle?
I am afraid we can't give you the beetle.
In exchange, we'll give you all the money and food we have on the island!
So please, leave now!
Of course, we're gonna take EVERYTHING regardless of what you say!
The money, the food and the giant beetle!
I sure ate a lot!
Who're you?
What're you doing?
Hey, Flashy-Hat. Get lost.
What?!
That giant beetle won't become friends with a pirate.
Just give it up.
What was that? A "friend"?!
You don't get it, do you?
I said I was here to TAKE him!
Wha-?! H-H-Hey, wait a sec!
That won't work on me!
'Cause I'm a rubber-man!
A Devil Fruit user, huh?!
TL Note: Rubber Whip
Zoro! Sanji!
Sure!
I got it!
Here they come!
You still gonna fight, Flashy-Hat?
That beetle's gonna have a rematch with me tomorrow!
I won't let you interfere!
That hurts!
Luffy!
Amore, my beloved brother Corto.
What a disgraceful appearance.
Do not think we will let you off easily just because you are a rubber-man, señor.
You did it! Just as I'd expect from you, Bro!
So melancholy.
What's this?!
Next time, on One Piece:
Movie Special Episode
The Amigo Pirates' Fierce Attack