Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to defeat one of the Four Emperors, rulers of the New World,
Luffy and his crew
formed a Pirate Alliance with Trafalgar Law.
Now they've invaded Dress Rosa
in order to release Caesar to Doflamingo.
Luffy learned that the prize of the colosseum battle
tournament was the Mera Mera Fruit,
and decided to join the fight, competing against mighty foes from all over the New World.
Follow me, Doflamingo!
What's this?
Are you trying to cross the bridge?
Dammit, those guys...
So that's what you were planning.
Wait, Doflamingo!  They have nothing to do with this!
It's over, Law!
Doflamingo's flying toward us!
Young master!
What is this nightmare?!
Are we gonna die?!
No!
Watch closely, Law.
Your allies are going to die a pathetic death right before your eyes!
Stop it!
Traf, hel-
Hey!
Don't come anywhere near my crying crewmates!
Sanji!
Well, here's a strong-looking one.
The Great Clash!
Sanji VS Doflamingo
You're Black Leg from the Straw Hats, right?
Diable Jambe!
Premier Hachis!
Penta-Chromatic String!
Sanji-san!
What did he do to him?!
Let's see if you can protect your crew!
He's coming for us!
You've gotta be kidding!
Young master!
Stay away!
Get lost!
No!
Diable Jambe!
Poêle à Frire
Spectre!
You're pretty tough.
Great, Sanji!
Get him!
W-What's this?!
I can't move!
What?  Sanji-san's frozen mid-air!
He cannot move.
The young master's power has stopped him.
Doflamingo's power?
Black Leg is like a fly trapped in a spider's web.
He can only await his death!
What?!
Look!
What is that?!
A whip?!
Stay out of this!  Run!
Get out of here with a Coup de Burst!
We can't leave you!
Overheat!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun, get out of there!
Shambles!
Room!
Law?
Dress Rosa
Run!
It's Traf!  He saved Sanji!
Sorry, this is my fault.
I'll take us to the ship.
Traf-san?
Sanji!
Dammit, I'm back on this ship!
Caesar!
Oh, Giolla!  Help me!
I am a prisoner as well.
I got careless.
Sanji-kun!
Nami-san!
Doflamingo's attacking again!
Damn!
Black Legger.
Where are you guys at with the destruction of the factory?
Franky said he knows where it is, but that destroying it will be difficult.
Where is Father?!  And Kanjuurou?!
San-goro, what happened to them?!
Momonosuke.
The samurai's inside the factory too.
We will be able to save him.
We still need more time, huh?
Hey you!  Is that my heart?!
Were you keeping it in the cabin?!
This one is mine.  I had your heart.
What?!
Dammit!
So you were storing it inside your own chest?!
You guys.
You have to go to Zou with this guy, right now.
Zou?
Didn't I give you a Vivre Card pointing toward the next island?
Is this a Vivre Card?
That's right.  It will guide you to Zou, the island I mentioned earlier.
This, huh?
We're moving on?  But what about Luffy-san and the others?!
Once the factory is destroyed, we're done here.
We'll catch up with you soon enough.
No, we have to wait!
We can't set sail without our captain!
We are the Straw Hat Pirates!
What?!
A warship's flying straight toward us!
Why?!
Fujitora, huh?
And Doflamingo's coming from the other direction!
The warship's getting closer!
No!
You can stay if you want to, but don't let them have Caesar.
Fire!
Something's falling from the sky!
Meteors?!
Room!
Traf-kun!  The "Swirly Hat Pirates" are setting sail!
Agreed!
Get going!
Hey, Law!
I understand that we have to get Caesar away from here...
and I'm fine with moving forward...
but...
Dress Rosa was supposed to be a brief stop.
Our ultimate goal was to take down the Emperor Kaidou, right?
Don't you think... you're focusing too much on Doflamingo?
Meteors!  Meteors!
Tact!
Isshou-san, there's a hole in the hull!
Oh, what a blunder.  So Law-san was down there.
Is this really the time to be eating?!
Is something wrong?
Let's just go back to Dress Rosa.
The tide of war...
will shift soon, it seems.
Give the order to turn around!
Yes, sir!
Here we go, guys!
Roger that!
Understood, Nami-swan!
You're not getting away!
It's that whip again!
Joker, help me!
Overheat!
Namier!  Listen up.
You have to find a path without clouds!
What?!  Why?
Ito: Thread
Doflamingo ate the Ito Ito Fruit.
He can attach threads to clouds and move through the air.
He can't follow you if the sky is clear!
Threads?  I see.
Just go already!
Here goes!  Coup de Burst!
Look, Doflamingo!
Law, what are you doing?!
Young master, don't worry about me!
You there!  There's something I want to ask you.
You on the second floor!
Yes, you!  Answer!
Hey!  Can't you hear me?
Yes, you!
Hey!
I've only just met my idol, Luffy-senpai...
and now, even Zoro-senpai is calling for me!
I can't stop my tears of joy!
Quite the suspicious fellow.
Who is he?
Hey!  Whoever you are, could you tell us how to get into the colosseum?
All the entrances are closed.
Z-Zoro-senpai is asking me a question?!
I'm so glad I set out to sea!
What's he talking about?
He does seem to be rather excited.
Hey, calm down and listen!  We need...
I wish you could have seen me too, Zoro-senpai!
Luffy-senpai was so freaking cool in there!
Hmm?  I could have sworn he just referred to you and Luffy-dono.
How does that man know who you two really are?
I dunno.
The battle royale rages on in the Corrida Colosseum!
There can only be one winner in Block D,
who can fight in the final round!
The battle to decide who that one finalist will be rages on!
Those movements are not those of a regular gladiator.
But why?  She's had plenty of chances to finish off her opponents, yet she won't attack.
What is she doing?!  She's up against the edge!
You should worry about yourself rather than focusing on others!
Rebecca will be fine.
What?
Hang in there, Rebecca!
Get them!
Hey, why are you stepping back?!
You've got your back against the edge!
Good work!  Keep it up!
What's good about it?
Just watch and you'll see.
I hope you're ready, kid!
Bite the dust, Rebecca!
Kill her!
See?
Keep it up, Rebecca!
Wh-What was that?
What did she do?
We've managed to shake off the Navy and Doflamingo.
We're setting the course for Zou.
What?!  Hey wait a second, Sanji!
You're just leaving us?!
Sorry.  You'll have to meet up with us again later.
You're kidding!
I was planning to run away as soon as the chance presented itself.
And now you're just leaving us?!
Sorry.
Don't worry, Sanji!
You can go to that "zoo" you're talking about.
I'll destroy the factory, no problem!
So, what about Luffy and Law?
Zoro and Kin'emon have gone to contact Luffy.
As for Law...
What are you hoping to achieve by letting half of the Straw Hats escape?
The rest of them are still on Dress Rosa.
I just have to take them all hostage, and I'll have Caesar back in no time.
Didn't you say that underestimating them was a fatal mistake?
It's a shame, but my alliance with the Straw Hats ends here.
I teamed up with them for one goal.
I was merely using them to stop the production of Smiles.
Even if I can't take you down personally,
if you lose the Smiles,
you'll soon be killed by Kaidou.
I see.
So you hoped to take me down with you.
I'd like to see the chaos your death will bring to the world,
but my main priority is settling the score for what happened thirteen years ago,
Joker!
The secret technique Rebecca learned from the one-legged soldier is finally unleashed!
Next time, on One Piece:
Rebecca's Finishing Move!
Backwater Sword Dance
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!