Vegard Aune
otameganekko
It is currently the Great Age of Pirates.
A struggle between countless pirates began
while looking for the great treasure, One Piece,
left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The boy who became a rubber man after eating the Gomu Gomu Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, is one of the many adventurers
who went out to sea to become the Pirate King.
Luffy and his companions have already experienced countless adventures.
Not even the World Government can ignore their existence any longer.
I'm really excited!
What adventure is waiting for us next?
Today, the crew aiming for the New World
will continue through the Grand Line!
Luffy had been blasted off from the Sabaody Archipelago by the Warlord, Bartholomew Kuma.
He was separated from his crew,
and landed alone in a kingdom forbidden to men,
Amazon Lily.
Sister!
Sister, what on Earth is going on?!
What exactly happened here?
No, well, I...
He saw my back!
Luffy, who saw the secret that was hidden on the pirate empress Hancock's back,
was captured and sent to the arena by the Kuja pirates.
Hey!
Hey, what did you do to them!?
They saved my life!
This place is the kingdom of the warriors, Amazon Lily,
wherein if you are powerful, you are beautiful.
You should perish in battle.
We shall watch your death.
There's something wrong with all of you...
Even after your comrades...
Have been turned into stone by that woman,
why are you still laughing?!
That savage is shouting at us!
Unbelievable!
What a fierce animal!
We feel sorry for those three,
but what the Snake Princess did wasn't wrong!
They had broken the laws!
They're the ones at fault!
I will be...
Forgiven no matter what I do.
If you ask why...
Indeed,
it is because I am beautiful!
You're pissin' me off.
Those people use Devil's Fruit powers too?
Execute him!
The snake dance of the younger sisters is about to start!
I want to see Marigold-sama's "Salamander" with my own eyes!
Sandersonia-sama's "Forked Snake" too.
Execute him!
What impressive forms!
This is proof that they defeated
the monster, Gorgon, and took its powers!
Even after they were cursed, the sisters are still beautiful!
Cursed?
What are they talking about?
No matter how it looks, you just ate the Devil's Fruit!
This time that boy will be finished off for good, right?
I can't wait anymore!
Hurry up and start!
Execute him!
Maybe I should swallow him up?
Or maybe I should strangle him to death?
Could it be that he is scared?
You're going to get killed like that without doing anything!
Wait a second!
You're going to beg for your life?
Even if you apologize now, your sins can't be pardoned!
It's nothing like that.
What happened?
Look!
They don't have any cracks, right?
You three wait here.
Sorry about this. Because of me you guys turned into stone.
If Chopper was here, I'd ask him to check on you right away.
It's just like when Robin and I were turned into ice by Aokiji.
You guys might be able to turn back to normal.
Shouldn't you be more concerned about your own safety instead of theirs?
Shut up!
I can do what I want!
That man...
Intends to save Margaret and others?
No way...
Even though he is about to be executed...!?
Well then...
Anyway, I just gotta beat you guys up, right?
No way!
What did that boy just say?
He thinks he can beat the sisters up?
Funny!
Making people laugh during his execution...
Men are really funny!
How strange!
I can do that, right?
Beat you up, I mean.
Yeah, sure you can.
If you haven't given up on your life yet,
let me tell you something.
You'd better not fall into the space
between the audience and the arena.
I don't mind if it happens, but if you fall,
you will be stabbed by the spikes below.
You don't have anything else to do, right?
Nah, I'm fine!
I see...
Then, let's start.
Kill him, Sandersonia, Marigold!
For the crime of intruding on this island of women!
For the sin of insulting me,
show him the art of the punishment!
Finish him off!
Take that, and that, and that!
He's not bad at this huh?
Finish him off, Marigold-sama!
Wha-?!
Poison?!
That was close!
It's a deadly poison!
Too bad for you!
She bounced it back!
That hurts...
Why? I'm rubber...
Look! He was just bluffing after all!
But it's true that men can stretch!
Interesting!
What?
Did I lose my rubber powers?
Guess not...
Then why are their attacks hurting me?
That's unfair.
Don't hog all the fun yourself, Mari.
I want to have some fun too.
Why does it hurt...
When I'm rubber?
That's right!
The guy with the battle-axe was like that, too...
What?
It was just like this!
But he wasn't a Devil's Fruit user...
Which means this isn't a Devil's Fruit ability?
You're a Devil's Fruit user, too, right?
You seem to be a Paramecia type.
I knew it!
Why'd you guys make up the lie about being cursed?
That's a secret.
I can't tell anyone...
Even if they're about to die.
Dammit!
But you can't use "Willpower", right?
People who are not from this island are unfamiliar with it.
That's why you're weak.
A kick with the left foot.
I'm over here.
She predicted my move!
She did it!
Attacks like that won't work on me.
Just like always!
Snake Dance!
Amazing moves!
There is no attack that Sonia-sama can't dodge using her "Willpower"!
You're too easy to read.
I've already grasped your movements.
What's going on?
She's predicting all of my moves!
I don't mind if you focus on attacking her, but...
That hurts!
Don't forget that there are two of us!
Oh, crap!
He's falling onto the spikes!
It looked as though he tried to avoid something...
That man...
Visit us at http://www.yibis.com
Chat us up at #yibis@irc.rizon.net
That was close!
Ah, how disappointing!
He should have just fallen like that!
No matter how much he resists,
he can't be a match for the most powerful members of the Kuja Pirates.
The Snake Princess tucked her hair behind ear!
Her beauty knows no boundaries!
This man is nothing but talk.
How silly.
Shut up, you idiot!
I can't take it anymore!
He insulted the Snake Princess again!
Unforgivable!
Hurry up and kill that man!
Sonia!
Mari!
Put an end to that man's life right now,
so that I will never have to hear...
His filthy talk again!
I wanted to enjoy it a little more,
but since it is our sister's order, it can't be helped.
Then, the play time is over.
Let's hand the convict over to his despair and death!
Margaret!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Don't touch them!
What if they break?!
They saved my life!
I'll break them.
You said they saved your life, right?
Then she deserves it.
Too bad for this girl,
but it's your punishment...
Quit screwing with me!
This fight is between me and you!
Stop it!
From above!
Hey, you!
Dammit! Let go!
You're the only one who thinks that this is a fight.
This is a public execution.
Watch it quietly.
This is nothing compared to the wound in our sister's heart.
The Snake Princess...
Is the woman whom everyone in this country looks up to!
She's strong, elegant...
And the most beautiful woman in the world...
The Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Hey, stop it!
She admired you!
Everyone in this kingdom does.
That's why I think she would be satisfied with that.
Like hell she would!
Are you stupid?!
Such insolent words.
We'll break the other two, as well...
After we're done with this one.
Slowly and taking our time.
That way you will suffer more, right?
Here I go...
Three...
Hey, stop it!
Two...
I said wait!
Can't you hear me?
Useless!
One...
Margaret!
I TOLD YOU TO STOP, DAMMIT!
The warriors are fainting!
Could that be...?
Thank god.
Not a single scratch on her!
What, so you listened to me after all? Thanks!
That was the King's "Willpower"!
That's a joke, right?
Only one in a million people is capable of using the "Willpower" of the chosen ones.
I haven't seen anybody who can use it,
aside from our sister...
That kid has the quality of a king,
capable of standing above all others!
He has the King's "Willpower", just as I do...
What is going on?
Isn't he just an ordinary kid?!
Who on Earth is that boy?!
You guys sure are noisy!
What're you talking about?
He doesn't realize that he used "Willpower"?
So he doesn't have control over it, right?
Alright!
I can tell that you guys are strong!
Let's continue...
The fight.
Luffy activates Gear Second.
But the sisters also release the real power of the Snake Snake Fruit.
Next time on One Piece:
Battle at Full Power!
Gomu Gomu vs. Hebi Hebi.
I'm gonna be the pirate king!