Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
All pirates who seek One Piece
strive to reach the second half of the Grand Line...
The place called the New World.
However, the only one who ever conquered that ocean
was the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The New World has killed
the dreams and ambitions of countless pirates.
And now, the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit
and became a rubber man,
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are going to challenge that sea.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
In order to reach their next stage, the New World, Luffy and the other Straw Hat Pirates...
have gone to Fishman Island,
located ten thousand meters under the sea.
But there, the New Fishman Pirates
are planning to overthrow the Ryuuguu Kingdom,
and Vander Decken has been stalking the Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
The crew find themselves drawn into these events.
Zoro, Usopp and Brook have been captured by Hody in Ryuuguu Palace.
My love was unrequited...
Unrequited!
Oh, right.
What is it?
I know!  I just have to destroy everything!
Every last thing!
Sheesh... You've caused me so much trouble.
Take care of Hachi for me, Caimie.
Uh, alright!
Go, Megalo!
Is this... the power of their drugs?!
We're almost at the plaza.  Hurry, Megalo!
Father...
Hey, it is me -jamon!
Boss Jinbe-sama!  Megalo!
You're alright after all?
Father!
I'm coming right now!
No!  Wait!
Father!
Please, stop!
Princess Shirahoshi!
Stay still, unless you want the princess to get hurt.
P-Please let me go.
Now, let's get going with them!
No way...
Our gallery has grown quite a bit.
You fiend!
Now, this is a nice view!
Prince Manboshi!
Prince Ryuuboshi!
Prince Fukaboshi!
What did those pirates do?
The Princes were wiping the floor with them!
But then the situation suddenly turned on its head!
I haven't rampaged enough -zugon!
Muhi, you're too fired up!
You're gonna turn me into a grilled squid!
The army's soldiers, the ministers, and the Royal Family...
Now, there's nobody left in the country
who can fight us!
What outrageous power.
Please forgive me, Father.
Don't say that!  Their power isn't real -jamon!
But they can still use it
to take the country from us.
Captain Hody, let's execute them!
Roast them!
No, skewer them!
Those royals wanted to coexist with the humans!
They have no pride!
Give them a cruel death!
Put them up for display at the gallery!
Execute them!
Execute them!  Execute them!
Silence.
Decken's crew still haven't
sent word that Shirahoshi is dead.
If I can't lure her here, this will all be meaningless!
Keep your hands off our sister!  She's not a warrior!
What threat does she pose to you?!
Do you think I don't know?
The one I want to get rid of the most...
is the legendary mermaid,
who possesses that most troublesome power.
Hody!
Captain Hody!
We've caught them!
Princess Shirahoshi and Jinbe fell for our trap!
Shirahoshi!
Father!  Brothers!
What luck!
The two people I feared the most, captured at the same time!
This is almost too good to be true!
I really am so sorry.
Just because I fell for their trap, even you ended up...
What's done is done.  Don't worry about the past.
So you came after all, Jinbe.
I used to like you,
back when you were more ruthless.
What happened to you, Hody?  You look different.
It's Boss Jinbe!
I thought he left the island after he resigned from the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
I heard that Princess Shirahoshi
had been kidnapped by Straw Hat Luffy...
Did Boss Jinbe rescue her?
Alright, we have everyone we need.
It was much easier than I thought it would be.
Now, the only ones left are the Straw Hats, and I don't know what they'll do.
I'm guessing that they're at a loss,
looking for a way inside Ryuuguu Palace.
Even if they come here,
enraged by the death of their companions...
we'll be ready for them.
I've been capturing human slaves
on the ocean floor for the past month...
Thirty thousand of them!
And seventy thousand fishmen, all heavily armed!
I-I can't believe this!
They've moved here from the closed-off Fishman District.
In all, we've got a hundred thousand outlaws!
There are some women and children around the plaza, but they can't fight.
We'll take care of them after things have settled down.
Of course, the number of human slaves
will rapidly grow soon!
But for now,
we have a hundred thousand new citizens!
The ones who have disgraced our species
will be forced to surrender their houses to you.
Die or run away... They should decide quickly!
You're causing quite a ruckus out here in public.
How undignified.
You shouldn't let yourself get carried away like this...
Hody Jones.
Long time, no see.
What do you want?
I'd like to say something to you,
since you seem to think you've already won.
Madame Shyarly.
I saw that a certain man
would destroy Fishman Island...
in my predictions.
We might end up destroying it.
So you saw me?
No.
The man I saw destroying the island...
was Straw Hat Luffy.
What?!
What will the boy with the straw hat do now?
Even I can't be sure, but-
What are you trying to say?
That it won't be you!
One thing is certain...
Somebody holds the fate
of Fishman Island in their hands.
But Hody, I know this much...
It is not you.
I see!  Madame's predictions are never wrong!
In other words,
the future where Hody reigns over this island...
has no chance of happening!
Madame Shyarly!
Madame!
How could he?!
Ridiculous.  What were you implying, Shyarly?
Are you trying to get back at me?!
I'm different from your brother.
True, when I was a kid, everyone in
Fishman District looked up to your brother, Arlong.
But we have gained power!
By now, the mark of the Arlong Pirates is just an empty symbol to unite us.
Arlong's name is completely unnecessary now!
The only one who can crush this country down to its foundation, and recreate it...
is me!
I have the power to do that!
Behold, the size of this mob!
This is my strength!
My plan has been in the works for ten years!
Shall I tell you...
who killed the beloved Queen of Ryuuguu Kingdom?
Your beloved Otohime was killed...
by me!
What?!
Impossible!
Then...
what about that human?
You're fools for not realizing it!
A few days before that day ten years ago...
I don't know who you are,
but if the pay's good, I'll gladly take any job.
For real?!
That's half of your payment.
I'll give you the rest after you've finished the job.
Alright, I accept.
Even this is enough to keep me drinking for a while.
So?  What kind of job is it?
It's an easy job.  Even a kid could do it.
But you have to make sure that nobody notices you!
And then, on that day...
Get back!  They're going up in flames!
Put out the flames!
Run!
Protect the Royal Family!
Hurry and put out the flames!
Otohime-sama's been shot!
Hey!  Give me the rest of my money already!
I burned the signatures, just like I promised!
I won't bother you after this, so just give me the money!
What's going on?!
You foolish human.
Damn it... Damn it to hell!
A human...
killed our country's queen!
Queen Otohime's killer was human!
Every single one of you was tricked!
Damn it!  So he...
Queen Otohime.
Hody, you filth!
Father!
Stop it, Hody!
She was quite a nuisance.
Right, Shirahoshi?!
Claiming that revenge against humans was evil...
Preaching all around the island
that we should get along with humans...
And that woman almost realized her dreams.
I hated every single thing about her!
No, she was the kind of person whose influence wouldn't fade even if I killed her!
But to me, your mother...
was someone who just had to die!
Stop!  Stop hurting the princess!
This is too cruel!
Since I couldn't just kill her...
I made an excellent plan to turn her death to my favor!
To renew Fishman Island's hatred toward humankind,
and to break that ridiculous dream Otohime and the citizens shared.
Both of them shattered in an instant!  It was a flawless plan!
Namely, to have a human kill Otohime!
If I blamed the humans, the citizens' hatred toward humankind would flare up again.
And you all fell completely
for the scenario that I set up!
It truly was worth killing her!
You hear that, Shirahoshi?
It was not some human that killed your mother.
It was me, a fellow fishman!
I, the very person before your eyes, was the one who killed her!
I knew.
Shirahoshi!
What?!
They say the people of Fishman Island
built this mysterious giant ship long ago.
It's called Noah.
I don't know why this ship was built...
but by now it's just a relic of the past.
I'll just touch it with my right hand.
Captain Decken... W-What are you planning to do?
W-What?  What happened?!
My heartache from being rejected will never fade.
Wh-Wh-Wha?!
It started moving!
W-What's going on?
Run!
I sent Noah flying straight toward Shirahoshi!
Whaaaaat?!
Noah is half the size of Fishman Island itself!
Which means, if Noah collides with the island...
it won't just kill Shirahoshi,
it'll make the entire island crumble!
There is nowhere to run or hide!
Shirahoshi will live in my heart for all time!
May the entire island perish!
Farewell, my beloved Shirahoshi!
Farewell, Fishman Island!
Shirahoshi desperately tries to
keep her promise with her mother Otohime.
Hody, who taunts her,
finally begins Neptune's execution.
The people are trapped in an abyss of despair,
and shout the name of their last remaining hope.
Their voices echo across all of Fishman Island!
Next time, on One Piece:
Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Finally Arrives
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!